<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:syn="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" version="2.0">
<channel>
<atom:link href="http://feed.zacks.com/commentary/AllStories/rss/TradingView/TradingView" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
<title>
<![CDATA[ Zacks Investment Research - All Commentary Articles ]]>
</title>
<link>https://www.zacks.com</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[ Zacks is the leading investment research firm focusing on equities earnings estimates and stock analysis for the individual investor, including stock picks, stock screening, portfolio stock tracker and stock screeners. ]]>
</description>
<copyright>
<![CDATA[ Copyright 2006-2025 Zacks Equity Research, Inc. ]]>
</copyright>
<managingEditor>editor@zacks.com (Managing editor)</managingEditor>
<webMaster>webmaster@zacks.com (Webmaster)</webMaster>
<language>en-us</language>
<pubDate>2025-05-05 13:50:18 GMT</pubDate>
<lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 13:53:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
<category>
<![CDATA[ Commentaries and Blogs ]]>
</category>
<image>
<link>https://www.zacks.com</link>
<title>
<![CDATA[ Zacks Investment Research Services - All Commentary Articles ]]>
</title>
<url>http://b7d61a7c6b8c307bf531-a92a66b9587e2a0aa805bd4e70b98407.r95.cf2.rackcdn.com/images/zacks/pyramid.png</url>
<description>
<![CDATA[ Zacks Investment Research Services for the Investment Community ]]>
</description>
<height>55</height>
<width>62</width>
</image>
<item>
<guid>
<![CDATA[ https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2461789/cra-international-shares-barely-move-since-q1-earnings-beat?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-analyst_blog|earnings_article-2461789 ]]>
</guid>
<title>
<![CDATA[ CRA International Shares Barely Move Since Q1 Earnings Beat ]]>
</title>
<pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 12:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
<description>
<![CDATA[ <p><strong>CRA International, Inc.&nbsp;</strong>CRAI reported impressive first-quarter 2025 results, with earnings and revenues beating the Zacks Consensus Estimate. The stock has barely moved since the earnings release despite the better-than-expected results.</p><p>Quarterly adjusted EPS came in at $2.22, which surpassed the Zacks Consensus Estimate by 15% and increased 13.3% year over year. Revenues of $182 million beat the consensus mark by 3.5% and rose 6% from the year-ago quarter.</p><div class="chart_embed"><h3>Charles River Associates Price, Consensus and EPS Surprise</h3> <img alt="Charles River Associates Price, Consensus and EPS Surprise" height="266" src="https://staticx-tuner.zacks.com/images/charts/d9/1746444670.png" title="" width="573" /> <p>Charles River Associates price-consensus-eps-surprise-chart | Charles River Associates Quote</p></div><h2><strong>CRAI: Other Quarterly Details</strong></h2><p>The company delivered 76% utilization, while the headcount was down 5% year over year. Non-GAAP EBITDA increased 10.6% year over year to $24.8 million. The non-GAAP EBITDA margin improved 58 basis points year over year to 13.6%, in line with our estimate.</p><p>The company exited the quarter with a cash and cash equivalent balance of $25.6 million compared with $26.7 million witnessed at the end of the prior quarter. It generated $80 million of cash from operating activities, and capex was $974 million. In the quarter, Charles River paid out $3.5 million in dividends.</p><h2><strong>CRAI&rsquo;s 2025 Outlook</strong></h2><p>CRAI announced its 2025 constant currency revenue guidance in the range of $715 million-$735 million for 2025. The company expects a non-GAAP EBITDA margin in the range of 12%-13%.</p><p>Currently, Charles River carries a Zacks Rank #3 (Hold). You can see&nbsp;<strong>the complete list of today&rsquo;s Zacks #1 Rank (Strong Buy) stocks here.</strong></p><h2><strong>Earnings Snapshot</strong></h2><p><strong>Fiserv, Inc.</strong>&nbsp;FI reported mixed first-quarter 2025 results. The company&rsquo;s earnings beat the Zacks Consensus Estimate, while revenues missed the mark.</p><p>FI&rsquo;s adjusted earnings per share of $2.14 beat the consensus mark by 2.9% and gained 13.8% year over year. Adjusted revenues of $4.8 billion missed the consensus estimate by 1.6% but rose 5.5% on a year-over-year basis. (See the Zacks Earnings Calendar to stay ahead of market-making news.)</p><p><strong>The Interpublic Group of Companies, Inc.&nbsp;</strong>IPG reported mixed first-quarter 2025 results. The company&rsquo;s earnings topped the Zacks Consensus Estimate, while revenues missed the mark.</p><p>IPG&rsquo;s adjusted earnings of 33 cents per share surpassed the Zacks Consensus Estimate by 10% but decreased 8.3% from the year-ago quarter. Revenues before billable expenses (net revenues) of $2 billion missed the consensus estimate by a slight margin and declined 20% year over year. Total revenues of $2.3 billion decreased 7.2% year over year but outpaced the Zacks Consensus Estimate of $2 billion.</p><p><a href="https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2461789/cra-international-shares-barely-move-since-q1-earnings-beat?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-analyst_blog|earnings_article-2461789">This article originally published on Zacks Investment Research (zacks.com).</a></p><p><a href="https://www.zacks.com/">Zacks Investment Research</a></p> ]]>
</description>
<link>
<![CDATA[ https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2461789/cra-international-shares-barely-move-since-q1-earnings-beat?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-analyst_blog|earnings_article-2461789 ]]>
</link>
<author>
<![CDATA[ Zacks Equity Research ]]>
</author>
<category domain="tradingview:section">
<![CDATA[ Analyst Blog ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NSDQ:CRAI ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NYSE:IPG ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NYSE:FI ]]>
</category>
</item>
<item>
<guid>
<![CDATA[ https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2461775/is-cvna-stock-a-buy-pre-q1-earnings-key-metrics-to-watch?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-analyst_blog|most_popular_stocks-2461775 ]]>
</guid>
<title>
<![CDATA[ CRA International Shares Barely Move Since Q1 Earnings Beat ]]>
</title>
<pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 12:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
<description>
<![CDATA[ <p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Carvana</strong>&nbsp;CVNA is slated to release&nbsp;first-quarter 2025 results&nbsp;on Wednesday, after market close. The Zacks Consensus Estimate for the to-be-reported quarter&rsquo;s earnings and revenues is pegged at 75 cents per share and $4.04 billion, respectively.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">The earnings estimate for the first quarter of 2025 has moved up by 2 cents over the past seven days. In the year-ago quarter, the company had incurred a loss of 41 cents per share. The Zacks Consensus Estimate for quarterly revenues suggests a year-over-year increase of 32%.</p><p><img alt="Zacks Investment Research" src="https://staticx-tuner.zacks.com/images/articles/charts/7f/102750.jpg?v=225282893" /> <span style="width:100%; display: inline-block; font-size: 8pt;">Image Source: Zacks Investment Research</span></p><p style="text-align: justify;">The Zacks Consensus Estimate for CVNA&rsquo;s 2025 revenues is pegged at $17.20 billion, implying a rise of 25.8% year over year. The consensus mark for 2025 EPS is pegged at $3.67, calling for a whopping increase of 130.8%. In the trailing four quarters, this e-retailer of used vehicles surpassed EPS estimates on all occasions.</p><h2>Q1 Earnings Whispers for Carvana</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Our proven model predicts an earnings beat for Carvana this time around. The combination of a positive&nbsp;Earnings ESP&nbsp;and a Zacks Rank #1 (Strong Buy), 2 (Buy) or 3 (Hold) increases the odds of an earnings beat. You can uncover the best stocks to buy or sell before they&rsquo;re reported with our&nbsp;Earnings ESP Filter.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">CVNA has an Earnings ESP of +4.89% and a Zacks Rank #2. You can see&nbsp;<strong>the complete list of today&rsquo;s Zacks #1 Rank stocks here</strong>.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">(Find the latest EPS estimates and surprises on Zacks&nbsp;Earnings Calendar.)</p><h2>Factors to Note Ahead of CVNA&rsquo;s Q1 Results</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Carvana&rsquo;s used vehicle retail sales returned to growth in the first quarter of 2024 &mdash; the first time since June 2022. The company sold over 100,000 vehicles in each of the last three quarters of 2024 and ranked as the second-largest used car retailer in the United States. In the final quarter of 2024, retail units sold surged 50% year over year. Encouragingly, Carvana expects continued sequential growth in the first quarter of 2025. Our model projects a 32.6% year-over-year increase in retail units sold, reaching approximately 121,868 vehicles for the March quarter.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Additionally, Carvana&rsquo;s cost-cutting strategy is delivering solid results. For the first quarter of 2025, we estimate adjusted EBITDA to rise 85% year over year to $434.5 million, driven by improved operational efficiency. The company has been streamlining its operations through various tech, product, and process initiatives. It has also made meaningful cuts to SG&amp;A expenses by optimizing staffing, scaling back on advertising, and better managing inventory. These moves are expected to support further improvement in adjusted EBITDA margins in the upcoming report.</p><h2>CVNA Price Performance &amp; Valuation</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">On a year-to-date basis, shares of CVNA have surged 26%, significantly outperforming its close peers&nbsp;<strong>CarMax</strong>&nbsp;KMX and <strong>Sonic Automotive</strong> SAH and the auto sector.</p><h2 style="text-align: center;">YTD Price Performance Comparison</h2><p style="text-align: center;"><img alt="Zacks Investment Research" src="https://staticx-tuner.zacks.com/images/articles/charts/a6/102751.jpg?v=1445933378" /> <span style="width:100%; display: inline-block; font-size: 8pt;">Image Source: Zacks Investment Research</span></p><p style="text-align: justify;">From a valuation lens, Carvana trades at a forward 12-month P/S of 2.97&mdash;well above CarMax (0.37) and Sonic Automotive (0.15). Despite CarMax and Sonic Automotive offering lower multiples, CVNA&rsquo;s premium reflects stronger growth expectations. If the company sustains its execution, the premium could be warranted.</p><h2 style="text-align: center;">CVNA&#39;s P/S Vs. KMX &amp; SAH</h2><p style="text-align: center;"><img alt="Zacks Investment Research" src="https://staticx-tuner.zacks.com/images/articles/charts/bd/102752.jpg?v=1559206795" /> <span style="width:100%; display: inline-block; font-size: 8pt;">Image Source: Zacks Investment Research</span></p><h2>Buy Carvana Stock Ahead of Q1 Results?</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Carvana&rsquo;s turnaround strategy is clearly working. Its focus on hitting key goals&mdash;like positive adjusted EBITDA, better profits per vehicle, and growing efficiently&mdash;is paying off. In 2024, the company delivered a record adjusted EBITDA of $1.4 billion with an industry-leading 10.1% margin. Cost-cutting in areas like vehicle reconditioning and transport has boosted profitability, and Carvana expects even more gains in 2025.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">The acquisition of ADESA&rsquo;s U.S. operations has made Carvana stronger in logistics and vehicle processing. Even as the second-largest used car retailer in the country, it holds only about 1% of the market, leaving lots of room to grow in this fragmented space. Its unique, tech-driven business model and scalable platform give it an edge in a changing retail environment.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">While economic headwinds remain, Carvana&rsquo;s improved efficiency, strong fundamentals and clear path to growth are encouraging signs. With expectations of earnings beat in the quarter-to-be reported, momentum looks strong. As such, CVNA stock appears worth considering ahead of its upcoming results.</p><p><a href="https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2461775/is-cvna-stock-a-buy-pre-q1-earnings-key-metrics-to-watch?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-analyst_blog|most_popular_stocks-2461775">This article originally published on Zacks Investment Research (zacks.com).</a></p><p><a href="https://www.zacks.com/">Zacks Investment Research</a></p> ]]>
</description>
<link>
<![CDATA[ https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2461775/is-cvna-stock-a-buy-pre-q1-earnings-key-metrics-to-watch?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-analyst_blog|most_popular_stocks-2461775 ]]>
</link>
<author>
<![CDATA[ Rimmi Singhi ]]>
</author>
<category domain="tradingview:section">
<![CDATA[ Analyst Blog ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NYSE:KMX ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NYSE:SAH ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NYSE:CVNA ]]>
</category>
</item>
<item>
<guid>
<![CDATA[ https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2462057/zacks-investment-ideas-feature-highlights-quanta-services-bwx-technologies-and-constellation-energy?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-press_releases-2462057 ]]>
</guid>
<title>
<![CDATA[ CRA International Shares Barely Move Since Q1 Earnings Beat ]]>
</title>
<pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 12:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
<description>
<![CDATA[ <h2 style="text-align: justify;">For Immediate Release</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Chicago, IL &ndash; May 5, 2025&ndash; Today, Zacks Investment Ideas feature highlights Quanta Services PWR, BWX Technologies, Inc. BWXT and Constellation Energy CEG.</p><h2 style="text-align: justify;"><em>Top Nuclear Energy Stocks to Buy Before Earnings for AI-Powered Growth</em></h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Wall Street pushed the Nasdaq above its 50-day moving average on Thursday as big tech results poured in. The bulls continue to buy stocks as earnings results and guidance highlight the resilience and financial firepower of technology and other critical areas of the economy.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Meta and Microsoft flexed their muscles on Wednesday, following strong reports from Alphabet and Taiwan Semiconductor over the last several weeks. The recent performances are pushing the broader earnings outlook higher, helping Wall Street feel confident that the economy is not headed over a cliff.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">As long as the tariff war continues to cool off and Trump and his team keep talking about progress with big trading partners and China (even if China denies it), the bulls might be ready to press higher.</p><h2 style="text-align: justify;">Why It&#39;s Time to Buy Back into Beaten-Down Nuclear Energy Stocks</h2><p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Quanta Services</strong>stock soared 10% on Thursday after an impressive beat-and-raise first quarter release.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Quanta is an infrastructure solutions standout benefiting from the energy transition, the artificial intelligence power boom, and the overall expansion of the U.S. energy ecosystem. Quanta stock is up 190% in the past three years and is now racing back up to its all-time highs.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">On top of that, Alphabet, Microsoft, Meta, and the other AI hyperscalers are pouring billions of dollars on AI-related capital spending projects despite near-term economic uncertainty.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Large data centers can consume nearly as much electricity as a midsize city, and generative AI platforms like ChatGPT use at least 10 times the energy of a typical Google search. This AI-driven energy boom is arriving just as the U.S. and major tech companies aim to reduce their reliance on fossil fuels.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Given this backdrop, big tech is all-in on nuclear energy to help add to U.S. energy capacity. The U.S. government has launched various initiatives to support the nuclear energy revival, aiming to triple capacity by 2050. The Office of Nuclear Energy, part of the U.S. Department of Energy, posted on X in April that the &quot;U.S. nuclear renaissance starts now.&quot;</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Despite the nuclear energy push, the U.S. and big tech will have to kick things into overdrive soon to start bringing new nuclear energy capacity online in the foreseeable future.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">With this in mind, today&#39;s Full Court Finance at Zacks dives into two great nuclear energy stocks&mdash;BWX Technologies and Constellation Energy&mdash;to consider buying before their earnings reports for near-term upside and long-term artificial intelligence-boosted growth.</p><h2 style="text-align: justify;">Buy this Under-the-Radar Nuclear Energy Stock Before Earnings?</h2><p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>BWX Technologies, Inc. </strong>is a pure-play nuclear technology firm ready to report its first quarter financial results on Monday, May 5.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">BWXT stock trades 17% below its record highs from November. The nuclear energy stock retook its 200-day moving average on Thursday after finding support at a critical technical range in early April. Investors should also know that BWX Technologies climbed 400% in the past 15 years and more than tripled the S&amp;P 500 over the past three years.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">On the valuation front, the nuclear energy tech firm trades at a 65% discount to its highs and in line with its 10-year median, with a 2.5 price/earnings-to-growth (PEG) ratio.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">BWX Technologies is a nuclear power-focused manufacturing and engineering standout, operating across energy, defense, space exploration, and beyond. BWXT is expanding its commercial power segment and gaining ground at the cutting edge of small modular and micro nuclear reactors. BWXT is working alongside the U.S. government and other cutting-edge nuclear energy companies.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">BWX Technologies has topped our earnings estimates for eight quarters in a row. Plus, the nuclear tech company is expected to grow its revenue by roughly 11% in 2025 and 2026, marking its best back-to-back years as a public company. BWXT is projected to expand its adjusted earnings by 5% in 2025 and 13% in FY26.</p><h2 style="text-align: justify;">Is this Nuclear Stock the Best Long-Term Buy in the Entire Energy Sector?</h2><p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Constellation Energy </strong>will report its quarterly results before the market opens on Tuesday, May 6. Constellation was already the largest U.S. nuclear power company before it announced a $26.6 billion deal to acquire natural gas and geothermal titan Calpine at the start of 2025.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">CEG&#39; acquisition creates the nation&#39;s largest clean energy firm and expands its footprint into power-hungry, tech-heavy Texas and California. Adding natural gas is critical since it will grow in the coming decades as the U.S. and big tech race to expand energy capacity&mdash;natural gas remains by far the largest source of U.S. electricity generation (43% vs. nuclear&#39;s 20%).</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Constellation raised its dividend by 25% in 2024 and expects to increase its dividend per share by another 10% in 2025. Constellation projects &quot;visible, double-digit long-term base EPS growth backed by the Nuclear Production Tax Credit.&quot; The energy powerhouse is expected to grow its adjusted earnings by 10% in 2025 and 20% in 2026. Plus, its earnings estimates have jumped heading into its report.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Constellation has soared 315% during the past three years, including its 7% pop on Thursday that helped it retake its 200-day moving average. Despite this run, CEG trades 30% below its highs. A strong report could see it storm back up to its September breakout levels after it landed a 20-year power purchase agreement with Microsoft, and then march toward its peaks.</p><p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Why Haven&#39;t You Looked at Zacks&#39; Top Stocks?</strong></p><p style="text-align: justify;">Since 2000, our top stock-picking strategies have blown away the S&amp;P&#39;s +7.7% average gain per year. Amazingly, they soared with average gains of <strong>+48.4%, +50.2%</strong> and <strong>+56.7%</strong> per year.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Today you can access their live picks without cost or obligation.</p><p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>See Stocks Free &gt;&gt;</strong></p><p style="text-align: justify;">Media Contact</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Zacks Investment Research</p><p style="text-align: justify;">800-767-3771 ext. 9339</p><p style="text-align: justify;">support@zacks.com</p><p style="text-align: justify;">https://www.zacks.com</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Past performance is no guarantee of future results. Inherent in any investment is the potential for loss. This material is being provided for informational purposes only and nothing herein constitutes investment, legal, accounting or tax advice, or a recommendation to buy, sell or hold a security. No recommendation or advice is being given as to whether any investment is suitable for a particular investor. It should not be assumed&nbsp;that any investments in securities, companies, sectors or markets identified and described were or will be profitable. All information is current as of the date of herein and&nbsp;is subject to change without notice. Any views or opinions expressed may not reflect those of the firm as a whole. Zacks Investment Research does not engage in investment banking, market making or asset management activities of any securities. These returns are from hypothetical portfolios consisting of stocks with Zacks Rank = 1 that were rebalanced monthly with zero transaction costs. These are not the returns of actual portfolios of stocks. The S&amp;P 500 is an unmanaged index. Visit https://www.zacks.com/performancefor information about the performance numbers displayed in this press release.</p><p><a href="https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2462057/zacks-investment-ideas-feature-highlights-quanta-services-bwx-technologies-and-constellation-energy?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-press_releases-2462057">This article originally published on Zacks Investment Research (zacks.com).</a></p><p><a href="https://www.zacks.com/">Zacks Investment Research</a></p> ]]>
</description>
<link>
<![CDATA[ https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2462057/zacks-investment-ideas-feature-highlights-quanta-services-bwx-technologies-and-constellation-energy?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-press_releases-2462057 ]]>
</link>
<author>
<![CDATA[ Zacks Equity Research ]]>
</author>
<category domain="tradingview:section">
<![CDATA[ Press Releases ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ CEG ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NYSE:PWR ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NYSE:BWXT ]]>
</category>
</item>
<item>
<guid>
<![CDATA[ https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2461774/gm-vs-tsla-which-auto-giant-is-a-better-investment-option-now?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-analyst_blog|most_popular_stocks-2461774 ]]>
</guid>
<title>
<![CDATA[ CRA International Shares Barely Move Since Q1 Earnings Beat ]]>
</title>
<pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 12:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
<description>
<![CDATA[ <p style="text-align: justify;">A fresh wave of auto tariffs is rattling the U.S. auto industry &mdash; this time targeting imported parts rather than fully assembled vehicles. While previous levies largely spared American-made cars, the new tariff on auto parts affects nearly every vehicle produced in the United States. Not one of the 10 million cars built in the country last year rolled off the line without some foreign components. With the implementation of the new duties, tens of billions in additional costs are looming over manufacturers, which will potentially be passed down to consumers in the form of higher prices.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Already vulnerable to economic cycles, the auto industry now faces even greater uncertainty. In this environment, investors must be extra cautious. So, how do two of the sector&rsquo;s biggest names&mdash;<strong>General Motors</strong> GM and <strong>Tesla</strong> TSLA&mdash;stack up as investment opportunities amid these headwinds? Let&rsquo;s break down their fundamentals, growth catalysts and looming risks to determine which automaker offers the better bet right now.</p><h2 style="text-align: justify;">The Case for General Motors</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">General Motors is the country&rsquo;s top-selling automaker, supported by strong demand for its popular pickups and SUVs. In its recently released first-quarter 2025 results, GM continued its streak of beating earnings expectations, showing resilience despite tough conditions.</p><div class="chart_embed"><h2 style="text-align: center;">General Motors Company Price, Consensus and EPS Surprise</h2><p style="text-align: center;"> <img alt="General Motors Company Price, Consensus and EPS Surprise" height="266" src="https://staticx-tuner.zacks.com/images/charts/39/1746443262.png" title="" width="574" /> </p><p style="text-align: center;">General Motors Company price-consensus-eps-surprise-chart | General Motors Company Quote</p></div><p style="text-align: justify;">However, the company wouldn&rsquo;t be immune to the tariffs. Citing uncertainty, GM lowered its full-year guidance. It now expects adjusted EBIT between $10 billion and $12.5 billion, down from the earlier range of $13.7 billion to $15.7 billion. Net income forecasts were also trimmed to $8.2 billion&ndash;$10.1 billion from the previous $11.2 billion&ndash;$12.5 billion. Free cash flow expectations have dropped, too, and GM has paused its share buyback program until the full tariff impact is clearer.</p><h2 style="text-align: center;">Earnings Estimates for GM</h2><p style="text-align: center;"><img alt="Zacks Investment Research" src="https://staticx-tuner.zacks.com/images/articles/charts/6f/102744.jpg?v=1649873451" /> <span style="width:100%; display: inline-block; font-size: 8pt;">Image Source: Zacks Investment Research</span></p><p style="text-align: justify;">Despite these near-term headwinds, GM&rsquo;s long-term story is intact, especially its shift toward electric vehicles. It was the second-largest EV seller in the United States last reported quarter, with Chevrolet emerging as the fastest-growing EV brand. Impressively, GM&rsquo;s EV lineup became &quot;variable profit positive&quot; by the end of 2024, meaning it now covers its production costs. The company aims to reduce those losses even further this year.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Strategic partnerships with firms like Vianode, LG Chemical and Lithium Americas have strengthened GM&rsquo;s EV supply chain. Meanwhile, cost-cutting remains a priority. GM met its $2 billion cost reduction target in 2024 and is targeting an additional $1 billion in annual savings by exiting its robotaxi program.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Financially, GM is in good shape. It ended the first quarter with $20.7 billion in cash and is seeing progress in its China restructuring, aiming to return to profitability there this year.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">In short, while GM faces near-term challenges, its strong ICE and EV portfolios, improving cost structure, and solid balance sheet support its long-term potential.</p><h2>The Case for Tesla</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Tesla, once seen as the gold standard in the electric vehicle world, is now facing a tough stretch. The company is dealing with falling deliveries across major markets, as competition heats up from legacy automakers and new EV entrants. Its brand image has also taken a hit. CEO Elon Musk&rsquo;s political involvement has distracted him from the company&rsquo;s core operations. In the first quarter of 2025, Tesla missed its earnings expectations.</p><div class="chart_embed"><h2 style="text-align: center;">Tesla, Inc. Price, Consensus and EPS Surprise</h2><p style="text-align: center;"> <img alt="Tesla, Inc. Price, Consensus and EPS Surprise" height="266" src="https://staticx-tuner.zacks.com/images/charts/c1/1746443450.png" title="" width="573" /> </p><p style="text-align: center;">Tesla, Inc. price-consensus-eps-surprise-chart | Tesla, Inc. Quote</p></div><p style="text-align: justify;">Musk recently said he would reduce his role in the U.S. government&rsquo;s Department of Government Efficiency (DOGE) and focus more on Tesla. But it&rsquo;s unclear whether this move can undo the damage already done. The company has been offering steep discounts to keep sales going, but that&rsquo;s putting pressure on its automotive profit margins. Amid the global tariff uncertainty and ongoing challenges in China, the company plans to revisit its 2025 delivery volume guidance in the next quarterly update.</p><h2 style="text-align: center;">Earnings Estimates for TSLA</h2><p style="text-align: center;"><img alt="Zacks Investment Research" src="https://staticx-tuner.zacks.com/images/articles/charts/fc/102747.jpg?v=411613685" /> <span style="width:100%; display: inline-block; font-size: 8pt;">Image Source: Zacks Investment Research</span></p><p style="text-align: justify;">One bright spot is Tesla&rsquo;s energy generation and storage segment. This part of the business is growing fast and is more profitable, but it&rsquo;s not enough to balance out the weakness in its EV division.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Financially, Tesla is strong. As of March 31, 2025, the company had $37 billion in cash, up slightly from the previous quarter. Its long-term debt is low, with a debt-to-capital ratio of just 7. This gives it the flexibility to invest in new opportunities.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Looking ahead, Tesla is betting big on self-driving technology. Musk plans to launch robotaxi services in Austin this June. The company is also working on its humanoid robot, Optimus, and a two-seat autonomous vehicle called the Cybercab, set for volume production in 2026. While these plans are exciting, they are still in early stages and come with execution risks.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">For now, Tesla&rsquo;s core business&mdash;selling electric cars&mdash;is under pressure. The company&rsquo;s future depends on its ability to deliver on ambitious new projects while stabilizing its existing operations.</p><h2>GM Looks Undervalued, TSLA Too Pricey</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Tesla is trading at a forward sales multiple of 8.75X, above its median of 7.72X over the last five years. Tesla has a&nbsp;Value Score&nbsp;of F. Meanwhile, General Motors has a Value Score of A, with its forward sales multiple at 0.25X, below its 5-year average of 0.32.</p><p style="text-align: center;"><img alt="Zacks Investment Research" src="https://staticx-tuner.zacks.com/images/articles/charts/03/102748.jpg?v=498194079" /> <span style="width:100%; display: inline-block; font-size: 8pt;">Image Source: Zacks Investment Research</span></p><h2>Conclusion</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Both GM and Tesla are facing challenges right now. Tesla, once seen as the top name in EVs, is struggling with falling sales, shrinking profits and distractions from its CEO. While its future plans&mdash;like robotaxis and humanoid robots&mdash;sound exciting, they&rsquo;re still just promises at this stage. The core car business is clearly under pressure.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">GM, on the other hand, has its own issues, especially with tariffs and lowered guidance. But it&rsquo;s still holding up better. It continues to sell a lot of trucks and SUVs, and its EV push is gaining ground. In fact, GM&rsquo;s electric portfolio was near breakeven on variable profit in the last reported quarter. The company is also cutting costs and building strong partnerships to support its future goals.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">So, while both General Motors and Tesla are navigating an environment marked by economic uncertainty, rising tariffs and shifting consumer demand, GM may be the better pick for investors seeking a more balanced exposure to the auto sector right now. Tesla still has the bigger brand and bold vision, but GM currently offers more stability and a more grounded execution strategy.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Tesla currently carries a Zacks Rank #5 (Strong Sell), while GM is #3 Ranked (Hold).</p><p style="text-align: justify;">You can see&nbsp;<strong>the complete list of today&rsquo;s Zacks #1 Rank (Strong Buy) stocks here</strong></p><p><a href="https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2461774/gm-vs-tsla-which-auto-giant-is-a-better-investment-option-now?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-analyst_blog|most_popular_stocks-2461774">This article originally published on Zacks Investment Research (zacks.com).</a></p><p><a href="https://www.zacks.com/">Zacks Investment Research</a></p> ]]>
</description>
<link>
<![CDATA[ https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2461774/gm-vs-tsla-which-auto-giant-is-a-better-investment-option-now?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-analyst_blog|most_popular_stocks-2461774 ]]>
</link>
<author>
<![CDATA[ Rimmi Singhi ]]>
</author>
<category domain="tradingview:section">
<![CDATA[ Analyst Blog ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NYSE:GM ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NSDQ:TSLA ]]>
</category>
</item>
<item>
<guid>
<![CDATA[ https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2461772/henry-schein-q1-earnings-top-estimates-revenues-miss-stock-falls?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-analyst_blog|earnings_article-2461772 ]]>
</guid>
<title>
<![CDATA[ CRA International Shares Barely Move Since Q1 Earnings Beat ]]>
</title>
<pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 12:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
<description>
<![CDATA[ <p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Henry Schein, Inc.&nbsp;</strong>HSIC registered adjusted earnings per share (EPS) of $1.15 in the first quarter of 2025, up 4.5% from the year-ago period&rsquo;s figure. The figure topped the Zacks Consensus Estimate by 3.6%. (Find the latest EPS estimates and surprises on Zacks Earnings Calendar).</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Excluding adjustments such as restructuring costs, acquisition intangible amortization, cyber incident-insurance proceeds and others, the company reported a GAAP EPS of 88 cents. This compares to the year-ago quarter&rsquo;s earnings of 72 cents.</p><h2>HSIC&rsquo;s Q1 Revenues in Detail</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Henry Schein reported net sales of $3.17 billion, down 0.1% year over year. The metric also lagged the Zacks Consensus Estimate by 1.8%.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Meanwhile, constant currency total net sales increased 1.4%. Excluding the impact of personal protective equipment (PPE) and COVID-19 test kits, constant currency sales growth was 2% year over year.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Following the earnings announcement, HSIC stock declined 1.4% in pre-market trading today.</p><h2>HSIC&rsquo;s Q1 Segmental Analysis</h2><h3><em>Global&nbsp;Distribution and Value-Added Services</em></h3><p style="text-align: justify;">Sales in the segment fell 0.7% on a reported basis (up 0.8% in constant currencies) year over year, to $2.68 billion. This was almost in line with our model&rsquo;s projection.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Within this, Global Dental Distribution merchandise sales for the quarter rose 0.4% in constant currencies. Monthly sales growth accelerated throughout the quarter after a slow start in January, primarily due to weather-related events in the United States.</p><div class="chart_embed"><h3 style="text-align: center;">Henry Schein, Inc. Price, Consensus and EPS Surprise</h3><p style="text-align: center;"> <img alt="Henry Schein, Inc. Price, Consensus and EPS Surprise" height="264" src="https://staticx-tuner.zacks.com/images/charts/01/1746443831.png" title="" width="567" /> </p><p>Henry Schein, Inc. price-consensus-eps-surprise-chart | Henry Schein, Inc. Quote</p></div><p style="text-align: justify;">Global Dental Distribution equipment sales decreased 2.4% in constant currencies, impacted by a deferral of sales from the fourth quarter of 2023 to the first quarter of 2024, resulting in a more difficult year-over-year comparison.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Global Medical Distribution sales for the quarter jumped 3% in constant currencies, reflecting increased patient traffic to physician offices, strong growth in the home solutions business and growth from acquisitions.</p><h3><em>Global Specialty Products </em></h3><p style="text-align: justify;">In the first quarter, the segment&rsquo;s sales totaled $367 million, up 2% on a reported basis (4.3% in constant currencies). This reflectedcontinued growth in implant and biomaterial sales and acquisition growth. Our model forecast was $385 million.</p><h3><em>Global Technology</em></h3><p style="text-align: justify;">The segment&rsquo;s sales were $162 million, up 2.9% on a reported basis and advanced 3.4% in constant currencies,led by strong sales growth in practice management systems, including Dentrix Ascend and Dentally cloud-based solutions, as well as in revenue cycle management products. Our model projected $160.8 million for this segment.</p><h2>HSIC&rsquo;s Margin Performance</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">In the reported quarter, the gross profit totaled $1.00 billion, representing a 1.2% decrease year over year. The gross margin contracted 34 basis points (bps) to 31.6% due to a 0.4% rise in the cost of sales.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">SG&amp;A expenses declined 6.7% to $738 million in the quarter under review. The adjusted operating profit was $262 million, up 18.6% year over year. The adjusted operating margin expanded 130 bps year over year to 8.3%.</p><h2>Liquidity Position of HSIC</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Henry Schein exited the first quarter of 2025 with cash and cash equivalents of $127 million compared with $122 million at the end of the fourth quarter of 2024.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Cumulative net cash provided by operating activities at the end of the first quarter was $37 million, down from the year-ago figure of $197 million.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">During the reported quarter, HSIC repurchased nearly 2.3 million shares of its common stock at an average price of $71.58 per share for a total of approximately $161 million. The company had approximately $718 million authorized and available for future stock repurchases as of the end of the first quarter.</p><h2>HSIC&rsquo;s 2025 Guidance</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">The company restated its adjusted EPS forecast for the year, expected in the range of $4.80-$4.94. The figure indicates 1-4% growth from the reported figure of 2024. The Zacks Consensus Estimate for the metric is currently pegged at $4.82 per share.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Projected revenue growth for 2025 also remains unchanged at nearly 2-4% compared with the year-ago figure. The Zacks Consensus Estimate for revenues is currently pegged at $12.99 billion.</p><h2>Our Take on HSIC</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Henry Schein delivered an earnings beat and revenue miss in the first quarter of 2025. The top line was also down slightly on a year-over-year basis. The contraction of the gross margin is discouraging.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">On a promising note, the company has entered the second quarter with solid momentum, reflecting confidence in its core business fundamentals. Henry Schein is advancing its BOLD+1 Strategic Plan, which has been refreshed for 2025 to 2027, focused on growing the distribution business through increasing operational efficiency and enhancing customer experience, growing the dental and medical specialty businesses and corporate brand products, and further developing its digital footprint and digital solutions.</p><h2>HSIC&rsquo;s Zacks Rank &amp; Key Picks</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">HSIC currently carries a Zacks Rank #3 (Hold).</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Some better-ranked stocks from the broader medical space are <strong>AngioDynamics </strong>ANGO, <strong>Integer Holdings Corporation </strong>ITGR and <strong>Boston Scientific </strong>BSX.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">AngioDynamics, currently sporting a Zacks Rank #1 (Strong Buy), reported a third-quarter fiscal 2025 adjusted EPS of 3 cents against the Zacks Consensus Estimate of a 13-cent loss. Revenues of $72 million beat the Zacks Consensus Estimate by 2%. You can see <strong>the complete list of today&rsquo;s Zacks #1 Rank stocks here</strong>.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">ANGO has an estimated fiscal 2026 earnings growth rate of 27.8% compared with the S&amp;P 500 composite&rsquo;s 10.5% growth. The company surpassed earnings estimates in each of the trailing four quarters, with the average surprise being 70.9%.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Integer Holdings, sporting a Zacks Rank #1 at present, posted a first-quarter 2025 adjusted EPS of $1.31, exceeding the Zacks Consensus Estimate by 3.1%. Revenues of $437.4 million surpassed the Zacks Consensus Estimate by 1.3%.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">ITGR has an estimated long-term earnings growth rate of 20.8% compared with the industry&rsquo;s 14.3% growth. The company&rsquo;s earnings surpassed estimates in three of the trailing four quarters and missed on one occasion, with the average surprise being 2.8%.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Boston Scientific, currently carrying a Zacks Rank #2 (Buy), reported a first-quarter 2025 adjusted EPS of 75 cents, which surpassed the Zacks Consensus Estimate by 11.9%. Revenues of $4.66 billion topped the Zacks Consensus Estimate by 2.3%.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">BSX has an estimated 2025 earnings growth rate of 15.9% compared with the S&amp;P 500 composite&rsquo;s 11.9% growth. The company&rsquo;s earnings surpassed estimates in each of the trailing four quarters, with the average surprise being 8.8%.</p><p><a href="https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2461772/henry-schein-q1-earnings-top-estimates-revenues-miss-stock-falls?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-analyst_blog|earnings_article-2461772">This article originally published on Zacks Investment Research (zacks.com).</a></p><p><a href="https://www.zacks.com/">Zacks Investment Research</a></p> ]]>
</description>
<link>
<![CDATA[ https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2461772/henry-schein-q1-earnings-top-estimates-revenues-miss-stock-falls?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-analyst_blog|earnings_article-2461772 ]]>
</link>
<author>
<![CDATA[ Zacks Equity Research ]]>
</author>
<category domain="tradingview:section">
<![CDATA[ Analyst Blog ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NYSE:BSX ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NSDQ:ANGO ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NSDQ:HSIC ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NYSE:ITGR ]]>
</category>
</item>
<item>
<guid>
<![CDATA[ https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2461920/take-the-zacks-approach-to-beat-the-markets-adma-biologics-limbach-quest-diagnostics-in-focus?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-analyst_blog|investment_ideas-2461920 ]]>
</guid>
<title>
<![CDATA[ CRA International Shares Barely Move Since Q1 Earnings Beat ]]>
</title>
<pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 12:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
<description>
<![CDATA[ <p style="text-align: justify;">The three most widely followed indexes in the United States have ended the past trading week on a positive note. The Nasdaq Composite, the S&amp;P 500 and the Dow Jones Industrial Average have gained by 3.52%, 2.86%, and 3.41%, respectively. Though the overall economic condition is still gloomy due to major shifts in the U.S. foreign tariff policy, weak economic data, and rising geopolitical tension, investors are betting on strong earnings results and the possibility of a significant reduction in import duties by&nbsp; the Trump administration after trade deals with major trading partners.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">The Gross Domestic Product (GDP) contracted for the first time in three years. In Q1 2025, GDP grew at a 0.3% annualized rate compared to 2.4% in the previous quarter.&nbsp;The consumer sentiment index reported by the University of Michigan for April came in at 52.2, down sharply from 57.0 in March, marking the lowest since July 2022.&nbsp;The consumer confidence index fell to 86 in April from 92.9 in March. The Personal Consumption Expenditure (PCE) index remained flat in March, however, Personal consumption and personal income grew by 0.7% and 0.5% respectively in March compared to street expectations of 0.5% and 0.4%.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">The Institute of Supply Management (ISM) reported that the manufacturing PMI (purchasing managers&rsquo; index) for April contracted to 48.7% from 49% in March. It is important to note that any reading below 50% indicates contraction in manufacturing activities. The U.S. labor market remains resilient. Nonfarm payrolls increased by 177,000 in April, exceeding analyst expectations, whereas the unemployment rate remained unchanged at 4.2%.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Regardless of market conditions, we, here at Zacks, provide investors with unbiased guidance on how to beat the market.&nbsp;</p><p style="text-align: justify;">As usual, Zacks Research guided investors over the past three months with its time-tested methodologies. Given the prevailing market uncertainty, you may want to look at our feats to prepare better for your next action.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Here are some of our key achievements:</p><p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>ADMA Biologics and Intrepid Potash Following Zacks Rank Upgrade</strong></p><p style="text-align: justify;">Shares of <strong>ADMA Biologics, Inc.</strong> ADMA have gained 48.6% (versus the S&amp;P 500&rsquo;s 3% decrease) since it was upgraded to a Zacks Rank #2 (Buy) on March 4.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Another stock, <strong>Intrepid Potash, Inc. </strong>IPI, which was upgraded to a Zacks Rank #2 on March 6, has returned 28.9% (versus the S&amp;P 500&rsquo;s 2.9% decrease) since then.</p><p style="text-align: justify;"><em>A hypothetical portfolio of Zacks Rank # 1 (Strong Buy) stocks returned -3.48% in January 2025 (through February 3<sup>rd</sup>) vs. -0.60% for the S&amp;P 500 index and -2.75% for the equal-weight version of the index</em></p><p style="text-align: justify;"><em>This portfolio returned +22.3% in 2024, vs. +28% for the S&amp;P 500 index and +19.9% for the equal-weight version of the S&amp;P 500 index. </em></p><p style="text-align: justify;"><em>This hypothetical portfolio returned +20.63% in 2023 vs. +24.83% for the S&amp;P 500 index and +15% for the equal-weight S&amp;P 500 index. </em></p><p style="text-align: justify;"><em>The portfolio of Zacks Rank #1 stocks is an equal-weight portfolio, while the S&amp;P 500 index is a market-cap-weighted index that has been notably distorted by the concentrated performance of mega-cap stocks since late 2022. </em></p><p style="text-align: justify;"><em>The Zacks Model Portfolio - consisting of Zacks Rank #1 stocks &ndash; has outperformed the S&amp;P index by almost 13 percentage points since 1988 (through the end of January 2025, the Zacks # 1 Rank stocks generated an annualized average return of +23.9% since 1988 vs. +11.3% for the S&amp;P 500 index).</em></p><p style="text-align: justify;">You can see&nbsp;the complete list of today&rsquo;s Zacks Rank #1 stocks here &gt;&gt;&gt;</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Check ADMA Biologics&rsquo;s historical EPS and Sales here&gt;&gt;&gt;</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Check Intrepid Potash&rsquo;s historical EPS and Sales here&gt;&gt;&gt;</p><p><img alt="Zacks Investment Research" height="438" src="https://staticx-tuner.zacks.com/images/articles/charts/ef/63619.jpg?v=179273311" width="632" /><br /><span style="width:100%; display: inline-block; font-size: 8pt;">Image Source: Zacks Investment Research</span></p><p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Zacks Recommendation Upgrades Limbach and Dave</strong></p><p style="text-align: justify;">Shares of<strong> Limbach Holdings, Inc. </strong>LMB and<strong> Dave Inc. </strong>DAVE have advanced 40.8% (versus the S&amp;P 500&rsquo;s 2.8% increase) and 21.7% (versus the S&amp;P 500&rsquo;s 1.4% increase) since their Zacks Recommendation was upgraded to Outperform on March 14 and March 13, respectively.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">While the Zacks Rank is our short-term rating system that is most effective over the one- to three-month holding horizon, the Zacks Recommendation aims to predict performance over the next 6 to 12 months. However, just like the Zacks Rank, the foundation for the Zacks Recommendation is trends in earnings estimate revisions.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">The Zacks Recommendation classifies stocks into three groups &mdash; Outperform, Neutral and Underperform. While these recommendations are determined quantitatively, our analysts have the flexibility to override them for the 1100+ stocks they closely follow based on their better judgment of factors such as valuation, industry conditions and management effectiveness than the quantitative model.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">To access our research reports with Zacks Recommendations for the 1100+ stocks we cover, click here&gt;&gt;&gt;</p><p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Zacks Focus List Stocks Constellation Brands, Cheniere Energy Shoot Up</strong></p><p style="text-align: justify;">Shares of <strong>Constellation Brands, Inc. </strong>STZ, which belongs to the Zacks Focus List, have gained 8.2% over the past 12 weeks. The stock was added to the Focus List on April 18, 2017. Another Focus-List holding, <strong>Cheniere Energy, Inc. </strong>LNG, which was added to the portfolio on September 6, 2022, has returned 2.3% over the past 12 weeks. The S&amp;P 500 has decreased 6.2% over this period.</p><p style="text-align: justify;"><em>The Focus List portfolio returned -2.96% in the first quarter of 2025 vs. -4.30% for the S&amp;P 500 index and -0.61% for the equal-weight version of the index. </em></p><p style="text-align: justify;"><em>The 50-stock Zacks Focus List portfolio returned +18.41% in 2024 vs. +25.04% for the S&amp;P 500 index and +13% for the equal-weight S&amp;P 500 index. The portfolio had returned +29.54% in 2023 vs. +26.28% for the S&amp;P 500 index and +13.61% for the equal-weight S&amp;P 500 index. In 2022, the portfolio returned &nbsp;-15.2% vs. the S&amp;P 500 index&rsquo;s -17.96%. </em></p><p style="text-align: justify;"><em>Since 2004, the Focus List portfolio has produced an annualized return of +11.39% (through the end of 2025 Q1). This compares to a +10.03% annualized return for the S&amp;P 500 index and +9.87% for the equal-weight version of the index in the same time period.</em></p><p style="text-align: justify;"><em>The portfolio lags the broader market over the preceding year, but leads over the preceding 3, 5, and 10-year periods.</em></p><p style="text-align: justify;">Unlock all of our powerful research, tools and analysis, including the Focus List, Zacks #1 Rank List, Equity Research Reports, Zacks Earnings ESP Filter, Premium Screener and more, as part of Zacks Premium. Gain full access now &gt;&gt;</p><p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Zacks ECAP Stocks Monster Beverage &amp; Rollins Make Significant Gains</strong></p><p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Monster Beverage Corporation </strong>MNST, a component of our Earnings Certain Admiral Portfolio (ECAP), has jumped 30.1% over the past 12 weeks. <strong>Rollins, Inc. </strong>ROL has followed Monster Beverage with 14.2% returns.</p><p style="text-align: justify;"><em>The Zacks Earnings Certain Admiral Portfolio (ECAP), which consists of 30 concentrated, ultra-defensive, long-term Buy-and-Hold stocks, returned +3.20% in the first quarter of 2025 vs. the S&amp;P 500 index&rsquo;s -4.30% decline (SPY ETF). </em></p><p style="text-align: justify;"><em>For the year 2024, the portfolio returned +16.26% vs. +24.89% for the S&amp;P 500 index (SPY ETF). </em></p><p style="text-align: justify;"><em>In 2023, the portfolio returned +12.17% vs. +26.28% for the S&amp;P 500 index. The portfolio returned -4.7% in 2022 vs. the S&amp;P 500 index&rsquo;s -17.96%.&nbsp; </em></p><p style="text-align: justify;">With little to no turnover and annual rebalance periodicity, ECAP seeks to minimize capital loss by holding shares of companies whose earnings streams exhibit a proven 20+ year track record of surviving recessionary periods with minimal impact on aggregate earnings growth relative to the overall S&amp;P 500.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">The ECAP and many other model portfolios are available as part of Zacks Advisor Tools, a cloud-based solution to access Zacks award-winning stock, mutual fund and ETF research. Click here to schedule a demo.</p><p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Zacks ECDP Stocks Coca-Cola and Quest Diagnostics Outperform Peers</strong></p><p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>The Coca-Cola Company </strong>KO, which is part of our Earnings Certain Dividend Portfolio (ECDP), has returned 13.5% over the past 12 weeks. Another ECDP stock, <strong>Quest Diagnostics Incorporated </strong>DGX, has increased 7.9% over the same time frame. Of course, the inclination of investors toward quality dividend stocks to secure an income stream amid heightened market volatility contributed to this performance.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Check Coca-Cola&rsquo;s dividend history here&gt;&gt;&gt;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Check Quest Diagnostics&#39; dividend history here&gt;&gt;&gt;</p><p style="text-align: justify;">With an extremely low beta and a history of minimum earnings variability over the last 20+ years, this 25-stock portfolio helps to significantly mitigate risk.</p><p style="text-align: justify;"><em>The Zacks Earnings Certain Dividend Portfolio (ECDP) returned +5.74% in 2025 Q1 vs. the S&amp;P 500 index&rsquo;s -2.41% pullback and the Dividend Aristocrats ETF&rsquo;s (NOBL) +3.11% return. </em></p><p style="text-align: justify;"><em>For the full-year 2024, the portfolio returned +6.95% vs. +24.89% for the S&amp;P 500 index and +6.72% for NOBL. </em></p><p style="text-align: justify;"><em>The portfolio returned -0.9% in 2023 vs. +26.28% for the S&amp;P 500 index and +8.11% for NOBL. The portfolio returned -2.3% in 2022 vs. -17.96% for the S&amp;P 500 index and -8.34% for NOBL.</em></p><p style="text-align: justify;">Click here to access this portfolio on Zacks Advisor Tools.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p><p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Zacks Top 10 Stock Primo Brands Delivers Solid Returns</strong></p><p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Primo Brands Corporation </strong>PRMB, from the Zacks Top 10 Stocks for 2025, has jumped 7.4% year to date, compared with the S&amp;P 500 index&rsquo;s 3.3% decrease.</p><p style="text-align: justify;"><em>The Top 10 portfolio returned -11% this year in 2025 Q1 vs. -4.3% for the S&amp;P 500 index and -0.61% for the equal-weight version of the index. </em></p><p style="text-align: justify;"><em>The Top 10 portfolio returned +62.98% in 2024, vs. +25.04% for the S&amp;P 500 index and +13% for the equal-weight version of the index. The portfolio had returned +25.15% in 2023 vs. +26.28% for the S&amp;P 500 index. </em></p><p style="text-align: justify;"><em>Since 2012, the Top 10 portfolio has produced a cumulative return of +1767.4% through the end of 2025 Q1 vs. +437.9% for the S&amp;P 500 index and +348.9% for the equal-weight version of the index. The portfolio has produced an average return of +24.2% in the period 2012 through 2025 Q1 vs. +11.79% for the S&amp;P 500 index and +9.89% for the equal-weight version of the index.</em></p><p><a href="https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2461920/take-the-zacks-approach-to-beat-the-markets-adma-biologics-limbach-quest-diagnostics-in-focus?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-analyst_blog|investment_ideas-2461920">This article originally published on Zacks Investment Research (zacks.com).</a></p><p><a href="https://www.zacks.com/">Zacks Investment Research</a></p> ]]>
</description>
<link>
<![CDATA[ https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2461920/take-the-zacks-approach-to-beat-the-markets-adma-biologics-limbach-quest-diagnostics-in-focus?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-analyst_blog|investment_ideas-2461920 ]]>
</link>
<author>
<![CDATA[ Santanu Roy ]]>
</author>
<category domain="tradingview:section">
<![CDATA[ Analyst Blog ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NYSE:KO ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NYSE:DGX ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NYSE:STZ ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ DAVE ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NYSE:LNG ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NSDQ:MNST ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NYSE:ROL ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NYSE:IPI ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NSDQ:ADMA ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NYSE MKT (ex. AMEX):NOBL ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NSDQ:LMB ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ PRMB ]]>
</category>
</item>
<item>
<guid>
<![CDATA[ https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2461919/s-p-500-achieves-a-milestone-after-two-decades-5-top-picks?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-analyst_blog|investment_ideas-2461919 ]]>
</guid>
<title>
<![CDATA[ CRA International Shares Barely Move Since Q1 Earnings Beat ]]>
</title>
<pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 12:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
<description>
<![CDATA[ <p style="text-align: justify;">The S&amp;P 500 Index has been able to recoup all losses suffered due to the Trump administration&rsquo;s tariff-led market mayhem at a lightning speed. On May 2, the broad-market index recorded a nine-day winning streak, for the first time since November 2004.&nbsp;</p><p style="text-align: justify;">With this, Wall Street&rsquo;s most observed stock index recovered all losses since April 2, when President Donald Trump announced the imposition of reciprocal tariffs. The index is currently around 7% away from its all-time high recorded in February.&nbsp;</p><p style="text-align: justify;">During the tariff-led April turmoil, at one point, the S&amp;P 500 was down nearly 20% from its all-time high and was on the verge of entering the bear market zone. In addition, the index also posted two consecutive weeks of a winning run.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">At this stage, we recommend investing in five S&amp;P 500 stocks with a favorable Zacks Rank that have provided more than 20% returns year to date. These are: <strong>Netflix Inc.</strong> NFLX, <strong>Philip Morris International Inc.</strong> PM, <strong>Newmont Corp.</strong> NEM, <strong>CenterPoint Energy Inc.</strong> CNP and <strong>Exelon Corp. </strong>EXC.&nbsp;</p><p style="text-align: justify;">These stocks have strong revenue and earnings growth potential for 2025 and have seen positive earnings estimate revisions in the last 60 days. Each of our picks carries a Zacks Rank #2 (Buy). You can see <strong>the complete list of today&rsquo;s Zacks #1 Rank (Strong Buy) stocks here</strong>.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">The chart below shows the price performance of our five picks year to date.</p><p style="text-align: center;"><img alt="Zacks Investment Research" src="https://staticx-tuner.zacks.com/images/articles/charts/37/102749.jpg?v=2045661410" style="border-width: 1px; border-style: solid;" /><br /><span style="width:100%; display: inline-block; font-size: 8pt;">Image Source: Zacks Investment Research</span></p><h2 style="text-align: justify;">Netflix Inc.</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Netflix handsomely beat the Zacks Consensus Estimate for bottom line while the top line was mostly in line with the consensus mark in first-quarter 2025. Despite trade and tariff-related doldrums, NFLX seems to have maintained healthy engagement levels. NFLX reaffirmed its 2025 guidance irrespective of the possibility of a near-term recession.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">The primary reason for positive revenue and earnings estimates revisions by brokerage firms is the strong visibility of NFLX&rsquo;s business. On April 1, Netflix launched its Ad Suite in the United States. The company will ramp up this Ad Suite in international markets in the ensuing second quarter. The ad-supported offerings will enable management to witness impressive subscribers and ARPU (average revenue per user) growth.&nbsp;</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Netflix&rsquo;s policies of offering an ad-supported lower-priced tier, abolishing password sharing and effective price increase, should help it to become a defensive play ahead of a possible economic downturn.&nbsp;</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Furthermore, Netflix uses artificial intelligence (AI), data science and machine language (ML) extensively to provide consumers with more appropriate and intuitive suggestions. Netflix&#39;s AI platform takes into account an individual&rsquo;s viewing habits and hobbies and accordingly provides recommendations.&nbsp;</p><p style="text-align: justify;">NFLX&rsquo;s AI model compiles subscriber information and recommends content based on their preferences, which can be customized by end users. AI applications enable NFLX to offer a high-quality streaming service at reduced bandwidths. &nbsp;</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Netflix has an expected revenue and earnings growth rate of 14% and 27.7%, respectively, for the current year. The Zacks Consensus Estimate for current-year earnings has improved 3.1% over the last 30 days.&nbsp;</p><h2 style="text-align: justify;">Philip Morris International Inc.</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Philip Morris has benefited from strong pricing power and an expanding smoke-free product portfolio. PM has been making significant progress with its smoke-free transition, with products like IQOS and ZYN contributing to strong performance. In fact, PM aims to become substantially smoke-free by 2030.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Philip Morris is set for another year of robust growth in 2025, driven by increasing demand across all product categories. PM anticipates positive volume growth for the fifth consecutive year, with an expected increase of 2%. Smoke-free products remain a key growth driver, projected to expand by 12-14%, reinforcing PM&rsquo;s strategic shift toward reduced-risk alternatives.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Philip Morris has an expected revenue and earnings growth rate of 8.1% and 13.7%, respectively, for the current year. The Zacks Consensus Estimate for current-year earnings has improved 4.6% over the last 30 days.&nbsp;</p><h2 style="text-align: justify;">Newmont Corp.</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Newmont is making notable progress with its growth projects. NEM is likely to gain from several projects, including the Tanami expansion. The acquisition of Newcrest also created an industry-leading portfolio and provided opportunities for significant synergies. NEM also remains focused on improving operational efficiency and returning value to shareholders.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Newmont has received full funds approval for its Ahafo North project and the project has reached the execution stage. Commercial production for the project is expected to commence in second-half 2025. NEM remains committed to Ghana, investing $950 million to $1,050 million in development capital for Ahafo North.&nbsp;</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Newmont has an expected revenue and earnings growth rate of 0.1% and 16.7%, respectively, for the current year. The Zacks Consensus Estimate for current-year earnings has improved 23.4% over the last 30 days.&nbsp;</p><h2 style="text-align: justify;">CenterPoint Energy Inc.</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">CenterPoint Energy is likely to benefit from increasing electricity demand, backed by rapid electrification of transportation amid rising investments in renewable energy. CNP aims to invest substantially in upgrading its infrastructure. Successful returns from these investments should boost CNP&rsquo;s long-term growth. CNP boasts a solid solvency position.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">With the rapid electrification of the transportation sector, backed by growing clean energy adoption among industries across the board, the utilization of electric vehicles (EVs) has increased manifold in recent times.&nbsp;</p><p style="text-align: justify;">To tap the growth benefits of the EV market, CenterPoint Energy has been investing significantly in building a smarter, cleaner and more resilient ecosystem to meet the needs of EV drivers and fleet operators. To this end, CNP has been actively promoting off-road electrification, including electric forklifts and carts.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">CenterPoint Energy has an expected revenue and earnings growth rate of 3.4% and 8%, respectively, for the current year. The Zacks Consensus Estimate for current-year earnings has improved 0.1% over the last 60 days.</p><h2 style="text-align: justify;">Exelon Corp.</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Exelon&rsquo;s investment will strengthen its transmission and distribution infrastructure and help in providing reliable services to customers. EXC&rsquo;s initiatives in grid modernization will improve the resilience of its operations, and revenue decoupling will mitigate the impact of load fluctuation. A stable cash flow allows EXC to pay out regular dividends. The development of data centers will increase demand.&nbsp;</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Exelon has an expected revenue and earnings growth rate of 4.3% and 6.8%, respectively, for the current year. The Zacks Consensus Estimate for current-year earnings has improved 0.4% over the last 30 days.</p><p><a href="https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2461919/s-p-500-achieves-a-milestone-after-two-decades-5-top-picks?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-analyst_blog|investment_ideas-2461919">This article originally published on Zacks Investment Research (zacks.com).</a></p><p><a href="https://www.zacks.com/">Zacks Investment Research</a></p> ]]>
</description>
<link>
<![CDATA[ https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2461919/s-p-500-achieves-a-milestone-after-two-decades-5-top-picks?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-analyst_blog|investment_ideas-2461919 ]]>
</link>
<author>
<![CDATA[ Nalak Das ]]>
</author>
<category domain="tradingview:section">
<![CDATA[ Analyst Blog ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NSDQ:EXC ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NSDQ:NFLX ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NYSE:PM ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NYSE:CNP ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NYSE:NEM ]]>
</category>
</item>
<item>
<guid>
<![CDATA[ https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2461913/5-momentum-stocks-to-buy-for-may-after-a-mixed-april?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-analyst_blog|investment_ideas-2461913 ]]>
</guid>
<title>
<![CDATA[ CRA International Shares Barely Move Since Q1 Earnings Beat ]]>
</title>
<pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 12:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
<description>
<![CDATA[ <p style="text-align: justify;">Wall Street saw severe volatility and almost day-to-day fluctuations in both directions in April. Finally, U.S. stock markets ended mixed last month. The S&amp;P 500 and the Dow fell 3.2% and 0.8%, respectively. However, the Nasdaq Composite gained 0.9%.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Wall Street has seen severe volatility in April owing to the imposition of President Donald Trump&rsquo;s tariffs and trade-related policies. A large section of economists and financial researchers have warned of a near-term recession too. The U.S. GDP contracted for the first time in three years in first-quarter 2025.&nbsp;The consumer sentiment index reported by the University of Michigan for April came in at 52.2, down sharply from 57.0 in March, marking the lowest since July 2022.&nbsp;The consumer confidence index fell to 86 in April from 92.9 in March. The Personal Consumption Expenditure (PCE) index remained flat in March, however, Personal consumption and personal income grew by 0.7% and 0.5% respectively in March compared to street expectations of 0.5% and 0.4%.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">The Institute of Supply Management (ISM) reported that the manufacturing PMI (purchasing managers&rsquo; index) for April contracted to 48.7% from 49% in March. It is important to note that any reading below 50% indicates contraction in manufacturing activities. The U.S. labor market remains resilient. Nonfarm payrolls increased by 177,000 in April, exceeding analyst expectations, whereas the unemployment rate remained unchanged at 4.2%.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Regardless of market conditions, we, here at Zacks, provide investors with unbiased guidance on how to beat the market.&nbsp;</p><p style="text-align: justify;">As usual, Zacks Research guided investors over the past three months with its time-tested methodologies. Given the prevailing market uncertainty, you may want to look at our feats to prepare better for your next action.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Here are some of our key achievements:</p><p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>ADMA Biologics and Intrepid Potash Following Zacks Rank Upgrade</strong></p><p style="text-align: justify;">Shares of <strong>ADMA Biologics, Inc.</strong> ADMA have gained 48.6% (versus the S&amp;P 500&rsquo;s 3% decrease) since it was upgraded to a Zacks Rank #2 (Buy) on March 4.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Another stock, <strong>Intrepid Potash, Inc. </strong>IPI, which was upgraded to a Zacks Rank #2 on March 6, has returned 28.9% (versus the S&amp;P 500&rsquo;s 2.9% decrease) since then.</p><p style="text-align: justify;"><em>A hypothetical portfolio of Zacks Rank # 1 (Strong Buy) stocks returned -3.48% in January 2025 (through February 3<sup>rd</sup>) vs. -0.60% for the S&amp;P 500 index and -2.75% for the equal-weight version of the index</em></p><p style="text-align: justify;"><em>This portfolio returned +22.3% in 2024, vs. +28% for the S&amp;P 500 index and +19.9% for the equal-weight version of the S&amp;P 500 index. </em></p><p style="text-align: justify;"><em>This hypothetical portfolio returned +20.63% in 2023 vs. +24.83% for the S&amp;P 500 index and +15% for the equal-weight S&amp;P 500 index. </em></p><p style="text-align: justify;"><em>The portfolio of Zacks Rank #1 stocks is an equal-weight portfolio, while the S&amp;P 500 index is a market-cap-weighted index that has been notably distorted by the concentrated performance of mega-cap stocks since late 2022. </em></p><p style="text-align: justify;"><em>The Zacks Model Portfolio - consisting of Zacks Rank #1 stocks &ndash; has outperformed the S&amp;P index by almost 13 percentage points since 1988 (through the end of January 2025, the Zacks # 1 Rank stocks generated an annualized average return of +23.9% since 1988 vs. +11.3% for the S&amp;P 500 index).</em></p><p style="text-align: justify;">You can see&nbsp;the complete list of today&rsquo;s Zacks Rank #1 stocks here &gt;&gt;&gt;</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Check ADMA Biologics&rsquo;s historical EPS and Sales here&gt;&gt;&gt;</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Check Intrepid Potash&rsquo;s historical EPS and Sales here&gt;&gt;&gt;</p><p><img alt="Zacks Investment Research" height="438" src="https://staticx-tuner.zacks.com/images/articles/charts/ef/63619.jpg?v=179273311" width="632" /><br /><span style="width:100%; display: inline-block; font-size: 8pt;">Image Source: Zacks Investment Research</span></p><p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Zacks Recommendation Upgrades Limbach and Dave</strong></p><p style="text-align: justify;">Shares of<strong> Limbach Holdings, Inc. </strong>LMB and<strong> Dave Inc. </strong>DAVE have advanced 40.8% (versus the S&amp;P 500&rsquo;s 2.8% increase) and 21.7% (versus the S&amp;P 500&rsquo;s 1.4% increase) since their Zacks Recommendation was upgraded to Outperform on March 14 and March 13, respectively.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">While the Zacks Rank is our short-term rating system that is most effective over the one- to three-month holding horizon, the Zacks Recommendation aims to predict performance over the next 6 to 12 months. However, just like the Zacks Rank, the foundation for the Zacks Recommendation is trends in earnings estimate revisions.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">The Zacks Recommendation classifies stocks into three groups &mdash; Outperform, Neutral and Underperform. While these recommendations are determined quantitatively, our analysts have the flexibility to override them for the 1100+ stocks they closely follow based on their better judgment of factors such as valuation, industry conditions and management effectiveness than the quantitative model.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">To access our research reports with Zacks Recommendations for the 1100+ stocks we cover, click here&gt;&gt;&gt;</p><p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Zacks Focus List Stocks Constellation Brands, Cheniere Energy Shoot Up</strong></p><p style="text-align: justify;">Shares of <strong>Constellation Brands, Inc. </strong>STZ, which belongs to the Zacks Focus List, have gained 8.2% over the past 12 weeks. The stock was added to the Focus List on April 18, 2017. Another Focus-List holding, <strong>Cheniere Energy, Inc. </strong>LNG, which was added to the portfolio on September 6, 2022, has returned 2.3% over the past 12 weeks. The S&amp;P 500 has decreased 6.2% over this period.</p><p style="text-align: justify;"><em>The Focus List portfolio returned -2.96% in the first quarter of 2025 vs. -4.30% for the S&amp;P 500 index and -0.61% for the equal-weight version of the index. </em></p><p style="text-align: justify;"><em>The 50-stock Zacks Focus List portfolio returned +18.41% in 2024 vs. +25.04% for the S&amp;P 500 index and +13% for the equal-weight S&amp;P 500 index. The portfolio had returned +29.54% in 2023 vs. +26.28% for the S&amp;P 500 index and +13.61% for the equal-weight S&amp;P 500 index. In 2022, the portfolio returned &nbsp;-15.2% vs. the S&amp;P 500 index&rsquo;s -17.96%. </em></p><p style="text-align: justify;"><em>Since 2004, the Focus List portfolio has produced an annualized return of +11.39% (through the end of 2025 Q1). This compares to a +10.03% annualized return for the S&amp;P 500 index and +9.87% for the equal-weight version of the index in the same time period.</em></p><p style="text-align: justify;"><em>The portfolio lags the broader market over the preceding year, but leads over the preceding 3, 5, and 10-year periods.</em></p><p style="text-align: justify;">Unlock all of our powerful research, tools and analysis, including the Focus List, Zacks #1 Rank List, Equity Research Reports, Zacks Earnings ESP Filter, Premium Screener and more, as part of Zacks Premium. Gain full access now &gt;&gt;</p><p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Zacks ECAP Stocks Monster Beverage &amp; Rollins Make Significant Gains</strong></p><p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Monster Beverage Corporation </strong>MNST, a component of our Earnings Certain Admiral Portfolio (ECAP), has jumped 30.1% over the past 12 weeks. <strong>Rollins, Inc. </strong>ROL has followed Monster Beverage with 14.2% returns.</p><p style="text-align: justify;"><em>The Zacks Earnings Certain Admiral Portfolio (ECAP), which consists of 30 concentrated, ultra-defensive, long-term Buy-and-Hold stocks, returned +3.20% in the first quarter of 2025 vs. the S&amp;P 500 index&rsquo;s -4.30% decline (SPY ETF). </em></p><p style="text-align: justify;"><em>For the year 2024, the portfolio returned +16.26% vs. +24.89% for the S&amp;P 500 index (SPY ETF). </em></p><p style="text-align: justify;"><em>In 2023, the portfolio returned +12.17% vs. +26.28% for the S&amp;P 500 index. The portfolio returned -4.7% in 2022 vs. the S&amp;P 500 index&rsquo;s -17.96%.&nbsp; </em></p><p style="text-align: justify;">With little to no turnover and annual rebalance periodicity, ECAP seeks to minimize capital loss by holding shares of companies whose earnings streams exhibit a proven 20+ year track record of surviving recessionary periods with minimal impact on aggregate earnings growth relative to the overall S&amp;P 500.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">The ECAP and many other model portfolios are available as part of Zacks Advisor Tools, a cloud-based solution to access Zacks award-winning stock, mutual fund and ETF research. Click here to schedule a demo.</p><p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Zacks ECDP Stocks Coca-Cola and Quest Diagnostics Outperform Peers</strong></p><p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>The Coca-Cola Company </strong>KO, which is part of our Earnings Certain Dividend Portfolio (ECDP), has returned 13.5% over the past 12 weeks. Another ECDP stock, <strong>Quest Diagnostics Incorporated </strong>DGX, has increased 7.9% over the same time frame. Of course, the inclination of investors toward quality dividend stocks to secure an income stream amid heightened market volatility contributed to this performance.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Check Coca-Cola&rsquo;s dividend history here&gt;&gt;&gt;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Check Quest Diagnostics&#39; dividend history here&gt;&gt;&gt;</p><p style="text-align: justify;">With an extremely low beta and a history of minimum earnings variability over the last 20+ years, this 25-stock portfolio helps to significantly mitigate risk.</p><p style="text-align: justify;"><em>The Zacks Earnings Certain Dividend Portfolio (ECDP) returned +5.74% in 2025 Q1 vs. the S&amp;P 500 index&rsquo;s -2.41% pullback and the Dividend Aristocrats ETF&rsquo;s (NOBL) +3.11% return. </em></p><p style="text-align: justify;"><em>For the full-year 2024, the portfolio returned +6.95% vs. +24.89% for the S&amp;P 500 index and +6.72% for NOBL. </em></p><p style="text-align: justify;"><em>The portfolio returned -0.9% in 2023 vs. +26.28% for the S&amp;P 500 index and +8.11% for NOBL. The portfolio returned -2.3% in 2022 vs. -17.96% for the S&amp;P 500 index and -8.34% for NOBL.</em></p><p style="text-align: justify;">Click here to access this portfolio on Zacks Advisor Tools.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p><p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Zacks Top 10 Stock Primo Brands Delivers Solid Returns</strong></p><p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Primo Brands Corporation </strong>PRMB, from the Zacks Top 10 Stocks for 2025, has jumped 7.4% year to date, compared with the S&amp;P 500 index&rsquo;s 3.3% decrease.</p><p style="text-align: justify;"><em>The Top 10 portfolio returned -11% this year in 2025 Q1 vs. -4.3% for the S&amp;P 500 index and -0.61% for the equal-weight version of the index. </em></p><p style="text-align: justify;"><em>The Top 10 portfolio returned +62.98% in 2024, vs. +25.04% for the S&amp;P 500 index and +13% for the equal-weight version of the index. The portfolio had returned +25.15% in 2023 vs. +26.28% for the S&amp;P 500 index. </em></p><p style="text-align: justify;"><em>Since 2012, the Top 10 portfolio has produced a cumulative return of +1767.4% through the end of 2025 Q1 vs. +437.9% for the S&amp;P 500 index and +348.9% for the equal-weight version of the index. The portfolio has produced an average return of +24.2% in the period 2012 through 2025 Q1 vs. +11.79% for the S&amp;P 500 index and +9.89% for the equal-weight version of the index.</em></p><p><a href="https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2461913/5-momentum-stocks-to-buy-for-may-after-a-mixed-april?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-analyst_blog|investment_ideas-2461913">This article originally published on Zacks Investment Research (zacks.com).</a></p><p><a href="https://www.zacks.com/">Zacks Investment Research</a></p> ]]>
</description>
<link>
<![CDATA[ https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2461913/5-momentum-stocks-to-buy-for-may-after-a-mixed-april?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-analyst_blog|investment_ideas-2461913 ]]>
</link>
<author>
<![CDATA[ Nalak Das ]]>
</author>
<category domain="tradingview:section">
<![CDATA[ Analyst Blog ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NYSE:PM ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NYSE:AEM ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NSDQ:SFM ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NYSE:NWG ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ SONY ]]>
</category>
</item>
<item>
<guid>
<![CDATA[ https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2461914/top-wide-moat-stocks-to-invest-in-for-long-term-growth?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-wide_moat-2461914 ]]>
</guid>
<title>
<![CDATA[ CRA International Shares Barely Move Since Q1 Earnings Beat ]]>
</title>
<pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 12:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
<description>
<![CDATA[ <p style="text-align: justify;"><em>An updated edition of the March 12, 2025, article.</em></p><p style="text-align: justify;">In the business world, the concept of a wide moat refers to companies with strong, durable competitive advantages that protect them from rivals, much like a moat defends a castle. First popularized by Warren Buffett, this strategy emphasizes investing in businesses that can sustain superior profitability over the long term due to their unique positioning, strong brand loyalty, cost advantages, network effects, or regulatory barriers.&nbsp;<br /><br />Among the companies that are recognized for their wide moats, some are <strong>Pfizer Inc. </strong>PFE, <strong>ASML Holding N.V.</strong> ASML, <strong>Lam Research Corporation</strong> LRCX and <strong>The Coca-Cola Company</strong> KO. These companies operate in industries with high barriers to entry, making it difficult for rivals to challenge their positions and ensuring consistent revenue growth.<br /><br />Wide-moat companies typically benefit from several key factors such as brand strength, network effects, high customer switching costs, regulatory protections, and economies of scale. These characteristics make it challenging for new entrants or existing competitors to erode their market share. Companies with wide moats typically benefit from strong pricing power, stable profit margins, and the capacity to reinvest in their businesses, further reinforcing their competitive advantages.<br /><br />The case for investing in wide-moat businesses is rooted in their ability to deliver steady, long-term returns. In contrast to companies operating in fiercely competitive industries, where profits can be highly volatile due to pricing pressures and rivalry, wide-moat businesses tend to show greater resilience during economic downturns and market turbulence. Their solid market positions and robust balance sheets enable them to endure challenges that might seriously impact less competitive firms.<br /><br />Investing in wide-moat companies can be an effective strategy for building long-term wealth, as these businesses typically produce steady cash flows, navigate market volatility with resilience, and deliver value to shareholders through dividends and stock price growth. While no investment is entirely risk-free, companies with strong economic moats provide a level of durability that many investors seek in an ever-changing market. Our Wide Moat Screen makes it easy to identify high-potential stocks at any given time &mdash; just like the ones mentioned above.&nbsp;<br /><br /><em><strong>Ready to uncover more transformative thematic investment ideas? Explore 30 cutting-edge investment themes with Zacks Thematic Screens and discover your next big opportunity.</strong></em></p><h2>4 Wide-Moat Stocks to Buy Now</h2><p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Pfizer</strong>, one of the world&rsquo;s largest pharmaceutical companies, enjoys an economic moat built on its robust patent portfolio, strong research and development capabilities and global scale. The company&#39;s ability to innovate and deliver blockbuster drugs and treatments across oncology, immunology, and rare diseases underscores its scientific leadership.&nbsp;<br /><br />With a highly diversified product lineup and significant resources allocated toward developing new therapies, Pfizer consistently replenishes its pipeline, mitigating risks associated with patent expirations. The complexity of drug discovery, stringent regulatory approval processes, and massive investment required in clinical trials serve as high barriers to entry, protecting Pfizer&rsquo;s dominant position in the global pharmaceutical landscape.<br /><br />After witnessing possibly its worst slowdown in 2023/2024, the company seems to be gradually making a comeback and entering a transition phase. Last year was a strong one in terms of performance and execution by Pfizer. It saw improved performance of its new products, gained and maintained market share of some of its core brands and made rapid pipeline progress in 2024. Pfizer currently carries a Zacks Rank #2 (Buy). You can see <strong>the complete list of today&rsquo;s Zacks #1 Rank (Strong Buy) stocks here</strong>.<br /><br /><strong>ASML Holding</strong>, a vital supplier to the semiconductor industry, possesses one of the strongest technological moats in the world. Its technological leadership in lithography equipment makes it indispensable to the semiconductor industry. The company maintains a near-monopoly on extreme ultraviolet (EUV) lithography, which is essential for producing advanced chips at 3nm and below. Its EUV systems are crucial for leading chipmakers such as T<strong>aiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Company Limited</strong> TSM and <strong>Intel Corporation</strong> INTC, positioning ASML as a key enabler of cutting-edge semiconductor manufacturing. The company&rsquo;s technological superiority ensures high barriers to entry, giving it a competitive moat. &nbsp;<br />&nbsp;<br />ASML Holding&rsquo;s High-NA EUV technology represents the next frontier in chip manufacturing. Designed for sub-2nm nodes, these advanced systems will be critical for the industry&rsquo;s future. While the adoption of High-NA EUV has been slower than expected, the long-term potential remains enormous. As chipmakers ramp up production of smaller, more powerful chips, ASML&rsquo;s High-NA EUV tools will play a pivotal role, driving sustained demand. With EUV technology being essential for advanced semiconductor fabrication, ASML Holding&rsquo;s dominance remains intact, supporting its long-term growth outlook.<br /><br />ASML Holding, a Zacks Rank #2 stock, is well-positioned to capitalize on the artificial intelligence (AI) revolution, which is driving massive demand for advanced semiconductors. With AI workloads requiring cutting-edge GPUs, high-bandwidth memory and AI accelerators, the demand for smaller and more powerful chips is rising. This trend plays directly into ASML&rsquo;s hands, as its EUV and High-NA EUV machines are vital for manufacturing these advanced chips. As cloud providers, data centers and tech giants expand their AI infrastructure, ASML Holding&rsquo;s lithography tools will be in greater demand.<br /><br /><strong>Lam Research</strong> benefits from its leadership position in wafer fabrication equipment, specializing in etch and deposition technologies critical to semiconductor manufacturing. Its deep expertise, long-term customer relationships, and the enormous capital requirements of its industry form a powerful competitive moat. Technology inflections in the semiconductor industry, including 3D device scaling, multiple patterning, process flow, and advanced packaging chip integration, are expected to continue driving sustainable growth and increasing LRCX&rsquo;s served market for its products and services in the deposition, etch and clean businesses.&nbsp;<br /><br />Lam Research has high exposure to the memory segment, which is likely to see tremendous growth in the long run. The semiconductor memory market is being driven by the growing proliferation of AI, Machine Learning, Blockchain, cloud computing, big data, mobile devices and Internet of Things. The huge explosion of data as a result of these advanced technologies, requires to be stored, processed and analyzed to increase efficiency and drive the growth of the business. This has been leading to increased demand for memory chips. In addition, increasing adoption of semiconductor components across various industries, including automotive, consumer electronics, and IT &amp; telecom, remains a tailwind.&nbsp;<br /><br />Lam Research is at the center of the AI revolution, with its advanced fabrication tools playing a crucial role in enabling high-performance computing. Also, with AI applications requiring more efficient and high-speed memory, high bandwidth memory adoption is accelerating. Additionally, Lam is benefiting from increased complexity in semiconductor manufacturing, where etch and deposition technologies are crucial. These factors position this Zacks Rank #2 stock as a key enabler of next-generation AI chips.<br /><br /><strong>Coca-Cola</strong> is a textbook example of a wide-moat company. Its brand recognition, extensive distribution network, and proprietary formulas have enabled it to maintain a leading position for decades. Even with intense competition, especially with <strong>PepsiCo Inc.</strong> PEP, Coca-Cola&rsquo;s brand equity gives it a significant edge. With above 40% of the non-alcoholic beverage market, the company offers more than 4,700 products across 500 brands, spanning traditional sodas, energy drinks and healthier alternatives. This vast portfolio reflects Coca-Cola&rsquo;s adaptability to shifting consumer preferences and its commitment to innovation.<br /><br />Coca-Cola, a Zacks Rank #2 stock, is advancing as a total beverage company with a resilient all-weather strategy that blends marketing, innovation, and revenue growth management. Its revamped marketing model integrates digital, live, and in-store experiences, establishing personalized customer connections. Its marketing approach has driven strong results, including a $40 billion retail sales increase for Trademark Coca-Cola in the past three years.<br /><br />As part of its innovation strategy, Coca-Cola has strategically expanded its portfolio to meet evolving consumer preferences, focusing on healthier options and energy drinks alongside traditional offerings. Its innovation strategy emphasizes bold, high-impact initiatives with clear objectives, balancing short-term buzz with long-term growth. In 2024, innovation played a key role in revenue growth, with improved success rates over the previous year. Coca-Cola is poised to expand its innovation pipeline in 2025.</p><p><a href="https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2461914/top-wide-moat-stocks-to-invest-in-for-long-term-growth?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-wide_moat-2461914">This article originally published on Zacks Investment Research (zacks.com).</a></p><p><a href="https://www.zacks.com/">Zacks Investment Research</a></p> ]]>
</description>
<link>
<![CDATA[ https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2461914/top-wide-moat-stocks-to-invest-in-for-long-term-growth?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-wide_moat-2461914 ]]>
</link>
<author>
<![CDATA[ Anindya Barman ]]>
</author>
<category domain="tradingview:section">
<![CDATA[ Wide Moat ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NSDQ:INTC ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NYSE:KO ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NYSE:PFE ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NSDQ:ASML ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NSDQ:LRCX ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NSDQ:PEP ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NYSE:TSM ]]>
</category>
</item>
<item>
<guid>
<![CDATA[ https://www.zacks.com/commentary/2460901/new-strong-buy-stocks-for-may-5th?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-zacks_1_rank_additions-2460901 ]]>
</guid>
<title>
<![CDATA[ CRA International Shares Barely Move Since Q1 Earnings Beat ]]>
</title>
<pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 12:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
<description>
<![CDATA[ <p style="text-align: justify;">Here are five stocks added to the Zacks Rank #1 (Strong Buy) List today:</p><p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>GeneDx Holdings Corp. </strong>WGS: This genomics-related diagnostic and information services company has seen the Zacks Consensus Estimate for its current year earnings increasing 12.4% over the last 60 days.</p><div class="chart_embed"><h3>GeneDx Holdings Corp. Price and Consensus</h3> <img alt="GeneDx Holdings Corp. Price and Consensus" height="264" src="https://staticx-tuner.zacks.com/images/charts/b9/1746443527.png" title="" width="577" /> <p>GeneDx Holdings Corp. price-consensus-chart | GeneDx Holdings Corp. Quote</p></div><p><strong>NatWest Group plc </strong>NWG: This banking and financial services company has seen the Zacks Consensus Estimate for its current year earnings increasing 5.6% over the last 60 days.</p><div class="chart_embed"><h3>NatWest Group plc Price and Consensus</h3> <img alt="NatWest Group plc Price and Consensus" height="264" src="https://staticx-tuner.zacks.com/images/charts/31/1746443538.png" title="" width="568" /> <p>NatWest Group plc price-consensus-chart | NatWest Group plc Quote</p></div><p><strong>Herbalife Nutrition Ltd. </strong>HLF: This company that offers health and wellness products has seen the Zacks Consensus Estimate for its current year earnings increasing 9.8% over the last 60 days.</p><div class="chart_embed"><h3>Herbalife Ltd Price and Consensus</h3> <img alt="Herbalife Ltd Price and Consensus" height="264" src="https://staticx-tuner.zacks.com/images/charts/7f/1746443547.png" title="" width="562" /> <p>Herbalife Ltd price-consensus-chart | Herbalife Ltd Quote</p></div><p><strong>Cal-Maine Foods, Inc. </strong>CALM: This producer of shell eggs has seen the Zacks Consensus Estimate for its current year earnings increasing 46.2% over the last 60 days.</p><div class="chart_embed"><h3>Cal-Maine Foods, Inc. Price and Consensus</h3> <img alt="Cal-Maine Foods, Inc. Price and Consensus" height="264" src="https://staticx-tuner.zacks.com/images/charts/4a/1746443683.png" title="" width="574" /> <p>Cal-Maine Foods, Inc. price-consensus-chart | Cal-Maine Foods, Inc. Quote</p></div><p><strong>Euroseas Ltd. </strong>ESEA: This ocean-going transportation services company has seen the Zacks Consensus Estimate for its current year earnings increasing 8% over the last 60 days.</p><div class="chart_embed"><h3>Euroseas Ltd. Price and Consensus</h3> <img alt="Euroseas Ltd. Price and Consensus" height="264" src="https://staticx-tuner.zacks.com/images/charts/62/1746443692.png" title="" width="538" /> <p>Euroseas Ltd. price-consensus-chart | Euroseas Ltd. Quote</p></div><p>&nbsp;</p><p>You can see&nbsp;the complete list of today&rsquo;s Zacks #1 Rank (Strong Buy) stocks here.</p><p><a href="https://www.zacks.com/commentary/2460901/new-strong-buy-stocks-for-may-5th?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-zacks_1_rank_additions-2460901">This article originally published on Zacks Investment Research (zacks.com).</a></p><p><a href="https://www.zacks.com/">Zacks Investment Research</a></p> ]]>
</description>
<link>
<![CDATA[ https://www.zacks.com/commentary/2460901/new-strong-buy-stocks-for-may-5th?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-zacks_1_rank_additions-2460901 ]]>
</link>
<author>
<![CDATA[ Zacks Equity Research ]]>
</author>
<category domain="tradingview:section">
<![CDATA[ Zacks #1 Rank Additions ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NSDQ:CALM ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NYSE:HLF ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NSDQ:ESEA ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NYSE:NWG ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ WGS ]]>
</category>
</item>
<item>
<guid>
<![CDATA[ https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2461908/buy-these-top-ranked-5-stocks-to-play-an-earnings-beat?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-analyst_blog|rw-2461908 ]]>
</guid>
<title>
<![CDATA[ CRA International Shares Barely Move Since Q1 Earnings Beat ]]>
</title>
<pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 12:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
<description>
<![CDATA[ <p style="text-align: justify;">It is not surprising that before an earnings season, every investor looks for stocks that can beat market expectations. This is because investors always try to position themselves ahead of time and look to tap stocks that are high-quality in nature.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">In this regard, we ran a screener that yielded stocks <strong>Fox </strong>FOXA, <strong>Newmont </strong>NEM, <strong>Affirm </strong>AFRM, <strong>HealthStream </strong>HSTM) and <strong>Iridium Communications </strong>IRDM as the likely winners on the earnings beat potential.</p><h2><span style="font-size:18px;">Why Is a Positive Earnings Surprise So Important?</span></h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Historically, stocks of companies with solid quarterly earnings (on a nominal basis) tank if they miss or merely meet market expectations. After all, a 20% earnings rise (though apparently looks good) doesn&rsquo;t tell you if earnings growth has been exhibiting a decelerating trend.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Also, seasonal fluctuations come into play sometimes. If a company&rsquo;s Q1 is seasonally weak and Q4 strong, then it is likely to report a sequential earnings decline. In such cases, growth rates are misleading while judging the true health of a company.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">On the other hand, after much brainstorming and analysis of companies&rsquo; financials and initiatives, Wall Street analysts project earnings of companies. They in fact club their insights and a company&rsquo;s guidance when deriving an earnings estimate.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Thus, outperforming that estimate is almost equivalent to beating the company&rsquo;s own expectation as well as the market perception. And if the margin of earnings surprise is big, it typically drives the stock higher right after the release. Thus, more than anything else, an earnings surprise can push a stock higher.</p><h2><span style="font-size:18px;">How to Find Stocks that Can Beat?</span></h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Now, finding stocks that have the potential to beat on the bottom line may be investors&rsquo; dream but not an easy job. One way to do this is to look at the earnings surprise history of the company.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">An impressive track in this regard generally acts as a catalyst in sending a stock higher. It indicates the company&rsquo;s ability to surpass estimates. And investors generally believe that the company will apply the same secret sauce to execute yet another earnings beat in its next release.</p><h2><span style="font-size:18px;">The Winning Strategy</span></h2><p style="text-align: justify;">In order to shortlist stocks that are likely to come up with an earnings surprise, we chose the following as our primary screening parameters.</p><p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Last EPS Surprise greater than or equal to 10%:</strong>&nbsp;Stocks delivering positive surprise in the last quarter tend to surprise again.</p><p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Average EPS Surprise in the last four quarters greater than 20%:&nbsp;</strong>We lifted the bar for outperformance slight higher by setting the average earnings surprise for the last four quarters at 20%.</p><p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Average EPS Surprise in the last two quarters greater than 20%:</strong>&nbsp;This points to a more consistent surprise history and makes the case for another surprise even stronger.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">In addition, we place a few other criteria that push up the chance of a positive surprise.</p><p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Zacks Rank less than or equal to 2:</strong>&nbsp;Only companies with a Zacks Rank #1 (Strong Buy) or 2 (Buy) rating can get through.</p><p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Earnings ESP</strong><strong>&nbsp;greater than zero:&nbsp;</strong>A stock needs to have both a positive Earnings ESP and a Zacks Rank of #1, 2 or 3 for an earnings beat to happen, as per our proven model.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">In order to zero in on those that have long-term growth potential and high trading liquidity we have added the following parameters too:</p><p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Next 3&ndash;5 Years Estimated EPS Growth (Per Year) greater than 10%:</strong>&nbsp;Solid expected earnings growth exhibits the stock&rsquo;s long-term growth prospects.</p><p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Average 20-day Volume greater than 100,000:&nbsp;</strong>High trading volume implies that the stocks have adequate liquidity.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">A handful of criteria has narrowed down the universe from over 7,700 stocks to only five.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Here are all five stocks:</p><p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Fox</strong><strong>:</strong>The Zacks Rank #1 company is a news, sports and entertainment content provider. You can see&nbsp;<strong>the complete list of today&rsquo;s Zacks #1 Rank stocks here</strong>.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">The average earnings surprise of FOXA for the past four quarters is 24.20%.</p><p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Newmont</strong>: The Zacks Rank #2 company is one of the world&#39;s largest producers of gold with several active mines in Nevada, Peru, Australia and Ghana. The NEM stock has a Zacks Rank #2.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">The average earnings surprise of NEM for the past four quarters is 32.41%.</p><p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Affirm</strong>: The financial technology company specializing in payment solutions that provide consumers with flexible, transparent installment loans &mdash; both interest-free and interest-bearing &mdash; at the point of sale. By partnering with a diverse range of merchants, Affirm enables customers to pay for purchases over time. The stock has a Zacks Rank #1.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">The average earnings surprise of AFRM for the past four quarters is 84.09%.</p><p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>HealthStream</strong><strong>:</strong>The Zacks Rank #1 company HealthStream&#39;s suite of solutions is contracted by healthcare employees in the United States for workforce development, training &amp; learning management, talent management, credentialing, privileging, provider enrollment, performance assessment and managing simulation-based education programs.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">The average earnings surprise of HSTM for the past four quarters is 42.02%.</p><p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Iridium Communications</strong>: The company is a satellite communications company that offers dedicated commercial global voice and data communications services to both businesses and governments in the United States as well as globally.The stock has a Zacks Rank #2.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">The average earnings surprise of IRDM for the past four quarters is 40.90%.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">You can get the rest of the stocks on this list by signing up now for your 2-week free trial to the Research Wizard and start using this screen in your own trading. Further, you can also create your own strategies and test them first before taking the investment plunge.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">The Research Wizard is a great place to begin. It&#39;s easy to use. Everything is in plain language. And it&#39;s very intuitive. Start your Research Wizard trial today. And the next time you read an economic report, open up the Research Wizard, plug your finds in, and see what gems come out.</p><p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Click here to sign up for a free trial to the Research Wizard today</strong>.</p><p style="text-align: justify;"><em>Disclosure: Officers, directors and/or employees of Zacks Investment Research may own or have sold short securities and/or hold long and/or short positions in options that are mentioned in this material. An affiliated investment advisory firm may own or have sold short securities and/or hold long and/or short positions in options that are mentioned in this material.</em></p><p style="text-align: justify;"><em>Disclosure: Performance information for Zacks&rsquo; portfolios and strategies are available at:&nbsp;</em><em><strong>http://www.zacks.com/performance</strong></em>.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">&nbsp;</p><p style="text-align: justify;"><br />&nbsp;</p><p><a href="https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2461908/buy-these-top-ranked-5-stocks-to-play-an-earnings-beat?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-analyst_blog|rw-2461908">This article originally published on Zacks Investment Research (zacks.com).</a></p><p><a href="https://www.zacks.com/">Zacks Investment Research</a></p> ]]>
</description>
<link>
<![CDATA[ https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2461908/buy-these-top-ranked-5-stocks-to-play-an-earnings-beat?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-analyst_blog|rw-2461908 ]]>
</link>
<author>
<![CDATA[ Sanghamitra Saha ]]>
</author>
<category domain="tradingview:section">
<![CDATA[ Analyst Blog ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NYSE:NEM ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NSDQ:IRDM ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NSDQ:FOXA ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NSDQ:HSTM ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ AFRM ]]>
</category>
</item>
<item>
<guid>
<![CDATA[ https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2461847/flex-gearing-up-to-report-q4-earnings-here-s-what-to-expect?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-analyst_blog|earnings_preview-2461847 ]]>
</guid>
<title>
<![CDATA[ CRA International Shares Barely Move Since Q1 Earnings Beat ]]>
</title>
<pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 12:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
<description>
<![CDATA[ <p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Flex Ltd.</strong> FLEX is scheduled to report fourth-quarter fiscal 2025 results on May 7, before the market opens.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">The Zacks Consensus Estimate for fiscal fourth-quarter revenues is pegged at $6.23 billion, which indicates a rise of around 1% from the year-ago quarter&rsquo;s reported figure. The consensus mark for earnings is pegged at 69 cents per share, up 21.1% year over year.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">For the fourth quarter of fiscal 2025, Flex expects revenues to be between $6 billion and $6.4 billion. Management expects adjusted earnings of 65-73 cents per share, excluding 5 cents for net restructuring charges, 8 cents for stock-based compensation expense and 4 cents for net intangible amortization.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">The company&rsquo;s earnings beat the Zacks Consensus Estimate in each of the last four quarters. It delivered a trailing four-quarter earnings surprise of 15.7%, on average. (Find the latest EPS estimates and surprises on Zacks Earnings Calendar.)</p><h2>Factors to Note for FLEX&rsquo;s Q4 Results</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">For the Reliability Solutions business, management forecasts sales to remain flat to down mid-single digits in the fourth quarter owing to softness in the automotive vertical amid persistent macroeconomic challenges. Weaker core industrial demand is likely to have acted as an additional headwind. While demand for medical devices is expected to have remained stable, the timing of recovery in medical equipment sales remains uncertain.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Agility Solutions&rsquo; revenues are also anticipated to be flat to up in mid-single digits, supported by steady growth in cloud markets, which is likely to have offset muted spending in communications and enterprise segments. The Lifestyle business is expected to have faced a seasonally soft quarter. Consumer Devices is anticipated to have experienced typical post-holiday seasonality, with a continued focus on strong cost management.</p><div class="chart_embed"><h3>Flex Ltd. Price and EPS Surprise</h3> <img alt="Flex Ltd. Price and EPS Surprise" height="262" src="https://staticx-tuner.zacks.com/images/charts/8b/1746446830.png" title="" width="533" /> <p>Flex Ltd. price-eps-surprise | Flex Ltd. Quote</p></div><p>However, Flex&rsquo;s performance is likely to have been cushioned by steady momentum in data center, medical devices and consumer-related markets. The data center business stands to benefit from artificial intelligence (AI)-powered cloud transformation.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">FLEX remains focused on advancing cloud, power and automotive businesses through strategic programs, and the initiatives are likely to have positively impacted Flex&rsquo;s performance in the fiscal fourth quarter. These factors favorably position Flex for the AI-powered technology shift prevalent in the industry, from the grid to chip and from the cloud to the edge.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Margin improvement is likely to have been driven by strong execution, a favorable product mix and low-cost manufacturing.</p><h2>Recent Key Highlights</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">On April 29, 2025, Flex&#39;s JetCool launched the SmartSense Coolant Distribution Unit (CDU), an in-rack, liquid-to-liquid system that cools up to 300kW per rack or multiple high-density racks, offering modular, cost-effective solutions for data centers and colocation providers.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">On April 28, 2025, Flex expanded production of data center power products like Databar, Power Distribution Units (PDUs) and Remote Power Panels (RPPs) at its 134,000 sq. ft. Columbia, SC, facility to meet rising AI-driven demand and cut lead times. This complements its new 400,000 sq. ft. Dallas facility, boosting U.S. capacity for critical power products.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">On March 20, 2025, Flex announced the launch of a New Product Introduction (NPI) center near Boston, dedicated to serving healthcare customers. This state-of-the-art facility is designed to support the entire product development journey from prototype to preclinical builds, design verification and production transfer, enabling faster, more scalable and lower-risk market entry for medical products.</p><h2>What Our Model Says About Flex</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Our proven model does not predict an earnings beat for FLEX this time around. The combination of a positive Earnings ESP and a Zacks Rank #1 (Strong Buy), 2 (Buy) or 3 (Hold) increases the odds of an earnings beat. That is not the case here.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Flex has an <strong>Earnings ESP</strong> of 0.00% and a Zacks Rank #3. You can uncover the best stocks to buy or sell before they&rsquo;re reported with our <strong>Earnings ESP Filter.</strong></p><h2>Stocks to Consider</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Here are some stocks you may consider, as our model shows that these have the right combination of elements to beat on earnings this season.</p><p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Axon Enterprise</strong> AXON is set to report first-quarter 2025 earnings on May 7, after market close. It has an Earnings ESP of +9.28% and a Zacks Rank of 2 at present. You can see <strong>the complete list of today&rsquo;s Zacks #1 Rank stocks here</strong>.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">The Zacks Consensus Estimate for AXON&rsquo;s earnings is pegged at $1.27 per share, indicating year-over-year growth of 10.4%. The consensus estimate for its sales is pegged at $589.1 million, indicating year-over-year growth of 27.9%.</p><p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Expeditors International of Washington</strong> EXPD has an Earnings ESP of +3.76% and a Zacks Rank #3 at present. EXPD is scheduled to report first-quarter 2025 earnings on May 6.&nbsp;</p><p style="text-align: justify;">The Zacks Consensus Estimate for first-quarter 2025 revenues and earnings are pegged at $2.43 billion and $1.30 per share, respectively. EXPD&rsquo;s earnings beat the Zacks Consensus Estimate in each of the preceding four quarters, with the average surprise being 11.6%.</p><p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>CurtissWright </strong>CW is set to report its first-quarter results on May 7, after market close. It has an Earnings ESP of +0.12% and a Zacks Rank of 3 at present.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">The Zacks Consensus Estimate for CW&rsquo;s earnings is pegged at $2.39 per share, indicating year-over-year growth of 20.1%. The consensus estimate for its sales is pegged at $767.2 million, indicating year-over-year growth of 7.6%.</p><p><a href="https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2461847/flex-gearing-up-to-report-q4-earnings-here-s-what-to-expect?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-analyst_blog|earnings_preview-2461847">This article originally published on Zacks Investment Research (zacks.com).</a></p><p><a href="https://www.zacks.com/">Zacks Investment Research</a></p> ]]>
</description>
<link>
<![CDATA[ https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2461847/flex-gearing-up-to-report-q4-earnings-here-s-what-to-expect?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-analyst_blog|earnings_preview-2461847 ]]>
</link>
<author>
<![CDATA[ Zacks Equity Research ]]>
</author>
<category domain="tradingview:section">
<![CDATA[ Analyst Blog ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NYSE:EXPD ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NSDQ:SONO ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NSDQ:CDW ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ GXO ]]>
</category>
</item>
<item>
<guid>
<![CDATA[ https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2461730/pfizer-stock-up-5-following-q1-results-time-to-buy-sell-or-hold?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-analyst_blog|most_popular_stocks-2461730 ]]>
</guid>
<title>
<![CDATA[ CRA International Shares Barely Move Since Q1 Earnings Beat ]]>
</title>
<pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 12:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
<description>
<![CDATA[ <p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Pfizer</strong>&#39;s PFE stock has risen 5% since it reported first-quarter results on April 29. While the company beat estimates for earnings, it missed the same for sales. Earnings of 92 cents per share rose 12% year over year due to higher gross margins and cost control. However, revenues declined 6% on an operational basis as higher sales of the Vyndaqel family, Padcev, Lorbrena, Nurtec and Comirnaty vaccine were offset by lower sales of some key products like Paxlovid, Prevnar, Xeljanz, Eliquis and Ibrance. Higher manufacturer discounts resulting from the Medicare Part D redesign under the Inflation Reduction Act (IRA), which took effect in the first quarter, hurt U.S. revenues by $650 million.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">However, despite the sales miss, Pfizer maintained its earnings and sales outlook for the year. Pfizer projects total revenues between $61.0 billion and $64.0 billion, while earnings are expected in the range of $2.80 to $3.00 per share. Pfizer&rsquo;s chief financial officer, David Denton, said that the company is trending toward the upper end of the adjusted EPS guidance range.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">The guidance does not include the potential impact of future tariffs and trade policy changes. However, the company expects an impact of approximately $150 million in 2025 from tariffs already in place. Pfizer&rsquo;s CEO, Albert Bourla, said on the call that 25% tariffs on pharma imports are unlikely. However, if the import tariffs are implemented in the future, Pfizer said it has detailed contingency plans to manage the impact. The CEO said they have enough room at their manufacturing sites in the United States, particularly for injectables, if they have to transfer production to domestic facilities. Pfizer&rsquo;s positive comments about the impact of a potential tariff being manageable led the stock to increase despite a softer quarterly performance.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Nonetheless, a single quarter&rsquo;s results are not so important for long-term investors, and the focus should rather be on the company&rsquo;s strong fundamentals. Let&rsquo;s understand the company&rsquo;s strengths and weaknesses to better analyze how to play PFE&rsquo;s stock in the post-earnings scenario.</p><h2>Sales of PFE&rsquo;s COVID Products Declining</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">With the end of the pandemic, sales of Pfizer&rsquo;s COVID products, Comirnaty and Paxlovid, came down to around $11 billion in 2024 from $56.7 billion in 2022. In 2025, Pfizer&rsquo;s revenues from Paxlovid and Comirnaty are expected to be similar to 2024, excluding the $1.2 billion in one-time benefits from Paxlovid. COVID revenues may decline further in future years, depending on infection rates.</p><h2>PFE&rsquo;s New Drugs &amp; Seagen Acquisition Drive the Top Line</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Though COVID revenues are declining, Pfizer&rsquo;s non-COVID operational revenues improved in 2024, driven by its key in-line products like Vyndaqel, Padcev and Eliquis, new launches and newly acquired products like Nurtec and those from Seagen (December 2023. The positive trend continued in the first quarter of 2025. Continued growth of Pfizer&rsquo;s diversified portfolio of drugs, particularly oncology, should support top-line growth in 2025.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Pfizer&rsquo;s new products/late-stage pipeline candidates and newly acquired products, including those acquired from Seagen, position it strongly for operational growth in 2025 and beyond.</p><h2>PFE Enjoys a Strong Position in Oncology</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Pfizer is one of the largest and most successful drugmakers in oncology. The addition of Seagen strengthened its position in oncology.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Its oncology revenues grew 7% on an operational basis in the first quarter of 2025, driven by drugs like Xtandi, Lorbrena, the Braftovi-Mektovi combination and Padcev. Pfizer has ventured into the oncology biosimilars space and markets six biosimilars for cancer. Pfizer also advanced its oncology clinical pipeline with several candidates entering late-stage development, like sasanlimab, vepdegestrant and sigvotatug vedotin.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Pfizer is also working on expanding the labels of approved products (oncology as well as non-oncology) like Padcev, Adcetris, Litfulo, Nurtec, Velsipity and Elrexfio, among others.</p><h2>Pfizer&rsquo;s Other Headwinds in 2025</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Though Pfizer expects a moderate negative impact on revenues from the loss of exclusivity in 2025, the impact is expected to be significant in the 2026-2030 period as several of its key products, including Eliquis, Vyndaqel, Ibrance, Xeljanz and Xtandi, will face patent expirations.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Pfizer expects an unfavorable impact of approximately $1 billion from the Medicare Part D redesign under the IRA, which takes effect in 2025. Higher-priced drugs, including Vyndaqel, Ibrance, Xtandi and Xeljanz, are expected to be most affected by the IRA.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">The company has also faced its share of setbacks. Earlier this month, Pfizer said it is discontinuing the development of its GLP-1R agonist, danuglipron, which was developed as a weight loss pill. Pfizer took the decision after one of the participants in the dose-optimization studies developed a potentially&nbsp;drug-induced liver injury, which resolved after danuglipron was discontinued. <strong>Novo Nordisk</strong> NVO and <strong>Lilly</strong> LLY currently dominate the obesity market with their GLP-1 injections.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Moreover, stocks of vaccine makers like Pfizer have been under pressure with the appointment of Robert F. Kennedy Jr., a well-known vaccine skeptic, as the Secretary of Health and Human Services (HHS).</p><h2>PFE&rsquo;s Stock Performance, Rising Estimates &amp; Attractive Valuation</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Pfizer&rsquo;s stock has declined 7.3% so far this year against an increase of 2.4% for the industry.</p><h2 style="text-align: center;">PFE Stock Underperforms Industry</h2><p style="text-align: center;"><img alt="Zacks Investment Research" src="https://staticx-tuner.zacks.com/images/articles/charts/b5/102733.jpg?v=270020922" style="height: 315px; width: 600px;" /><br /><span style="width:100%; display: inline-block; font-size: 8pt;">Image Source: Zacks Investment Research</span></p><p style="text-align: justify;">From a valuation standpoint, Pfizer appears attractive relative to the industry and is trading below its 5-year mean. Going by the price/earnings ratio, the company&rsquo;s shares currently trade at 7.86 forward earnings, lower than 15.70 for the industry and the stock&rsquo;s 5-year mean of 10.99. The stock is also much cheaper than other large drugmakers like AbbVie, Novo Nordisk, Lilly, AstraZeneca, J&amp;J and others.</p><h2 style="text-align: center;">PFE Stock Valuation</h2><p style="text-align: center;"><img alt="Zacks Investment Research" src="https://staticx-tuner.zacks.com/images/articles/charts/ac/102734.jpg?v=1083830983" style="height: 310px; width: 600px;" /><br /><span style="width:100%; display: inline-block; font-size: 8pt;">Image Source: Zacks Investment Research</span></p><p style="text-align: justify;">The Zacks Consensus Estimate for 2025 earnings has risen from $2.99 per share to $3.07 per share, while that for 2026 has gone up from $3.02 to $3.10 per share over the past seven days.</p><h2 style="text-align: center;">PFE Estimate Movement</h2><p style="text-align: center;"><img alt="Zacks Investment Research" src="https://staticx-tuner.zacks.com/images/articles/charts/4c/102732.jpg?v=657958928" style="height: 310px; width: 600px;" /><br /><span style="width:100%; display: inline-block; font-size: 8pt;">Image Source: Zacks Investment Research</span></p><h2>Stay Invested in PFE Stock</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Pfizer faces its share of challenges, the key being declining sales of its COVID-19 products, U.S. Medicare Part D headwinds, the upcoming loss of exclusivity (LOE) cliff, uncertainties around tariffs and a volatile macro environment. However, with COVID-related uncertainties diminishing, its revenue volatility is declining. Pfizer&rsquo;s key drugs like Vyndaqel, Padcev and Eliquis and new and newly acquired products should continue to drive top-line growth.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Pfizer expects cost cuts and internal restructuring to deliver savings of $7.7 billion by the end of 2027. Pfizer&rsquo;s significant cost-reduction and efforts to improve R&amp;D productivity measures should drive profit growth. Though Pfizer does not expect strong top-line growth over the next three years due to the LOEs, it expects EPS growth.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Though scrapping danuglipron was a big setback, Pfizer is committed to building its cardiometabolic pipeline, including obesity, by advancing internal programs such as its GIPR antagonist and pursuing external opportunities that could include partnerships or acquisitions.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Pfizer returned $2.4 billion directly to shareholders through dividends in the first quarter of 2025. Its dividend yield stands at around 7.1%, which is impressive.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Investors may consider buying this Zacks Rank #2 (Buy) stock at the present cheap valuation for long-term gains, keeping track of the company&rsquo;s newer growth prospects. It will be a great pick for value investors, considering its cheap valuation, as well as for income investors due to its sky-high dividend yield.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">You can see the complete list of today&rsquo;s Zacks #1 Rank (Strong Buy) stocks here.</p><p><a href="https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2461730/pfizer-stock-up-5-following-q1-results-time-to-buy-sell-or-hold?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-analyst_blog|most_popular_stocks-2461730">This article originally published on Zacks Investment Research (zacks.com).</a></p><p><a href="https://www.zacks.com/">Zacks Investment Research</a></p> ]]>
</description>
<link>
<![CDATA[ https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2461730/pfizer-stock-up-5-following-q1-results-time-to-buy-sell-or-hold?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-analyst_blog|most_popular_stocks-2461730 ]]>
</link>
<author>
<![CDATA[ Kinjel Shah ]]>
</author>
<category domain="tradingview:section">
<![CDATA[ Analyst Blog ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NYSE:PFE ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NYSE:NVO ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NYSE:LLY ]]>
</category>
</item>
<item>
<guid>
<![CDATA[ https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2461841/microsoft-meta-platforms-amazon-and-apple-are-part-of-zacks-earnings-preview?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-press_releases-2461841 ]]>
</guid>
<title>
<![CDATA[ CRA International Shares Barely Move Since Q1 Earnings Beat ]]>
</title>
<pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 12:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
<description>
<![CDATA[ <h2 style="text-align: justify;">For Immediate Release</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Chicago, IL &ndash; May 5, 2025&ndash; Today, Zacks Investment Ideas feature highlights Quanta Services PWR, BWX Technologies, Inc. BWXT and Constellation Energy CEG.</p><h2 style="text-align: justify;"><em>Top Nuclear Energy Stocks to Buy Before Earnings for AI-Powered Growth</em></h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Wall Street pushed the Nasdaq above its 50-day moving average on Thursday as big tech results poured in. The bulls continue to buy stocks as earnings results and guidance highlight the resilience and financial firepower of technology and other critical areas of the economy.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Meta and Microsoft flexed their muscles on Wednesday, following strong reports from Alphabet and Taiwan Semiconductor over the last several weeks. The recent performances are pushing the broader earnings outlook higher, helping Wall Street feel confident that the economy is not headed over a cliff.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">As long as the tariff war continues to cool off and Trump and his team keep talking about progress with big trading partners and China (even if China denies it), the bulls might be ready to press higher.</p><h2 style="text-align: justify;">Why It&#39;s Time to Buy Back into Beaten-Down Nuclear Energy Stocks</h2><p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Quanta Services</strong>stock soared 10% on Thursday after an impressive beat-and-raise first quarter release.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Quanta is an infrastructure solutions standout benefiting from the energy transition, the artificial intelligence power boom, and the overall expansion of the U.S. energy ecosystem. Quanta stock is up 190% in the past three years and is now racing back up to its all-time highs.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">On top of that, Alphabet, Microsoft, Meta, and the other AI hyperscalers are pouring billions of dollars on AI-related capital spending projects despite near-term economic uncertainty.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Large data centers can consume nearly as much electricity as a midsize city, and generative AI platforms like ChatGPT use at least 10 times the energy of a typical Google search. This AI-driven energy boom is arriving just as the U.S. and major tech companies aim to reduce their reliance on fossil fuels.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Given this backdrop, big tech is all-in on nuclear energy to help add to U.S. energy capacity. The U.S. government has launched various initiatives to support the nuclear energy revival, aiming to triple capacity by 2050. The Office of Nuclear Energy, part of the U.S. Department of Energy, posted on X in April that the &quot;U.S. nuclear renaissance starts now.&quot;</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Despite the nuclear energy push, the U.S. and big tech will have to kick things into overdrive soon to start bringing new nuclear energy capacity online in the foreseeable future.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">With this in mind, today&#39;s Full Court Finance at Zacks dives into two great nuclear energy stocks&mdash;BWX Technologies and Constellation Energy&mdash;to consider buying before their earnings reports for near-term upside and long-term artificial intelligence-boosted growth.</p><h2 style="text-align: justify;">Buy this Under-the-Radar Nuclear Energy Stock Before Earnings?</h2><p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>BWX Technologies, Inc. </strong>is a pure-play nuclear technology firm ready to report its first quarter financial results on Monday, May 5.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">BWXT stock trades 17% below its record highs from November. The nuclear energy stock retook its 200-day moving average on Thursday after finding support at a critical technical range in early April. Investors should also know that BWX Technologies climbed 400% in the past 15 years and more than tripled the S&amp;P 500 over the past three years.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">On the valuation front, the nuclear energy tech firm trades at a 65% discount to its highs and in line with its 10-year median, with a 2.5 price/earnings-to-growth (PEG) ratio.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">BWX Technologies is a nuclear power-focused manufacturing and engineering standout, operating across energy, defense, space exploration, and beyond. BWXT is expanding its commercial power segment and gaining ground at the cutting edge of small modular and micro nuclear reactors. BWXT is working alongside the U.S. government and other cutting-edge nuclear energy companies.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">BWX Technologies has topped our earnings estimates for eight quarters in a row. Plus, the nuclear tech company is expected to grow its revenue by roughly 11% in 2025 and 2026, marking its best back-to-back years as a public company. BWXT is projected to expand its adjusted earnings by 5% in 2025 and 13% in FY26.</p><h2 style="text-align: justify;">Is this Nuclear Stock the Best Long-Term Buy in the Entire Energy Sector?</h2><p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Constellation Energy </strong>will report its quarterly results before the market opens on Tuesday, May 6. Constellation was already the largest U.S. nuclear power company before it announced a $26.6 billion deal to acquire natural gas and geothermal titan Calpine at the start of 2025.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">CEG&#39; acquisition creates the nation&#39;s largest clean energy firm and expands its footprint into power-hungry, tech-heavy Texas and California. Adding natural gas is critical since it will grow in the coming decades as the U.S. and big tech race to expand energy capacity&mdash;natural gas remains by far the largest source of U.S. electricity generation (43% vs. nuclear&#39;s 20%).</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Constellation raised its dividend by 25% in 2024 and expects to increase its dividend per share by another 10% in 2025. Constellation projects &quot;visible, double-digit long-term base EPS growth backed by the Nuclear Production Tax Credit.&quot; The energy powerhouse is expected to grow its adjusted earnings by 10% in 2025 and 20% in 2026. Plus, its earnings estimates have jumped heading into its report.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Constellation has soared 315% during the past three years, including its 7% pop on Thursday that helped it retake its 200-day moving average. Despite this run, CEG trades 30% below its highs. A strong report could see it storm back up to its September breakout levels after it landed a 20-year power purchase agreement with Microsoft, and then march toward its peaks.</p><p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Why Haven&#39;t You Looked at Zacks&#39; Top Stocks?</strong></p><p style="text-align: justify;">Since 2000, our top stock-picking strategies have blown away the S&amp;P&#39;s +7.7% average gain per year. Amazingly, they soared with average gains of <strong>+48.4%, +50.2%</strong> and <strong>+56.7%</strong> per year.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Today you can access their live picks without cost or obligation.</p><p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>See Stocks Free &gt;&gt;</strong></p><p style="text-align: justify;">Media Contact</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Zacks Investment Research</p><p style="text-align: justify;">800-767-3771 ext. 9339</p><p style="text-align: justify;">support@zacks.com</p><p style="text-align: justify;">https://www.zacks.com</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Past performance is no guarantee of future results. Inherent in any investment is the potential for loss. This material is being provided for informational purposes only and nothing herein constitutes investment, legal, accounting or tax advice, or a recommendation to buy, sell or hold a security. No recommendation or advice is being given as to whether any investment is suitable for a particular investor. It should not be assumed&nbsp;that any investments in securities, companies, sectors or markets identified and described were or will be profitable. All information is current as of the date of herein and&nbsp;is subject to change without notice. Any views or opinions expressed may not reflect those of the firm as a whole. Zacks Investment Research does not engage in investment banking, market making or asset management activities of any securities. These returns are from hypothetical portfolios consisting of stocks with Zacks Rank = 1 that were rebalanced monthly with zero transaction costs. These are not the returns of actual portfolios of stocks. The S&amp;P 500 is an unmanaged index. Visit https://www.zacks.com/performancefor information about the performance numbers displayed in this press release.</p><p><a href="https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2461841/microsoft-meta-platforms-amazon-and-apple-are-part-of-zacks-earnings-preview?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-press_releases-2461841">This article originally published on Zacks Investment Research (zacks.com).</a></p><p><a href="https://www.zacks.com/">Zacks Investment Research</a></p> ]]>
</description>
<link>
<![CDATA[ https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2461841/microsoft-meta-platforms-amazon-and-apple-are-part-of-zacks-earnings-preview?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-press_releases-2461841 ]]>
</link>
<author>
<![CDATA[ Zacks Equity Research ]]>
</author>
<category domain="tradingview:section">
<![CDATA[ Press Releases ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ CEG ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NYSE:PWR ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NYSE:BWXT ]]>
</category>
</item>
<item>
<guid>
<![CDATA[ https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2461844/buy-sell-or-hold-bgc-group-stock-key-insights-ahead-of-q1-earnings?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-analyst_blog|most_popular_stocks-2461844 ]]>
</guid>
<title>
<![CDATA[ CRA International Shares Barely Move Since Q1 Earnings Beat ]]>
</title>
<pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 12:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
<description>
<![CDATA[ <p>As a global financial services firm specializing in brokerage and financial technology, <strong>BGC Group Inc.</strong> BGC is at the forefront of digital transformation in capital markets. The company is slated to announce first-quarter 2025 results on Wednesday before the opening bell.<br /><br />BGC&rsquo;s fourth-quarter 2024 performance was decent. Results benefited from the strong brokerage revenue growth in the Energy, Commodities and Shipping (ECS), Rates and Foreign Exchange businesses. Further, Data, Network and Post-trade revenues witnessed a rise.&nbsp;<br />&nbsp;<br />BGC Group has a decent earnings surprise history. The company&rsquo;s earnings outpaced the Zacks Consensus Estimate in one of the trailing four quarters and met thrice, with the average beat being 3.26%.</p><p style="text-align: center;"><strong>Earnings Surprise</strong><br />&nbsp;</p><p><img alt="Zacks Investment Research" src="https://staticx-tuner.zacks.com/images/articles/charts/8a/102741.jpg?v=336045071" /><br /><span style="width:100%; display: inline-block; font-size: 8pt;">Image Source: Zacks Investment Research</span></p><p>The Zacks Consensus Estimate for sales of $635.1 million suggests 9.8% growth on a year-over-year basis. In the past week, the consensus estimate for earnings has remained unchanged at 29 cents. This indicates a rise of 16%. (Find the latest EPS estimates and surprises on Zacks Earnings Calendar.)</p><p style="text-align: center;"><strong>BGC&rsquo;s Earnings Estimates</strong><br />&nbsp;</p><p><img alt="Zacks Investment Research" src="https://staticx-tuner.zacks.com/images/articles/charts/f5/102740.jpg?v=1661136130" /><br /><span style="width:100%; display: inline-block; font-size: 8pt;">Image Source: Zacks Investment Research</span></p><p>Is it the right time to add BGC stock to your portfolio? Let&rsquo;s analyze the factors that are likely to have influenced its performance this time.</p><h2>Factors to Note &amp; Estimates for BGC Group&rsquo;s Q1 Results</h2><p><strong>Revenues:</strong> During the first quarter, client activity was robust, driven by heightened volatility amid tariff policy concerns. Thus, BGC Group&rsquo;s total brokerage revenues are likely to have witnessed solid growth similar to that of its peers, <strong>Robinhood Markets</strong> HOOD and <strong>Interactive Brokers</strong> IBKR.<br /><br />Robinhood, which announced first-quarter results on April 30, recorded a 77.2% year-over-year surge in transaction-based revenues. This was largely driven by an improvement in options, equities and cryptocurrencies revenues. Likewise, Interactive Brokers, which released quarterly numbers on April 15, witnessed a 35.6% jump in commissions.&nbsp;<br /><br />The Zacks Consensus Estimate for BGC&rsquo;s total brokerage revenues is pegged at $576.3 million, indicating a 9.1% rise from the prior-year quarter. This is likely to have been driven by higher rates, FX and ECS brokerage revenues.<br /><br />The consensus estimate for rates is $182.3 million, suggesting 4.1% growth. Further, the Zacks Consensus Estimate for foreign exchange and ECS revenues is pegged at $103.3 million and $153.5 million, respectively. Foreign exchange revenues are projected to grow 23%, while ECS revenues are estimated to jump 29.6% year over year.&nbsp;<br /><br />Additionally, the consensus estimate for credit and equities revenues is pinned at $74.9 million and $62.2 million, respectively. Credit revenues are projected to fall 14.5%, while equities revenues are estimated to decline 1.1% year over year.&nbsp;<br /><br />The Zacks Consensus Estimate for Data, Network and Post-trade is pegged at $33.9 million, suggesting a 9.7% increase from the prior-year quarter.<br /><br />BGC Group expects revenues between $610 million and $660 million, up from $578.6 million recorded in the prior-year quarter.<br /><br /><strong>Expenses:</strong> Total operating expenses are likely to have remained elevated as the company invests in key areas to enhance platform capabilities, drive product innovation and improve customer support. Also, the company&rsquo;s inorganic expansion efforts are likely to have resulted in some restructuring/merger-related charges during the quarter.</p><h2>What Our Model Unveils for BGC Group</h2><p>Our quantitative model does not conclusively predict an earnings beat for BGC Group this time. The combination of a positive Earnings ESP and a Zacks Rank #1 (Strong Buy), 2 (Buy) or 3 (Hold) increases the odds of an earnings beat. That is not the case here, as you can see below.<br /><br /><strong>Earnings ESP:</strong> BGC Group has an Earnings ESP of 0.00%. You can uncover the best stocks to buy or sell before they&rsquo;re reported with our Earnings ESP Filter.<br /><br /><strong>Zacks Rank:</strong> BGC sports a Zacks Rank #1 at present. You can see <strong>the complete list of today&rsquo;s Zacks #1 Rank stocks here</strong>.</p><h2>BGC Stock&rsquo;s Price Performance &amp; Valuation</h2><p>BGC Group shares have had a decent run on the bourses since the beginning of the year. The stock rose 3.3% so far this year compared with the industry&rsquo;s rally of 1.4%. Further, it fared better than Interactive Brokers&rsquo; rise of 2.8%, while Robinhood surged 30.4% during the same period.</p><p style="text-align: center;"><strong>BGC YTD Price Performance</strong><br />&nbsp;</p><p><img alt="Zacks Investment Research" src="https://staticx-tuner.zacks.com/images/articles/charts/cc/102738.jpg?v=1779014885" /><br /><span style="width:100%; display: inline-block; font-size: 8pt;">Image Source: Zacks Investment Research</span></p><p>Now, let&rsquo;s look at the value BGC Group offers investors at current levels.<br /><br />At present, BGC is trading at 15.05X 12-month trailing price/tangible book (P/TB), below its three-year median of 18.90X. Meanwhile, the industry&rsquo;s P/TB TTM is 2.78X. Hence, the stock looks expensive compared with the industry average.</p><p style="text-align: center;"><strong>BGC Group P/TB TTM</strong><br />&nbsp;</p><p><img alt="Zacks Investment Research" src="https://staticx-tuner.zacks.com/images/articles/charts/2e/102739.jpg?v=2117641640" /><br /><span style="width:100%; display: inline-block; font-size: 8pt;">Image Source: Zacks Investment Research</span></p><p>Further, Robinhood has a P/TB TTM of 5.85X and Interactive Brokers&rsquo; P/TB TTM is 1.14X. So, BGC Group is trading at a massive premium compared with its peers.</p><h2>Investment Thesis for BGC Group</h2><p>BGC Group&rsquo;s proprietary Fenics platform powers its electronic trading operations, enabling faster, more efficient transactions. The platform provides trading solutions, market data and analytics to institutional clients. Following the 2023 spin-off of its commercial real estate arm, Newmark, the company has sharpened its focus on its capital markets and fintech operations. This shift toward technology-driven services allows it to enhance margins and reduce dependence on traditional, labor-intensive models.&nbsp;<br /><br />BGC Group acquired OTC Global Holdings, LP, one of the fastest-growing energy and commodities brokerage firms, in April for $325 million. Moreover, it acquired Sage Energy Partners, LP, an energy and environmental brokerage firm, last year. These buyouts represent an advancement in the company&#39;s growth strategy, solidifying the ECS business as the largest asset class within the company. These acquisitions are projected to contribute more than $450 million in annual revenues and have positioned BGC as a major player in the energy sector.</p><p style="text-align: center;"><strong>ECS Acquisitions&rsquo; Expected Revenue Impact</strong></p><p><img alt="BGC Group Inc." src="https://staticx-tuner.zacks.com/images/articles/charts/68/102742.jpg?v=727543308" /><br /><span style="width:100%; display: inline-block; font-size: 8pt;">Image Source: BGC Group Inc.</span></p><p>BGC Group is well-positioned to capitalize on growing environmental and energy transition trends and will keep benefiting from consistent global demand for oil, the single largest source of energy. As such, the company&rsquo;s top-line growth is anticipated to be impressive. Over the last five years (2019-2024), the company&rsquo;s revenues recorded a CAGR of 1.5%.&nbsp;<br /><br />Other than the above-mentioned buyouts, BGC Group acquired ContiCap, Open Energy Group and Trident in 2023. These deals positioned the company as one of the leading global brokerage firms and bolstered its market share.&nbsp;<br /><br />BGC Group has been prioritizing share repurchases over dividend payouts. The company pays 2 cents per share as a quarterly dividend, which was increased 100% in February 2024. Additionally, in October 2024, the company re-authorized a $400 million share repurchase program. As of Dec. 31, 2024, approximately $350.0 million remained under this authorization.</p><h2>How to Play BGC Group Stock Ahead of Q1 Earnings</h2><p>Heightened market volatility, BGC Group&rsquo;s efforts to diversify its offerings and expansion initiatives to grow market share through acquisitions and organically bode well for its first-quarter results. However, uncertainties regarding tariffs, inflationary pressure, increased regulatory oversight and intense competition keep investors cautious about the company&rsquo;s growth.<br /><br />Nonetheless, BGC Group seems to be better placed to confront the near-term challenges and offer robust returns to investors. This makes it a better investment choice. While BGC stock might seem pricey, its premium valuation is justifiable considering the higher growth expectations.<br /><br />Thus, BGC Group&#39;s prospects look promising. Investors must consider adding the stock to their portfolio for attractive returns.</p><p><a href="https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2461844/buy-sell-or-hold-bgc-group-stock-key-insights-ahead-of-q1-earnings?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-analyst_blog|most_popular_stocks-2461844">This article originally published on Zacks Investment Research (zacks.com).</a></p><p><a href="https://www.zacks.com/">Zacks Investment Research</a></p> ]]>
</description>
<link>
<![CDATA[ https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2461844/buy-sell-or-hold-bgc-group-stock-key-insights-ahead-of-q1-earnings?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-analyst_blog|most_popular_stocks-2461844 ]]>
</link>
<author>
<![CDATA[ Swayta Shah ]]>
</author>
<category domain="tradingview:section">
<![CDATA[ Analyst Blog ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ BGC ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NSDQ:IBKR ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ HOOD ]]>
</category>
</item>
<item>
<guid>
<![CDATA[ https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2461830/cdw-gears-up-to-post-q1-earnings-is-a-beat-in-the-offing?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-analyst_blog|earnings_preview-2461830 ]]>
</guid>
<title>
<![CDATA[ CRA International Shares Barely Move Since Q1 Earnings Beat ]]>
</title>
<pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 12:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
<description>
<![CDATA[ <p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>CDW Corporation </strong>CDW is slated to report first-quarter 2025 results on May 7, before market open. (Find the latest EPS estimates and surprises on Zacks Earnings Calendar.)&nbsp;<br /><br />The Zacks Consensus Estimate for revenues is $4.89 billion, suggesting 0.4% growth from the year-ago quarter&rsquo;s reported figure.<br /><br />The consensus estimate for earnings is pegged at $1.96 per share, unchanged in the past 60 days, indicating an increase of 2.08% from the year-ago quarter&rsquo;s reported figure.<br /><br />CDW&rsquo;s earnings missed the Zacks Consensus Estimate in three of the last four quarters while beating once, with the average negative surprise being 3.1%.</p><h2>Factors Shaping CDW&rsquo;s Upcoming Q1 Results</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Increasing momentum across the cloud and SaaS is likely to have aided CDW&rsquo;s top line in the first quarter. Security and cloud revenues are expected to have benefited as customers&#39; spending priorities include cost optimization, data protection and workforce productivity. CDW remains focused on expanding its cloud and SaaS business to sustain revenue growth amid challenges in the hardware sector.<br /><br />Elevated demand for consumer devices like Notebooks and Chromebooks, coupled with steady growth in software and services, is likely to have acted as a major driving force. We expect revenues from Notebooks/Mobile Devices to be $1185.9 million, up 3.9% year over year. Our estimate for Software and Services revenues is currently pegged at $889.4 million and $436.4 million, respectively.&nbsp; Expanding workloads and surging data, rising security threats, aging client devices and the rising adoption of AI-powered tools and applications are likely to have driven growth against a volatile macroeconomic landscape.<br /><br />In the fourth quarter, revenues from Corporate, Small Business, Public and Healthcare rose 2.6%, 2.7%, 4.4% and 27.5%, respectively, while Government and Education fell 7.1% and 3.7%. For the first quarter, we expect revenues from Corporate, Government and Healthcare to be $2120.3 million, $512.4 million and $552.3 million, down 0.7%, 5.7% and 5.5%, respectively. Revenues from the Education sector and Small Business are estimated to be $668.7 million and $382.4 million, up 12% and 0.4%, respectively.</p><div class="chart_embed"><h3>CDW Corporation Price and EPS Surprise</h3> <img alt="CDW Corporation Price and EPS Surprise" height="262" src="https://staticx-tuner.zacks.com/images/charts/30/1746446407.png" title="" width="538" /> <p>CDW Corporation price-eps-surprise | CDW Corporation Quote</p></div><p style="text-align: justify;">Nonetheless, the company faces risks from a cautious customer approach as it continues to deal with pressing challenges, such as managing growing workloads, strengthening security against rising threats and upgrading aging client devices. Uncertain macroeconomic conditions and a complex technology landscape continue to dampen demand for hardware solutions, showing less sign of immediate recovery.<br /><br />Slower public spending in federal and education and rising uncertainty in the U.K. and Canada due to economic and political turmoil are likely to weigh on CDW&rsquo;s performance in the to-be-reported quarter.</p><h2>What Our Model Says for CDW</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Our proven model predicts an earnings beat for CDW this time around. The combination of a positive Earnings ESP and a Zacks Rank #1 (Strong Buy), 2 (Buy) or 3 (Hold) increases the odds of an earnings beat. That is exactly the case here.<br /><br />CDW currently has an Earnings ESP of +1.02% and a Zacks Rank #3. You can uncover the best stocks to buy or sell before they&rsquo;re reported with our Earnings ESP Filter.</p><h2>Other Stocks With the Favorable Combination</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Here are three other stocks you may want to consider, as our model shows that these, too, have the right elements to post an earnings beat in this reporting cycle.<br /><br /><strong>Expeditors International of Washington</strong> EXPD has an Earnings ESP of +3.76% and a Zacks Rank #3 at present. EXPD is scheduled to report first-quarter 2025 earnings on May 6.&nbsp; You can see <strong>the complete list of today&rsquo;s Zacks #1 Rank stocks here. </strong><br /><br />The Zacks Consensus Estimate for first-quarter 2025 revenues and earnings are pegged at $2.43 billion and $1.30 per share, respectively. EXPD&rsquo;s earnings beat the Zacks Consensus Estimate in each of the preceding four quarters, with the average surprise being 11.6%.<br /><br /><strong>GXO Logistics</strong> GXO currently has an Earnings ESP of +1.18% and a Zacks Rank of 3. The company is slated to report first-quarter 2025 results on May 7. The Zacks Consensus Estimate for first-quarter 2025 revenues and earnings are pegged at $2.91 billion and 26 cents per share, respectively.&nbsp;<br /><br />Shares of GXO have declined 27.1% in the past year.<br /><br /><strong>Sonos</strong> SONO currently has an Earnings ESP of +25.71% and a Zacks Rank of 3. The company is slated to report quarterly results on May 7. The Zacks Consensus Estimate for second-quarter fiscal 2025 revenues and loss are pegged at $255.9 million and 18 cents per share, respectively.&nbsp;<br /><br />Shares of SONO have declined 47.1% in the past year.</p><p><a href="https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2461830/cdw-gears-up-to-post-q1-earnings-is-a-beat-in-the-offing?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-analyst_blog|earnings_preview-2461830">This article originally published on Zacks Investment Research (zacks.com).</a></p><p><a href="https://www.zacks.com/">Zacks Investment Research</a></p> ]]>
</description>
<link>
<![CDATA[ https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2461830/cdw-gears-up-to-post-q1-earnings-is-a-beat-in-the-offing?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-analyst_blog|earnings_preview-2461830 ]]>
</link>
<author>
<![CDATA[ Zacks Equity Research ]]>
</author>
<category domain="tradingview:section">
<![CDATA[ Analyst Blog ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NYSE:EXPD ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NSDQ:SONO ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NSDQ:CDW ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ GXO ]]>
</category>
</item>
<item>
<guid>
<![CDATA[ https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2461712/amgn-s-key-drugs-repatha-evenity-blincyto-drive-q1-sales-growth?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-analyst_blog|earnings_article-2461712 ]]>
</guid>
<title>
<![CDATA[ CRA International Shares Barely Move Since Q1 Earnings Beat ]]>
</title>
<pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 12:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
<description>
<![CDATA[ <p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Amgen </strong>AMGN is off to a strong start in 2025 with its first-quarter earnings as well as sales beating estimates. Particularly, its strong top-line performance caught investor attention.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Amgen&rsquo;s total revenues rose 9% year over year. Total product revenues increased 11% from the year-ago quarter to $7.87 billion as volume growth was partially offset by continued price declines.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">In the first quarter, Amgen witnessed strong volume growth across all areas, backed by strong demand trends for its drugs globally. In the quarter, the company also delivered multiple positive phase III readouts, initiated four new phase III studies, and launched three new products or indications.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Coming back to the first-quarter results, sales of most of its products, like Prolia, Xgeva, Repatha, Blincyto and Evenity, beat estimates. Fourteen products, including Repatha, Blincyto, Tezspire, Tavneos and Evenity, achieved double-digit volume growth in the quarter.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Let us discuss how some of its key drugs performed in the quarter</p><p style="text-align: justify;">So far this year, Amgen&rsquo;s stock has risen 8.8% against the industry&lsquo;s 1.4% decline.</p><p style="text-align: center;"><img alt="Zacks Investment Research" src="https://staticx-tuner.zacks.com/images/articles/charts/58/102728.jpg?v=748148926" style="height: 310px; width: 600px;" /><br /><span style="width:100%; display: inline-block; font-size: 8pt;">Image Source: Zacks Investment Research</span></p><h2>Repatha, Evenity Drive General Medicine Growth</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">In general medicine, Repatha is Amgen&rsquo;s key drug, which is now a multi-billion-dollar product. Repatha generated revenues of $656.0 million, up 27% year over year, driven by higher volume growth. Repatha volumes rose 41%, driven by improved access in the United States, with many payers eliminating prior authorization requirements. Volume growth was partially offset by 9% lower prices due to higher rebates to support expanded access. Repatha sales beat the Zacks Consensus Estimate of $616.0 million and our model estimate of $570.9 million.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Evenity recorded sales of $442 million in the quarter, up 29% year over year, driven by solid volume growth in the United States. Evenity sales beat the Zacks Consensus Estimate of $406.0 million as well as our model estimate of $370.0 million.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Prolia revenues came in at $1.1 billion, up 10% from the year-ago quarter as higher volumes offset the impact of lower pricing. Prolia sales beat the Zacks Consensus Estimate of $994 million as well as our model estimate of $980.8 million.</p><h2>AMGN&rsquo;s Rare Disease Drug Sales Slightly Soft</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Turning to rare disease. Amgen&rsquo;s four key growth drivers, Tepezza, Krystexxa, Uplizna and Tavneos, are all early in their life cycles and well-positioned for long-term growth.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Sales of rare disease drugs rose 3% year over year, delivering $1 billion in sales in the quarter.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">In the quarter, sales of Tepezza and Krystexxa were adversely impacted by changes to U.S. wholesaler inventory levels. Amgen does not expect similar reductions in inventory levels for the remainder of the year.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Tepezza, Krystexxa and Uplizna were added to Amgen&rsquo;s portfolio with the acquisition of Horizon Therapeutics in 2023. Tepezza sales declined 10% year over year to $381 million. Krystexxa sales were flat year over year at $236.0 million. Uplizna rose 14% year over year to $91 million. Tavneos generated $90 million in sales in the quarter, up 76% year over year.</p><h2>AMGN&rsquo;s Oncology Portfolio Remained Strong</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Amgen&rsquo;s innovative oncology portfolio, including Blincyto, Imdelltra, Lumakras, Vectibix, Kyprolis, Nplate and Xgeva grew 10% year over year, generating over $2 billion in sales in the quarter.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">In oncology, the key revenue driver was Blincyto, which generated 370 million in sales, rising 52% from the year-ago period, driven by broad prescribing across both academic and community segments.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Xgeva delivered revenues of $566 million, up 1% year over year. Kyprolis recorded sales of $324 million, down 14% year over year, as competitive pressure hurt volume growth. Vectibix revenues came in at $267 million, up 8% year over year, driven by volume growth.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Nplate sales declined 1% to $313 million. New cancer drug, Imdelltra (tarlatamab), recorded sales of $81 million in the first quarter compared with $67 million in the previous quarter. The drug&rsquo;s 21% sequential growth was driven by volume growth.</p><h2>New Biosimilars Contribute to AMGN&rsquo;s Sales Growth</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">In the first quarter, Amgen&rsquo;s biosimilar portfolio sales were $735 million, up 35% year over year.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">While sales of Amgen&rsquo;s older biosimilars, Mvasi (biosimilar of <strong>Roche</strong>&rsquo;s [RHHBY] Avastin), Kanjinti (a biosimilar of Roche&rsquo;s Herceptin) and Amjevita (biosimilar of AbbVie&rsquo;s Humira) declined, its new biosimilar products generated impressive revenues in the quarter.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">In January, Amgen launched Wezlana, the first biosimilar version of <strong>J&amp;J</strong>&rsquo;s JNJ Stelara, which generated sales of $150 million in the quarter. Wezlana was approved by the FDA in 2023 but launched in January 2025, per a settlement with J&amp;J. Amgen also launched the first biosimilar version of Regeneron&rsquo;s Eylea, Pavblu, in the fourth quarter of 2024, which generated sales of $99 million in the first quarter of 2025. Another key biosimilar product, Bekemv, a biosimilar version of AstraZeneca&rsquo;s Soliris, was approved in the United States in May 2024 and was launched in the second quarter of 2025.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">However, on the first-quarter conference call, Amgen said that fluctuations in quarterly sales for Wezlana are expected in the United States. The company does not expect any sales from Wezlana in the second quarter following a large first-quarter order.</p><p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>AMGN&rsquo;s Inflammation Drugs</strong></p><p style="text-align: justify;">In its inflammation portfolio, sales of Otezla were $437.0 million in the quarter, up 11%, while Enbrel revenues of $510 million declined 10% year over year. Sales of both Otezla and Enbrel beat estimates.</p><h2>Conclusion</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Overall, Amgen&rsquo;s key medicines like Evenity, Repatha and Blincyto, as well as newer medicines like Tavneos and Tezspire, drove sales, more than offsetting declining revenues from oncology biosimilars and legacy established products such as Enbrel. Rare disease drugs are also boosting top-line growth. However, increased pricing headwinds and competitive pressure are hurting sales of many products. Weakness in some key brands like Otezla and Lumakras creates potential revenue headwinds. Sales of best-selling drugs, Prolia and Xgeva, are expected to decline in 2025, mainly from the second half, due to biosimilar competition.</p><h2>AMGN&rsquo;s Zacks Rank</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Amgen currently carries a Zacks Rank #3 (Hold).You can see&nbsp;<strong>the complete list of today&rsquo;s Zacks #1 Rank (Strong Buy) stocks here</strong>.</p><div class="chart_embed"><h3 style="text-align: center;">Amgen Inc. Price and Consensus</h3><p style="text-align: center;"> <img alt="Amgen Inc. Price and Consensus" height="264" src="https://staticx-tuner.zacks.com/images/charts/60/1746440121.png" title="" width="579" /> </p><p>Amgen Inc. price-consensus-chart | Amgen Inc. Quote</p></div><p><a href="https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2461712/amgn-s-key-drugs-repatha-evenity-blincyto-drive-q1-sales-growth?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-analyst_blog|earnings_article-2461712">This article originally published on Zacks Investment Research (zacks.com).</a></p><p><a href="https://www.zacks.com/">Zacks Investment Research</a></p> ]]>
</description>
<link>
<![CDATA[ https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2461712/amgn-s-key-drugs-repatha-evenity-blincyto-drive-q1-sales-growth?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-analyst_blog|earnings_article-2461712 ]]>
</link>
<author>
<![CDATA[ Zacks Equity Research ]]>
</author>
<category domain="tradingview:section">
<![CDATA[ Analyst Blog ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ OTC:RHHBY ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NYSE:JNJ ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NSDQ:AMGN ]]>
</category>
</item>
<item>
<guid>
<![CDATA[ https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2461709/cinco-de-mayo-2025-battle-mexico-vs-france-etf-showdown?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-etf_news_and_commentary-2461709 ]]>
</guid>
<title>
<![CDATA[ CRA International Shares Barely Move Since Q1 Earnings Beat ]]>
</title>
<pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 12:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
<description>
<![CDATA[ <p style="text-align: justify;">Cinco de Mayo, meaning the fifth of May in Spanish, is a day of gratification for all Mexicans. The day honors the Mexican army&#39;s incredible victory over the French militia in the Battle of Puebla in 1862. Though the victory was short-lived as the French finally took over, the day became commemorative of Mexican ethnicity and is widely celebrated even in the United States.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">So, let&rsquo;s play a mock war between Mexico and France. This mock fight will give investors a fair idea of the present stock market scenario of the two countries.</p><p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>iShares MSCI Mexico Capped ETF (</strong>EWW<strong>)</strong>&nbsp;&ndash; Up 19.3% YTD (as of May 3, 2025)<br /><br />The Mexican economy can be represented by the pure-play ETF EWW. The Mexican GDP grew by 0.2% sequentially in the first quarter of 2025, rebounding from a 0.6% contraction in the previous quarter and beating market expectations of no growth.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Although the modest quarter-over-quarter growth kept Mexico from entering a technical recession, it fails to alter the broader narrative of economic vulnerability significantly. The outlook remains uncertain amid tight financial conditions and U.S. trade war risks.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">On the currency front, the Mexican peso just recorded its biggest monthly advance since 2021, thanks to a reprieve in President&nbsp;Donald Trump&rsquo;s tariff plan and a decline in the U.S. dollar. Note that <strong>Invesco DB US Dollar Index Bullish Fund </strong>UUP lost 1.5% over the past month (as of May 3, 2025).</p><p style="text-align: justify;">The&nbsp;peso&nbsp;strengthened 4.4% against the greenback in April, outperforming all its main regional peers after Mexico was one of the few countries to be spared Trump&rsquo;s so-called reciprocal tariffs. But this peso rally is likely to be short-lived as the greenback staring to show strength amid easing global trade tensions. The UUP ETF gained 0.5% last week. The move will go against the Mexican peso.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Overall, growth in Latin America (Latam) is forecast to remain subdued at 1.4% in 2025 and 2.0% in 2026 after a tepid 1.7% in 2024, per KPMG.&nbsp;Given its heavy reliance on U.S. demand and high effective tariff rate, Mexico&mdash;one of the region&rsquo;s most exposed economies&mdash;could fall into recession.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">The fund EWW currently has a Zacks Rank #5 (Strong Sell).</p><p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>iShares MSCI France ETF (</strong>EWQ<strong>)&nbsp;</strong>&ndash; Up 17.8% YTD (as of May 3, 2025)</p><p style="text-align: justify;">On the other hand, the French economy grew by 0.1% sequentially in Q1 of 2025, reversing a 0.1% contraction in Q4 but falling short of market expectations for a 0.2% increase. Subdued household consumption and fixed investment weighed on the growth. A decline in goods purchases was offset by higher spending on services.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">President Trump&#39;s announcement of a three-month-tariff-pause for most countries came as a short-term relief. But French officials are viewing his trade policy as unpredictable.Low consumption and higher savings might lead the French economy close to stagnation for the rest of the year.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Still, the lure of French investments is not absolutely dull. On a yearly basis, the economy advanced 0.8%, in line with an upwardly revised Q4 figure and slightly surpassing consensus of 0.7%.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">The European Central Bank (ECB) has been accommodative. The ECB&rsquo;s generous rate cut momentum has proved to be a game-changer for the European stock market this year. Most Euro zone countries&rsquo; stock markets have surged in 2025 and beat their U.S. counterparts.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">In the tariff-laden past month, <strong>iShares MSCI Eurozone ETF (</strong>EZU<strong>) </strong>(up 7.5%) beat the S&amp;P 500 (up 5.4%). The Fance ETF EWQ also surpassed the gains of the S&amp;P 500, having risen by 6%.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">EWQ has a Zacks ETF Rank #3 (Hold).</p><h2><span style="font-size:18px;">The Winner</span></h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Like the actual war, the Mexico ETF has emerged as the winner this year. &nbsp;But this beat was by a margin. However, over the long term, the battle might present us a different victor like the actual war, given Mexican economy&rsquo;s more vulnerable nature. &nbsp;</p><p style="text-align: justify;">&nbsp;</p><p style="text-align: justify;">&nbsp;</p><p style="text-align: justify;"><br />&nbsp;</p><p><a href="https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2461709/cinco-de-mayo-2025-battle-mexico-vs-france-etf-showdown?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-etf_news_and_commentary-2461709">This article originally published on Zacks Investment Research (zacks.com).</a></p><p><a href="https://www.zacks.com/">Zacks Investment Research</a></p> ]]>
</description>
<link>
<![CDATA[ https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2461709/cinco-de-mayo-2025-battle-mexico-vs-france-etf-showdown?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-etf_news_and_commentary-2461709 ]]>
</link>
<author>
<![CDATA[ Sanghamitra Saha ]]>
</author>
<category domain="tradingview:section">
<![CDATA[ ETF News and Commentary ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NYSE:UUP ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NYSE:EWQ ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NYSE MKT (ex. AMEX):EZU ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NYSE:EWW ]]>
</category>
</item>
<item>
<guid>
<![CDATA[ https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2461707/arm-holdings-stock-before-q4-earnings-to-buy-or-not-to-buy?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-analyst_blog|most_popular_stocks-2461707 ]]>
</guid>
<title>
<![CDATA[ CRA International Shares Barely Move Since Q1 Earnings Beat ]]>
</title>
<pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 12:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
<description>
<![CDATA[ <p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Arm Holdings plc </strong>ARM will report its fourth-quarter fiscal 2025 results on May 7, after the bell.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">The Zacks Consensus Estimate for earnings in the to-be-reported quarter stands at 52 cents, indicating a 44.4% year-over-year growth. The consensus mark for revenues is pegged at $1.23 billion, indicating a 33% year-over-year increase.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">One estimate for the to-be-reported quarter has been revised downward over the past 60 days, versus no upward revisions. Over the same period, the Zacks Consensus Estimate for the quarter&rsquo;s earnings has decreased by 2%.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">&nbsp;</p><p style="text-align: center;"><img alt="Zacks Investment Research" src="https://staticx-tuner.zacks.com/images/articles/charts/59/102721.jpg?v=354909749" style="width: 600px; height: 310px;" /><span style="width:100%; display: inline-block; font-size: 8pt;">Image Source: Zacks Investment Research</span></p><p style="text-align: justify;">The company has an impressive earnings surprise history. Earnings surpassed the Zacks Consensus Estimate in all the trailing four quarters, with an earnings surprise of 18%, on average.</p><p style="text-align: center;"><img alt="Zacks Investment Research" src="https://staticx-tuner.zacks.com/images/articles/charts/17/102722.jpg?v=69832763" style="width: 600px; height: 310px;" /><span style="width:100%; display: inline-block; font-size: 8pt;">Image Source: Zacks Investment Research</span></p><h2>What Our Model Says</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Our proven model doesn&rsquo;t conclusively predict an earnings beat for ARM this time around. The combination of a positive&nbsp;Earnings ESP&nbsp;and a Zacks Rank #1 (Strong Buy), 2 (Buy) or 3 (Hold) increases the odds of an earnings beat. But that&rsquo;s not the case here. You can uncover the best stocks to buy or sell before they&#39;re reported with our&nbsp;Earnings ESP Filter.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">ARM has an Earnings ESP of 0.00% and a Zacks Rank #3. (Find the latest EPS estimates and surprises on Zacks Earnings Calendar.)&nbsp;</p><p style="text-align: justify;">You can see&nbsp;the complete list of today&rsquo;s Zacks #1 Rank stocks here<strong>.</strong></p><h2>Royalty and License Should Drive Performance Growth</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">We expect year-over-year improvement in the company&rsquo;s top line in the to-be-reported quarter to be driven mainly by an increase in Royalty and License revenues. The consensus estimate for License and other revenues is pegged at $665 million, indicating 60.6% year-over-year growth. The consensus mark for Royalty revenues is pegged at $571 million, suggesting a 11.1% year-over-year decline.</p><h2>Price Dynamics</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">ARM has rallied a massive 39% in the past month. This massive rally has sent the stock to a higher valuation. If we look at the forward 12-month Price/Earnings ratio, ARM shares currently trade at 59.6X forward earnings, well above the industry&rsquo;s 26.05X.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">&nbsp;</p><p style="text-align: center;"><img alt="Zacks Investment Research" src="https://staticx-tuner.zacks.com/images/articles/charts/b1/102720.jpg?v=1239830756" style="width: 600px; height: 310px;" /><br /><span style="width:100%; display: inline-block; font-size: 8pt;">Image Source: Zacks Investment Research</span></p><h2>Investment Considerations</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Arm Holdings maintains a dominant foothold in the semiconductor industry, especially in mobile device technology. Its low-power chip architecture has long been a critical component in smartphones and tablets. Major tech giants like <strong>Apple</strong> AAPL, <strong>Qualcomm</strong> QCOM, and Samsung have consistently relied on ARM&rsquo;s designs, making the company a backbone of mobile computing. As Apple, Samsung, and Qualcomm expand their product ecosystems, Arm Holdings&rsquo; technologies continue to see stable, long-term demand.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Looking ahead, the company is well-positioned to benefit from rapid advancements in artificial intelligence and the Internet of Things. Its energy-efficient chips are increasingly embedded in smart devices, autonomous technologies, and cloud infrastructure. With AI workloads and IoT deployments accelerating, the need for scalable, power-efficient solutions has never been greater. Arm Holdings&rsquo; ongoing efforts to tailor its architecture for AI applications further enhance its growth prospects. As Apple, Qualcomm, and Samsung push forward in these spaces, ARM is poised to grow alongside them.</p><h2>Wait for a Better Price</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Given the stock&rsquo;s substantial increase over the past month, it may experience a correction soon. Therefore, it might be wise for investors to wait for a potential correction.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">While ARM remains fundamentally strong, a more advantageous entry point could emerge if the stock undergoes some price adjustment. The company&rsquo;s robust position in the AI hardware market and its strategic advancements in chip design suggest long-term growth potential, but timing the market entry is crucial for maximizing investment returns.</p><p><a href="https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2461707/arm-holdings-stock-before-q4-earnings-to-buy-or-not-to-buy?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-analyst_blog|most_popular_stocks-2461707">This article originally published on Zacks Investment Research (zacks.com).</a></p><p><a href="https://www.zacks.com/">Zacks Investment Research</a></p> ]]>
</description>
<link>
<![CDATA[ https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2461707/arm-holdings-stock-before-q4-earnings-to-buy-or-not-to-buy?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-analyst_blog|most_popular_stocks-2461707 ]]>
</link>
<author>
<![CDATA[ Shuvra Shankar Dey ]]>
</author>
<category domain="tradingview:section">
<![CDATA[ Analyst Blog ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NSDQ:QCOM ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NSDQ:AAPL ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ ARM ]]>
</category>
</item>
<item>
<guid>
<![CDATA[ https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2461708/new-strong-sell-stocks-for-may-5th?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-tale_of_the_tape|new_zacks_5_rank_stocks-2461708 ]]>
</guid>
<title>
<![CDATA[ CRA International Shares Barely Move Since Q1 Earnings Beat ]]>
</title>
<pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 12:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
<description>
<![CDATA[ <p style="text-align: justify;">Here are three stocks added to the Zacks Rank #5 (Strong Sell) List today:</p><p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>CECO Environmental Corp. </strong>CECO provides solutions in industrial air quality, water treatment, and energy transition. The Zacks Consensus Estimate for its current year earnings has been revised 15% downward over the last 60 days.</p><p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Builders FirstSource, Inc. </strong>BLDR is a supplier of building materials, manufactured components, and construction services. The Zacks Consensus Estimate for its current year earnings has been revised 3.5% downward over the last 60 days.</p><p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Eagle Bancorp, Inc. </strong>EGBN is the bank holding company for EagleBank. The Zacks Consensus Estimate for its current year earnings has been revised 15.6% downward over the last 60 days.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">View the entire Zacks Rank #5 List.</p><p><a href="https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2461708/new-strong-sell-stocks-for-may-5th?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-tale_of_the_tape|new_zacks_5_rank_stocks-2461708">This article originally published on Zacks Investment Research (zacks.com).</a></p><p><a href="https://www.zacks.com/">Zacks Investment Research</a></p> ]]>
</description>
<link>
<![CDATA[ https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2461708/new-strong-sell-stocks-for-may-5th?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-tale_of_the_tape|new_zacks_5_rank_stocks-2461708 ]]>
</link>
<author>
<![CDATA[ Zacks Equity Research ]]>
</author>
<category domain="tradingview:section">
<![CDATA[ Tale of the Tape ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NYSE:BLDR ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ CECO ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NSDQ:EGBN ]]>
</category>
</item>
<item>
<guid>
<![CDATA[ https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2461706/should-you-buy-sell-or-hold-applovin-stock-before-q1-earnings?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-analyst_blog|most_popular_stocks-2461706 ]]>
</guid>
<title>
<![CDATA[ CRA International Shares Barely Move Since Q1 Earnings Beat ]]>
</title>
<pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 12:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
<description>
<![CDATA[ <p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>AppLovin Corporation </strong>APP will report its&nbsp;first-quarter 2025&nbsp;results on May 7, after the bell.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">The Zacks Consensus Estimate for earnings in the to-be-reported quarter stands at $1.45, indicating 116.4% growth from the year-ago reported quarter. The consensus estimate for revenues stands at $1.38 billion, implying 30.2% year-over-year growth. There has been no change in analyst estimates or revisions lately.</p><p style="text-align: center;"><img alt="Zacks Investment Research" src="https://staticx-tuner.zacks.com/images/articles/charts/65/102717.jpg?v=94782955" style="width: 600px; height: 310px;" /><span style="width:100%; display: inline-block; font-size: 8pt;">Image Source: Zacks Investment Research</span></p><p style="text-align: justify;">The company has an impressive earnings surprise history. Earnings surpassed the Zacks Consensus Estimate in all the trailing four quarters, with an earnings surprise of 23.5%, on average.</p><p style="text-align: center;"><img alt="Zacks Investment Research" src="https://staticx-tuner.zacks.com/images/articles/charts/73/102719.jpg?v=1449714744" style="width: 600px; height: 310px;" /><span style="width:100%; display: inline-block; font-size: 8pt;">Image Source: Zacks Investment Research</span></p><h2>Q1 Earnings Beat Seems Unlikely for APP</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Our proven model doesn&rsquo;t conclusively predict an earnings beat for APP this time around. The combination of a positive&nbsp;Earnings ESP&nbsp;and a Zacks Rank #1 (Strong Buy), 2 (Buy) or 3 (Hold) increases the odds of an earnings beat. But that&rsquo;s not the case here. You can uncover the best stocks to buy or sell before they&#39;re reported with our&nbsp;Earnings ESP Filter.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">APP has an Earnings ESP of 0.00% and a Zacks Rank #3. (Find the latest EPS estimates and surprises on Zacks Earnings Calendar.)&nbsp;</p><p style="text-align: justify;">You can see&nbsp;<strong>the complete list of today&rsquo;s Zacks #1 Rank stocks here</strong><strong>.</strong></p><h2>Software Platform Should Drive Performance Growth</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">We expect year-over-year improvement in the company&rsquo;s top line in the to-be-reported quarter to be driven mainly by an increase in the Software Platform. The consensus estimate for the Software Platform revenues is pegged at $1.05 billion, indicating 54.3% year-over-year growth. The consensus mark for Appsrevenuesis pegged at $331.7 million, suggesting a 12.7% year-over-year decline.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">The consensus mark for the Software Platform&rsquo;s adjusted EBITDA is pegged at $829.4 million, suggesting 68.6% year-over-year growth. APP&rsquo;s adjusted EBITDA is expected to decrease 16.8% year over year.</p><h2>APP Stock is in a&nbsp;Great Mood</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">APP has rallied a staggering 300% over the past year, easily outpacing the broader industry&#39;s 27% gain. In contrast, competitors like <strong>Alphabet</strong> GOOGL and <strong>Meta Platforms</strong> META have delivered mixed results. Alphabet shares slipped 2% during the same time frame, highlighting weakness in parts of its ad-driven business. Meanwhile, Meta Platforms climbed 29%, benefiting from its strong position in social media advertising. Both Alphabet and Meta Platforms remain major players, but AppLovin&rsquo;s specialized platform is delivering superior returns in this niche.</p><p style="text-align: center;"><img alt="Zacks Investment Research" src="https://staticx-tuner.zacks.com/images/articles/charts/0f/102718.jpg?v=1990819776" style="width: 600px; height: 310px;" /><br /><span style="width:100%; display: inline-block; font-size: 8pt;">Image Source: Zacks Investment Research</span></p><h2>Investment Risk and Rewards for APP</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">AppLovin&#39;s recent financial results underscore its strong fundamentals and impressive growth trajectory. The company continues to benefit from its AXON 2.0 technology and strategic expansion within the gaming and in-app advertising sectors. In the fourth quarter of 2024, revenues surged 44% year over year and 14% sequentially, reflecting strong market demand. Adjusted EBITDA jumped 78% year over year and 17.5% sequentially, showcasing improved operational efficiency. Net income skyrocketed 248% from the prior year and 38% sequentially, demonstrating APP&rsquo;s ability to translate revenue growth into significant profitability.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">For the full year 2024, revenues climbed 43% year over year, while adjusted EBITDA surged 81%, underscoring AppLovin&rsquo;s ability to seize market opportunities while maintaining efficiency. Looking ahead, management has guided for $1.4 billion in the first quarter of 2025 sales, slightly above the Zacks Consensus Estimate of $1.37 billion. Historically, AppLovin has consistently beaten earnings expectations, increasing the likelihood of another outperformance.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">However, potential risks persist. The growth in the in-game advertising segment may face challenges, and the uncertain impact of the company&rsquo;s ventures outside gaming could introduce volatility. Nonetheless, AppLovin&#39;s strategic focus on innovative technology and expansion within the gaming industry positions it well for sustained growth. With AXON 2.0 driving operational efficiencies and a diversified approach to revenue generation, the company is poised to maintain its growth momentum, making it an attractive option for long-term investors.</p><h2>Hold Recommendation</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">The stock has delivered exceptional growth over the past year, with the company showing robust financial results driven by its Software Platform and AXON 2.0 technology. While first-quarter 2025 earnings are expected to show strong year-over-year growth, the absence of a positive Earnings ESP and modest decline in App revenues suggest potential volatility. Still, APP&rsquo;s consistent earnings beats, operational efficiency, and leadership in mobile advertising make it a compelling long-term play. Given near-term uncertainty around earnings and potential sector risks, a Hold is prudent as investors await clearer post-earnings direction and sustained performance confirmation.</p><p><a href="https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2461706/should-you-buy-sell-or-hold-applovin-stock-before-q1-earnings?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-analyst_blog|most_popular_stocks-2461706">This article originally published on Zacks Investment Research (zacks.com).</a></p><p><a href="https://www.zacks.com/">Zacks Investment Research</a></p> ]]>
</description>
<link>
<![CDATA[ https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2461706/should-you-buy-sell-or-hold-applovin-stock-before-q1-earnings?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-analyst_blog|most_popular_stocks-2461706 ]]>
</link>
<author>
<![CDATA[ Shuvra Shankar Dey ]]>
</author>
<category domain="tradingview:section">
<![CDATA[ Analyst Blog ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ APP ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NSDQ:GOOGL ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ META ]]>
</category>
</item>
<item>
<guid>
<![CDATA[ https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2461705/sezzle-set-to-report-q1-earnings-here-s-what-you-should-know?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-analyst_blog|earnings_preview-2461705 ]]>
</guid>
<title>
<![CDATA[ CRA International Shares Barely Move Since Q1 Earnings Beat ]]>
</title>
<pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 12:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
<description>
<![CDATA[ <p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Sezzle Inc. </strong>SEZL is scheduled to release its&nbsp;first-quarter 2025&nbsp;results on May 7, after the bell. SEZL surpassed the Zacks Consensus Estimate in the fourth quarter of 2024 by 40.7%.</p><h2 style="text-align: justify;">Sezzle&rsquo;s Q1 Expectations</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">The Zacks Consensus Estimate projects revenues at $64.8 million, marking a 37.9% increase from the year-ago quarter. This anticipated top-line growth is likely driven by a larger, more engaged subscriber base and favorable momentum from the company&rsquo;s partnership with WebBank. As part of this collaboration, the company introduced Sezzle On-Demand, enabling non-subscribers to access the Sezzle Platform at any online or in-store merchant by paying a one-time finance charge.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">For the bottom line, the consensus estimate stands at 32 cents per share, indicating a 45.5% year-over-year increase, supported by strong revenue gains and disciplined cost management.</p><div class="chart_embed"><h2 style="text-align: center;">Sezzle Inc. Price and EPS Surprise</h2><h2 style="text-align: center;"> <img alt="Sezzle Inc. Price and EPS Surprise" src="https://staticx-tuner.zacks.com/images/charts/02/1746438261.png" style="width: 600px; height: 310px;" title="" /> </h2><p style="text-align: center;">Sezzle Inc. price-eps-surprise | Sezzle Inc. Quote</p></div><h2 style="text-align: justify;">What Our Model Says About SEZL</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Our proven model does not conclusively predict an earnings beat for Sezzle this time around. The combination of a positive&nbsp;Earnings ESP&nbsp;and a Zacks Rank #1 (Strong Buy), 2 (Buy) or 3 (Hold) increases the odds of an earnings beat. But that is not the case here. You can uncover the best stocks before they are reported with our&nbsp;Earnings ESP Filter.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">SEZL has an Earnings ESP of -15.41% and a Zacks Rank of 3 at present. (Find the latest EPS estimates and surprises on Zacks Earnings Calendar.)&nbsp;</p><p style="text-align: justify;">You can see&nbsp;the complete list of today&rsquo;s Zacks #1 Rank stocks here<strong>.</strong></p><h2 style="text-align: justify;">Stocks That Warrant a Look</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Here are a few stocks from the broader Business Services sector, which, according to our model, have the right combination of elements to beat on earnings this season.&nbsp;</p><p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>V2X, Inc., </strong>VVX: The Zacks Consensus Estimate for first-quarter 2025 revenues is pegged at $1 billion, indicating growth of 2% from the year-ago quarter&rsquo;s actual. For earnings, the consensus mark is pegged at 92 cents per share, suggesting a 2.2% rise from the year-ago quarter&rsquo;s reported number. VVX surpassed the consensus estimate in three of the past four quarters and missed once, with an average beat of 14%.&nbsp;</p><p style="text-align: justify;">VVX has an Earnings ESP of +1.53% and a Zacks Rank of 3 at present. It is scheduled to declare its first-quarter 2025 results on May 5.</p><p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Remitly Global, Inc. </strong>RELY: The Zacks Consensus Estimate for first-quarter 2025 revenues is pegged at $347 million, indicating 28.9% growth from the year-ago quarter&rsquo;s actual. The consensus mark for the bottom line is pegged at a loss of 4 cents per share, compared with earnings of 11 cents in the year-ago quarter. RELY surpassed the consensus estimate in the past four quarters, with an average beat of 58.8%.&nbsp;</p><p style="text-align: justify;">It has an Earnings ESP of +14.29% and a Zacks Rank of 3. The company is scheduled to declare its first-quarter 2025&nbsp;results on May 7.</p><p><a href="https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2461705/sezzle-set-to-report-q1-earnings-here-s-what-you-should-know?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-analyst_blog|earnings_preview-2461705">This article originally published on Zacks Investment Research (zacks.com).</a></p><p><a href="https://www.zacks.com/">Zacks Investment Research</a></p> ]]>
</description>
<link>
<![CDATA[ https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2461705/sezzle-set-to-report-q1-earnings-here-s-what-you-should-know?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-analyst_blog|earnings_preview-2461705 ]]>
</link>
<author>
<![CDATA[ Zacks Equity Research ]]>
</author>
<category domain="tradingview:section">
<![CDATA[ Analyst Blog ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ RELY ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ VVX ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ SEZL ]]>
</category>
</item>
<item>
<guid>
<![CDATA[ https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2461768/3-large-cap-blend-mutual-funds-that-should-be-on-your-radar?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-best_of_funds-2461768 ]]>
</guid>
<title>
<![CDATA[ CRA International Shares Barely Move Since Q1 Earnings Beat ]]>
</title>
<pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 12:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
<description>
<![CDATA[ <p style="text-align: justify;">Investors looking for exposure to both value and growth stocks while seeking returns at a lower level of risk may consider large-cap blend mutual funds. Large-cap funds offer more stability than mid- or small-cap funds and are thus safer.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Companies with a market capitalization of more than $10 billion are considered large caps. However, due to their significant international exposure, these companies run the risk of being hit by global woes.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Blend funds, also called hybrid funds, owe their origin to the graphical representation of their equity-style box. In addition to diversification, blend funds offer a great mix of growth and value investment.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Below, we share with you three large-cap blend mutual funds, viz., <strong>Fidelity Large Cap Stock Fund </strong>FLCSX, <strong>Vanguard Growth and Income Fund Investor Shares </strong>VQNPX and <strong>DFA U.S. Social Core Equity 2 Portfolio </strong>DFUEX. Each has earned a&nbsp;Zacks Mutual Fund #1 Rank (Strong Buy), as we expect these to outperform their peers in the future. Investors can&nbsp;click here to see the complete list of funds.</p><p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Fidelity Large Cap Stock Fund </strong>invests most of its net assets in common stocks of domestic and foreign companies with large market capitalization similar to that of the companies listed on the Russell 1000 Index or the S&amp;P 500 Index at the time of purchase. FLCSX advisors choose to invest in either value or growth stocks or a blend of both, along with sound fundamentals like financial condition, industry position, market and economic conditions.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Fidelity Large Cap Stock Fund has three-year annualized returns of 11.9%.As of the end of October 2024, FLCSX had 178 issues and invested 6.2% of its net assets in Microsoft Corp.</p><p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Vanguard Growth and Income Fund Investor Shares&nbsp;</strong>seeks capital appreciation along with dividend income greater than the return of the Standard &amp; Poor&#39;s 500 Index by investing most of its net assets in common stocks that are part of the S&amp;P 500 Index. VQNPX advisors use quantitative methods to select a group of stocks that are expected to give a higher total return than that of the index</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Vanguard Growth and Income Fund Investor Shares&nbsp;has three-year annualized returns of 8.6%. VQNPX has an expense ratio of 0.35%.</p><p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>DFA U.S. Social Core Equity 2 Portfolio</strong> fund invests most of its net assets in a diversified equity portfolio of domestic companies, irrespective of their market capitalization. DFUEX advisors generally invest in small-cap, high-profitability companies that are priced lower than their U.S. coverage universe.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">DFA U.S. Social Core Equity 2 Portfolio fund has three-year annualized returns of 8.1%. John A. Hertzer has been one of the fund managers of DFUEX since February 2022.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">To view the Zacks Rank and the past performance of all Large-Cap Blend Mutual Funds, investors can&nbsp;click here to see the complete list of Large-Cap Blend Mutual Funds.</p><h2 style="text-align: justify;">Want key mutual fund info delivered straight to your inbox?</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Zacks&rsquo; free Fund Newsletter will brief you on top news and analysis, as well as top-performing mutual funds, each week.&nbsp;Get it free &gt;&gt;</p><p><a href="https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2461768/3-large-cap-blend-mutual-funds-that-should-be-on-your-radar?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-best_of_funds-2461768">This article originally published on Zacks Investment Research (zacks.com).</a></p><p><a href="https://www.zacks.com/">Zacks Investment Research</a></p> ]]>
</description>
<link>
<![CDATA[ https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2461768/3-large-cap-blend-mutual-funds-that-should-be-on-your-radar?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-best_of_funds-2461768 ]]>
</link>
<author>
<![CDATA[ Zacks Equity Research ]]>
</author>
<category domain="tradingview:section">
<![CDATA[ Best of Funds ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ VQNPX ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ DFUEX ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ FLCSX ]]>
</category>
</item>
<item>
<guid>
<![CDATA[ https://www.zacks.com/commentary/2461672/best-growth-stocks-to-buy-for-may-5th?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-zacks_1_rank_additions|growth_additions-2461672 ]]>
</guid>
<title>
<![CDATA[ CRA International Shares Barely Move Since Q1 Earnings Beat ]]>
</title>
<pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 12:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
<description>
<![CDATA[ <p style="text-align: justify;">Here are three stocks with buy ranks and strong growth characteristics for investors to consider today, May 5<sup>th</sup>:</p><p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Limbach Holdings, Inc. </strong>LMB: This company which engineers, constructs and services the mechanical, plumbing, air conditioning, heating, building automation, electrical and control systems, carries a Zacks Rank #1 (Strong Buy), and has witnessed the Zacks Consensus Estimate for its current year earnings increasing 9.9% over the last 60 days.</p><div class="chart_embed"><h3>Limbach Holdings, Inc. Price and Consensus</h3> <img alt="Limbach Holdings, Inc. Price and Consensus" height="264" src="https://staticx-tuner.zacks.com/images/charts/c9/1746439453.png" title="" width="573" /> <p>Limbach Holdings, Inc. price-consensus-chart | Limbach Holdings, Inc. Quote</p></div><p>Limbach has a PEG ratio of 2.49 compared with 3.40 for the industry. The company possesses a Growth Score of A.</p><div class="chart_embed"><h3>Limbach Holdings, Inc. PEG Ratio (TTM)</h3> <img alt="Limbach Holdings, Inc. PEG Ratio (TTM)" height="250" src="https://staticx-tuner.zacks.com/images/charts/c2/1746439845.png" title="" width="527" /> <p>Limbach Holdings, Inc. peg-ratio-ttm | Limbach Holdings, Inc. Quote</p></div><p><strong>Broadcom Inc. </strong>AVGO: These company which is a premier designer, developer and global supplier of a broad range of semiconductor devices, carries a Zacks Rank #1, and has witnessed the Zacks Consensus Estimate for its current year earnings increasing 4.6% over the last 60 days.</p><div class="chart_embed"><h3>Broadcom Inc. Price and Consensus</h3> <img alt="Broadcom Inc. Price and Consensus" height="264" src="https://staticx-tuner.zacks.com/images/charts/eb/1746439464.png" title="" width="573" /> <p>Broadcom Inc. price-consensus-chart | Broadcom Inc. Quote</p></div><p>Broadcom has a PEG ratio of 1.62 compared with 12.96 for the industry. The company possesses a Growth Score of B.</p><div class="chart_embed"><h3>Broadcom Inc. PEG Ratio (TTM)</h3> <img alt="Broadcom Inc. PEG Ratio (TTM)" height="250" src="https://staticx-tuner.zacks.com/images/charts/9c/1746440649.png" title="" width="527" /> <p>Broadcom Inc. peg-ratio-ttm | Broadcom Inc. Quote</p></div><p><strong>BGC Group, Inc. </strong>BGC: This brokerage and financial technology company which through its various affiliates, specializes in the brokerage of a broad range of products, including Fixed Income, Foreign Exchange, Equities, Energy and Commodities, Shipping and Futures carries a Zacks Rank #1, and has witnessed the Zacks Consensus Estimate for its current year earnings increasing 5.2% over the last 60 days.</p><div class="chart_embed"><h3>BGC Group, Inc. Price and Consensus</h3> <img alt="BGC Group, Inc. Price and Consensus" height="264" src="https://staticx-tuner.zacks.com/images/charts/30/1746439545.png" title="" width="562" /> <p>BGC Group, Inc. price-consensus-chart | BGC Group, Inc. Quote</p></div><p>BGC has a PEG ratio of 0.31 compared with 1.32 for the industry. The company possesses a Growth Score&nbsp; of B.</p><div class="chart_embed"><h3>BGC Group, Inc. PEG Ratio (TTM)</h3> <img alt="BGC Group, Inc. PEG Ratio (TTM)" height="250" src="https://staticx-tuner.zacks.com/images/charts/df/1746440667.png" title="" width="527" /> <p>BGC Group, Inc. peg-ratio-ttm | BGC Group, Inc. Quote</p></div><p>&nbsp;</p><p>See the full list of top ranked stocks here.</p><p>&nbsp;</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Learn more about the Growth score and how it is calculated here.</p><p><a href="https://www.zacks.com/commentary/2461672/best-growth-stocks-to-buy-for-may-5th?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-zacks_1_rank_additions|growth_additions-2461672">This article originally published on Zacks Investment Research (zacks.com).</a></p><p><a href="https://www.zacks.com/">Zacks Investment Research</a></p> ]]>
</description>
<link>
<![CDATA[ https://www.zacks.com/commentary/2461672/best-growth-stocks-to-buy-for-may-5th?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-zacks_1_rank_additions|growth_additions-2461672 ]]>
</link>
<author>
<![CDATA[ Zacks Equity Research ]]>
</author>
<category domain="tradingview:section">
<![CDATA[ Zacks #1 Rank Additions ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ BGC ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NSDQ:AVGO ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NSDQ:LMB ]]>
</category>
</item>
<item>
<guid>
<![CDATA[ https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2461755/will-speciality-and-glp-1-drugs-help-cor-beat-q2-earnings-estimates?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-analyst_blog|earnings_preview-2461755 ]]>
</guid>
<title>
<![CDATA[ CRA International Shares Barely Move Since Q1 Earnings Beat ]]>
</title>
<pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 12:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
<description>
<![CDATA[ <p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Cencora&nbsp;</strong>COR is slated to report second-quarter fiscal 2025 results on May 7, before market open.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">In the last reported quarter, the company delivered an earnings surprise of 6.57%. COR&rsquo;s earnings beat estimates in each of the trailing four quarters, delivering an average surprise of 4.94%.(Stay up-to-date with all quarterly releases:&nbsp;See Zacks Earnings Calendar.)</p><h2 style="text-align: justify;">Q2 Estimates</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">The Zacks Consensus Estimate for revenues is pegged at $74.82 billion, up 9.4% from the prior-year quarter&rsquo;s level. The consensus mark for earnings is pinned at $4.08 per share, indicating an improvement of 7.4% from the prior-year quarter&rsquo;s figure.</p><h2 style="text-align: justify;">Factors to Consider</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Cencora is expected to have delivered a moderate performance in the fiscal second quarter, following a strong start in the previous quarter. In its U.S. Healthcare Solutions segment, the company reported 14% revenue growth to $74 billion and a 10% increase in segment operating income. The growth is likely to have continued on the back of strong demand for specialty distribution as well as GLP-1 drugs.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">COR&rsquo;s strong execution in distribution for physician practices and health systems, coupled with growing adoption of biosimilars, positions it well for consistent revenue performance. Moreover, the Retina Consultants of America&rsquo;s acquisition in January should have brought in additional revenues during the quarter.</p><div class="chart_embed"><h3>Cencora, Inc. Price and EPS Surprise</h3> <img alt="Cencora, Inc. Price and EPS Surprise" height="262" src="https://staticx-tuner.zacks.com/images/charts/6f/1746441261.png" title="" width="600" /> <p>Cencora, Inc. price-eps-surprise | Cencora, Inc. Quote</p></div><p style="text-align: justify;">However, the declining COVID-19 vaccine contribution might have hurt segmental sales as well as margins. Meanwhile, management expects sluggish growth in GLP-1 drug sales (compared with the 53% year-over-year increase seen in the first quarter).</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Our model expects revenues for this segment to be $66.61 billion. Adjusted operating income is estimated to be $901.9 million.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">On the international front, Cencora&rsquo;s Healthcare Solutions segment posted 5.5% revenue growth (8.5% in constant currency) but a 3% decrease in reported operating income in the first quarter. The second quarter is expected to be weaker on a sequential basis, primarily due to a stronger U.S. dollar hurting reported growth, even as constant-currency volumes remain steady.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">The company also anticipates a continuation of softer performance in its specialty logistics business, particularly World Courier, due to muted activity in clinical trials and cell and gene therapies. Additionally, macroeconomic and operational softness in certain European and animal health markets may weigh on near-term performance. However, Cencora expects a rebound in the second half of the year as international logistics normalize and currency effects potentially ease.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Our model expects the segment&rsquo;s adjusted operating income and revenues to be $185.7 million and $7.41 billion, respectively.</p><h2 style="text-align: justify;">Earnings Beat Likely</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Our proven model predicts an earnings beat for Cencora this time around. The combination of a positive&nbsp;Earnings ESP&nbsp;and a Zacks Rank #1 (Strong Buy), 2 (Buy) or 3 (Hold) increases the chances of an earnings beat.</p><p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Earnings ESP:</strong>&nbsp;Earnings ESP, which represents the difference between the Most Accurate Estimate and the Zacks Consensus Estimate, is +0.82%. You can uncover the best stocks to buy or sell before they&#39;re reported with our&nbsp;Earnings ESP Filter.</p><p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Zacks Rank:</strong>&nbsp;Cencora currently has a Zacks Rank #2.</p><h2 style="text-align: justify;">Other Stocks Worth a Look</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Here are some other medical stocks worth considering, as these, too, have the right combination of elements to post an earnings beat this reporting cycle.</p><p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Premier</strong>&nbsp;PINC has an Earnings ESP of +13.82% and a Zacks Rank #2 at present.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">PINC&rsquo;s earnings surpassed estimates in three of the trailing four quarters and missed the same in one, the average surprise being 20.43%. The Zacks Consensus Estimate for fiscal third-quarter EPS implies a decline of 43.6% from the year-ago reported figure.<strong>You can see&nbsp;</strong><strong>the complete list of today&rsquo;s Zacks #1 Rank stocks here</strong>.</p><p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>HealthEquity</strong>&nbsp;HQY has an Earnings ESP of +2.03% and a Zacks Rank #3 at present.&nbsp;</p><p style="text-align: justify;">HQY&rsquo;s earnings surpassed estimates in three of the trailing four quarters and missed the same in one, the average surprise being 12.78%. The Zacks Consensus Estimate for fiscal first-quarter EPS implies an improvement of 1.3% from the year-ago reported figure.</p><p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Progyny</strong> PGNY has an Earnings ESP of +2.68% and a Zacks Rank #3 at present. The company is scheduled to release first-quarter results on May 8.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">PGNY&rsquo;s earnings surpassed estimates in each of the trailing four quarters, the average surprise being 54.91%. The Zacks Consensus Estimate for first-quarter EPS implies an improvement of 15.4% from the year-ago reported figure.</p><p><a href="https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2461755/will-speciality-and-glp-1-drugs-help-cor-beat-q2-earnings-estimates?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-analyst_blog|earnings_preview-2461755">This article originally published on Zacks Investment Research (zacks.com).</a></p><p><a href="https://www.zacks.com/">Zacks Investment Research</a></p> ]]>
</description>
<link>
<![CDATA[ https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2461755/will-speciality-and-glp-1-drugs-help-cor-beat-q2-earnings-estimates?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-analyst_blog|earnings_preview-2461755 ]]>
</link>
<author>
<![CDATA[ Zacks Equity Research ]]>
</author>
<category domain="tradingview:section">
<![CDATA[ Analyst Blog ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NYSE:COR ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NSDQ:PINC ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NSDQ:HQY ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NSDQ:PGNY ]]>
</category>
</item>
<item>
<guid>
<![CDATA[ https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2461752/teleflex-q1-earnings-beat-25-eps-view-down-stock-up?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-analyst_blog|earnings_article-2461752 ]]>
</guid>
<title>
<![CDATA[ CRA International Shares Barely Move Since Q1 Earnings Beat ]]>
</title>
<pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 12:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
<description>
<![CDATA[ <p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Teleflex Incorporated</strong> TFX posted first-quarter 2025 adjusted earnings per share (EPS) from continuing operations of $2.91, down 9.3% from the year-ago quarter&rsquo;s figure. The metric topped the Zacks Consensus Estimate by 1%.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">GAAP EPS was $2.07 compared with $0.33 in the prior-year period.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Following the announcement, shares of the company rose 0.4% last Friday.&nbsp;</p><h2 style="text-align: justify;">TFX&rsquo;s Revenues</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Net revenues fell 5% year over year (down 3.8% at constant exchange rate or CER) to $700.7 million. However, the metric surpassed the Zacks Consensus Estimate by 0.2%. (See the Zacks Earnings Calendar to stay ahead of market-making news.)&nbsp;</p><h2 style="text-align: justify;">Segmental Analysis of TFX&rsquo;s Q1 Revenues</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Teleflex has three reportable segments &mdash; Americas, EMEA (Europe, the Middle East and Africa) and Asia (Asia Pacific).</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Net revenues in the <strong>Americas</strong> were $475.7 million, which decreased 3.7% from the year-ago period&rsquo;s level (down 3.2% at CER). This compares with our model&rsquo;s projection of $477.9 million for the quarter.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">The <strong>EMEA (Europe, the Middle East and Africa)</strong> net revenues of $151.2 million decreased 5.3% year over year (down 2.8% at CER). Our model projected revenues of $144.4 million for the quarter.&nbsp;</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Revenues from <strong>Asia (Asia Pacific)</strong> fell 12.8% to $73.8 million (down 9.7% at CER). Our model&rsquo;s projection was $75.4 million.</p><h2 style="text-align: justify;">TFX&rsquo;s Q1 Product Revenues in Detail</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">The <strong>Vascular Access</strong> segment recorded net revenues of $182.4 million, up 1.9% year over year at CER. This compares with our model&rsquo;s projection of $179.6 million.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">The <strong>Interventional</strong> business registered net revenues of $137.5 million, up 3.2% year over year at CER. This compares with our model&rsquo;s projection of $137.4 million.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Within the <strong>Anesthesia</strong> segment, net revenues decreased 8.6% year over year at CER to $86.6 million. This compares with our model&rsquo;s projection of $91.6 million.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">The <strong>Surgical</strong> segment recorded net revenues of $105.8 million, up 2% year over year at CER. Our model&rsquo;s projection was $108.7 million.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Revenues from the <strong>Interventional Urology</strong> segment totaled $71 million, down 10.7% year over year at CER. This compares with our model&rsquo;s projection of $70.1 million.</p><p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>OEM</strong> recorded revenue growth of $63.9 million, down 26.8% year over year at CER. This compares with our model&rsquo;s projection of $64 million.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">The <strong>Other</strong> product segment&rsquo;s (consisting of the company&rsquo;s respiratory products not included in the divestiture to Medline, manufacturing service agreement revenues and Urology Care products) net revenues of $53.5 million registered a year-over-year increase of 4.5% at CER. This compares with our model&rsquo;s projection of $46.6 million for the quarter.</p><h2 style="text-align: justify;">TFX&rsquo;s Margin Performance</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">The gross profit totaled $389.4 million, down 6.4% year over year. The gross margin contracted 82 basis points (bps) to 55.6% due to a 3.3% rise in the cost of goods sold.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Overall, the adjusted operating profit was $130.3 million, down 4.2% year over year. The adjusted operating margin expanded 17 bps to 18.6%.</p><h2 style="text-align: justify;">TFX&rsquo;s Liquidity Position</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Teleflex exited the first quarter of 2025 with cash and cash equivalents of $284.1 million compared with $290.2 million at the end of the fourth quarter of 2024.&nbsp;</p><h2>Teleflex Incorporated Price, Consensus and EPS Surprise</h2><div class="chart_embed"> <img alt="Teleflex Incorporated Price, Consensus and EPS Surprise" height="264" src="https://staticx-tuner.zacks.com/images/charts/71/1746440883.png" title="" width="579" /> <p>Teleflex Incorporated price-consensus-eps-surprise-chart | Teleflex Incorporated Quote</p></div><p style="text-align: justify;">Net cash flow provided by operating activities from continuing operations was $73.3 million compared with $112.8 million in the year-ago period.</p><h2 style="text-align: justify;">Teleflex&rsquo;s Updated 2025 Guidance</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">GAAP revenue growth for 2025 is now expected to be in the range of 1.28-2.28% (down from the prior guidance of 0.4% decline to 0.7% growth). The Zacks Consensus Estimate for total revenues is pegged at $3.07 billion.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Teleflex now anticipates adjusted EPS from continuing operations to be in the range of $13.20 to $13.60 (down from the prior guidance of $13.95-$14.35). The Zacks Consensus Estimate for EPS is pegged at $13.78.</p><h2 style="text-align: justify;">Our Take on TFX</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Teleflex exited the first quarter of 2025 with better-than-expected results, wherein both earnings and revenues beat estimates. However, the year-over-year decline in revenues was due to softness in orders in the EMEA region.&nbsp;</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Interventional, Vascular Access and Surgical businesses performed well with single-digit adjusted constant currency growth. Within Anesthesia, endotracheal tubes and hemostatic products showed growth in the quarter, which was offset by tough military orders and pressure on airway products.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">On a positive note, Teleflex has entered into a definitive agreement to acquire substantially all of the Vascular Intervention business of BIOTRONIK SE &amp; Co. KG. With the acquisition of BIOTRONIK products, Teleflex will gain meaningful scale, expand its presence in the cath lab and be poised for continued growth. The product portfolio includes a broad suite of vascular intervention devices such as drug-coated balloons, drug-eluting stents, covered stents balloon and self-expanding bare metal stents and balloon catheters.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">On the flip side, a contraction of the adjusted gross margin does not bode well for the stock. Also, the company&rsquo;s lowered 2025 adjusted EPS guidance adds to the worry.&nbsp;</p><h2 style="text-align: justify;">TFX&rsquo;s Zacks Rank and Key Picks</h2><p style="text-align: justify;">Teleflex currently carries a Zacks Rank #4 (Sell).</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Some better-ranked stocks from the broader medical space are <strong>AngioDynamics</strong> ANGO, <strong>Veeva Systems</strong> VEEV and <strong>Masimo </strong>MASI.&nbsp;</p><p style="text-align: justify;">AngioDynamics, currently sporting a Zacks Rank #1 (Strong Buy), reported third-quarter fiscal 2025 adjusted EPS of 3 cents, which beat the Zacks Consensus Estimate of a loss of 13 cents. You can see the complete list of today&rsquo;s Zacks #1 Rank stocks here.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Revenues of $72 million beat the Zacks Consensus Estimate by 2%. ANGO has an estimated fiscal 2026 earnings growth rate of 27.8% compared with the S&amp;P 500 composite&rsquo;s 10.5%. The company&rsquo;s earnings beat estimates in each of the trailing four quarters, the average surprise being 70.9%.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Veeva Systems, sporting a Zacks Rank #1 at present, posted fourth-quarter fiscal 2025 adjusted EPS of $1.75, which exceeded the Zacks Consensus Estimate by 10.1%. Revenues of $720.9 million surpassed the Zacks Consensus Estimate by 3.2%.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">VEEV has an estimated long-term earnings growth rate of 26.6% compared with the industry&rsquo;s 20.8%. The company&rsquo;s earnings surpassed estimates in each of the trailing four quarters, the average surprise being 7.9%.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">Masimo, currently sporting a Zacks Rank #1, reported fourth-quarter 2024 adjusted EPS of $1.80, which surpassed the Zacks Consensus Estimate by 20.8%. Revenues of $600.7 million topped the Zacks Consensus Estimate by 0.8%.</p><p style="text-align: justify;">MASI has an estimated earnings yield of 3.5% for fiscal 2025 compared with the industry&rsquo;s 3.6%. The company&rsquo;s earnings surpassed estimates in each of the trailing four quarters, the average surprise being 14.4%.</p><p><a href="https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2461752/teleflex-q1-earnings-beat-25-eps-view-down-stock-up?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-analyst_blog|earnings_article-2461752">This article originally published on Zacks Investment Research (zacks.com).</a></p><p><a href="https://www.zacks.com/">Zacks Investment Research</a></p> ]]>
</description>
<link>
<![CDATA[ https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2461752/teleflex-q1-earnings-beat-25-eps-view-down-stock-up?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-analyst_blog|earnings_article-2461752 ]]>
</link>
<author>
<![CDATA[ Zacks Equity Research ]]>
</author>
<category domain="tradingview:section">
<![CDATA[ Analyst Blog ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NSDQ:ANGO ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NSDQ:MASI ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NYSE:TFX ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NYSE:VEEV ]]>
</category>
</item>
<item>
<guid>
<![CDATA[ https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2461751/nisource-to-release-q1-earnings-here-s-what-you-need-to-know?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-analyst_blog|earnings_preview-2461751 ]]>
</guid>
<title>
<![CDATA[ CRA International Shares Barely Move Since Q1 Earnings Beat ]]>
</title>
<pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 12:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
<description>
<![CDATA[ <p><strong>NiSource </strong>NI is scheduled to release first-quarter 2025 results on May 7, before market open. The company delivered an earnings surprise of 4.3% in the last reported quarter. (See the Zacks Earnings Calendar to stay ahead of market-making news.)<br /><br />Let&rsquo;s discuss the factors that are likely to be reflected in the upcoming quarterly results.</p><h2>Major Factors That Might Have Impacted NI&#39;s Q1 Performance</h2><p>Northern Indiana Public Service Company LLC (&ldquo;NIPSCO&rdquo;), a subsidiary of NiSource, completed the Dunns Bridge II solar and storage project, which went online in January 2025. The project has a generation capacity of 435 megawatts, which is likely to have boosted the quarterly bottom line.<br /><br />Columbia Gas of Virginia and Columbia Gas of Kentucky&rsquo;s new rates became effective in January 2025. This is expected to have positively impacted NiSource&rsquo;s top line in the to-be-reported quarter.<br /><br />The company&rsquo;s revenues are also likely to have benefited from the new electric and gas rates that were implemented during the fourth quarter in its service territories.<br /><br />The bottom line is expected to have gained from increased investments, capital programs, and flat operation and maintenance expenses.<br /><br />However, higher depreciation and amortization expenses might have offset some of these positives in the first quarter.</p><h2>Q1 Expectations for NI</h2><p>The Zacks Consensus Estimate for earnings is pegged at 90 cents per share, implying a year-over-year increase of 5.9%.<br /><br />The Zacks Consensus Estimate for revenues is pinned at $1.86 billion, indicating an increase of 8.9% from the year-ago reported number.</p><h2>What Our Quantitative Model Predicts</h2><p>Our proven model does not predict an earnings beat for NiSource this time around. The combination of a positive Earnings ESP and a Zacks Rank #1 (Strong Buy), 2 (Buy) or 3 (Hold) increases the odds of an earnings beat. That is not the case here, as you will see below.<br />&nbsp;</p><div class="chart_embed"><h3>NiSource, Inc Price and EPS Surprise</h3><p style="text-align: justify;"> <img alt="NiSource, Inc Price and EPS Surprise" height="262" src="https://staticx-tuner.zacks.com/images/charts/06/1746440711.png" title="" width="533" /> </p><p>NiSource, Inc price-eps-surprise | NiSource, Inc Quote</p></div><p><strong>Earnings ESP:</strong> The company&rsquo;s Earnings ESP is 0.00%. You can uncover the best stocks to buy or sell before they&rsquo;re reported with our Earnings ESP Filter.<br /><br /><strong>Zacks Rank: </strong>Currently, NiSource carries a Zacks Rank #3. You can see <strong>the complete list of today&#39;s Zacks #1 Rank stocks here.</strong></p><h2>Stocks to Consider</h2><p>Investors may consider the following players from the same sector, as these have the right combination of elements to post an earnings beat this reporting cycle.<br /><br /><strong>American Electric Power</strong> AEP is likely to come up with an earnings beat when it reports first-quarter results on May 6. It has an Earnings ESP of +0.54% and a Zacks Rank #3 at present.<br /><br />AEP&rsquo;s long-term (three to five years) earnings growth rate is 6.43%. The Zacks Consensus Estimate for earnings is pinned at $1.39 per share, which implies a year-over-year increase of 9.5%.<br /><br /><strong>Alliant Energy</strong> LNT is likely to come up with an earnings beat when it reports first-quarter results on May 8. It has an Earnings ESP of +9.88% and a Zacks Rank #3 at present.<br /><br />LNT&rsquo;s long-term earnings growth rate is 6.73%. The Zacks Consensus Estimate for earnings is pinned at 57 cents per share, which implies a year-over-year decrease of 8.1%.<br /><br /><strong>MDU Resources Group</strong> MDU is likely to come up with an earnings beat when it reports first-quarter results on May 8. It has an Earnings ESP of +8.33% and a Zacks Rank #1 at present.<br /><br />MDU&rsquo;s long-term earnings growth rate is 6.46%. The Zacks Consensus Estimate for first-quarter earnings is pinned at 36 cents per share.<br /><br />&nbsp;</p><p><a href="https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2461751/nisource-to-release-q1-earnings-here-s-what-you-need-to-know?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-analyst_blog|earnings_preview-2461751">This article originally published on Zacks Investment Research (zacks.com).</a></p><p><a href="https://www.zacks.com/">Zacks Investment Research</a></p> ]]>
</description>
<link>
<![CDATA[ https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2461751/nisource-to-release-q1-earnings-here-s-what-you-need-to-know?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-analyst_blog|earnings_preview-2461751 ]]>
</link>
<author>
<![CDATA[ Zacks Equity Research ]]>
</author>
<category domain="tradingview:section">
<![CDATA[ Analyst Blog ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NYSE:NI ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NSDQ:AEP ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NSDQ:LNT ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NYSE:MDU ]]>
</category>
</item>
<item>
<guid>
<![CDATA[ https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2461749/murphy-oil-to-release-q1-earnings-here-s-what-you-need-to-know?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-analyst_blog|earnings_preview-2461749 ]]>
</guid>
<title>
<![CDATA[ CRA International Shares Barely Move Since Q1 Earnings Beat ]]>
</title>
<pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 12:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
<description>
<![CDATA[ <p><strong>Murphy Oil Corporation</strong> MUR is scheduled to release first-quarter 2025 results on May 7, after market close. The company delivered a negative earnings surprise of 37.5% in the last reported quarter. (See the Zacks Earnings Calendar to stay ahead of market-making news.)<br /><br />Let&rsquo;s discuss the factors that are likely to be reflected in the upcoming quarterly results.</p><h2>Key Factors That May Impact MUR&rsquo;s Q1 Results</h2><p>Murphy Oil&rsquo;s quarterly earnings are expected to have benefited from the production ramp-up in its domestic and international assets. The company benefited from new wells that were added in the Gulf of Mexico and Eagle Ford Shale.<br /><br />Production increases from diversified, low breakeven North American portfolio, have aided Murphy Oil&#39;s overall financial performance and free cash flow, enabling it to increase shareholder returns through stock repurchases. This is expected to have boosted the bottom line in the yet-to-be-reported quarter.<br /><br />Increased capital investments are expected to have further enhanced the company&rsquo;s offshore operations, since 45% of total investments are targeted toward offshore. &nbsp;<br /><br />Murphy Oil&#39;s ongoing debt-reduction initiatives are expected to have lowered capital servicing expenses, thus boosting margins in the to-be-reported quarter.</p><h2>Q1 Expectations for MUR</h2><p>The Zacks Consensus Estimate for earnings is pegged at 48 cents per share, indicating a year-over-year decrease of 43.5%. The Zacks Consensus Estimate for revenues is pinned at $667.76 million, indicating a decrease of 16.2% year over year.<br /><br />Murphy Oil anticipates quarterly production, excluding NCI, of 159-167 thousand barrels of oil equivalent per day (MBOEPD). Out of the expected production, 51% is anticipated to be oil. The Zacks Consensus Estimate is pegged at 164.83 MBOEPD.</p><h2>What Our Quantitative Model Predicts</h2><p>Our proven model predicts an earnings beat for Murphy Oil this time around. The combination of a positive Earnings ESP and a Zacks Rank #1 (Strong Buy), 2 (Buy) or 3 (Hold) increases the odds of an earnings beat, which is the case here, as you will see below.<br />&nbsp;</p><div class="chart_embed"><h3>Murphy Oil Corporation Price and EPS Surprise</h3><p style="text-align: justify;"> <img alt="Murphy Oil Corporation Price and EPS Surprise" height="262" src="https://staticx-tuner.zacks.com/images/charts/5a/1746439228.png" title="" width="533" /> </p><p>Murphy Oil Corporation price-eps-surprise | Murphy Oil Corporation Quote</p></div><p><strong>Earnings ESP:</strong> The company&rsquo;s Earnings ESP is +4.90%. You can uncover the best stocks to buy or sell before they&rsquo;re reported with our Earnings ESP Filter.<br /><br /><strong>Zacks Rank: </strong>Currently, Murphy Oil has a Zacks Rank #3. You can see <strong>the complete list of today&#39;s Zacks #1 Rank stocks here.</strong></p><h2>Other Stocks to Consider</h2><p>Investors may also consider the following players from the same sector, as these, too, have the right combination of elements to come up with an earnings beat this reporting cycle.<br /><br /><strong>Energy Transfer</strong> ET is expected to come up with an earnings beat when it reports first-quarter results on May 6, after market close. It has an Earnings ESP of +1.54% and a Zacks Rank #3 at present.<br /><br />ET&rsquo;s long-term (three to five years) earnings growth rate is 21.4%. The Zacks Consensus Estimate for first-quarter earnings is pinned at 33 cents per share.<br /><br /><strong>APA Corporation</strong> APA is expected to post an earnings beat when it announces first-quarter results on May 7, after market close. It has an Earnings ESP of +4.52% and a Zacks Rank #3 at present.<br /><br />The Zacks Consensus Estimate for first-quarter earnings is pinned at 83 cents per share. The Zacks Consensus Estimate for sales is pegged at $2.21 billion, indicating year-over-year growth of 16.3%.<br /><br /><strong>Occidental Petroleum</strong> OXY is likely to come up with an earnings beat when it announces first-quarter results on May 7, after market close. It has an Earnings ESP of +0.56% and a Zacks Rank #3 at present.<br /><br />The Zacks Consensus Estimate for first-quarter earnings is pinned at 73 cents per share. The company delivered an average earnings surprise of 23.6% in the trailing four quarters.<br /><br />&nbsp;</p><p><a href="https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2461749/murphy-oil-to-release-q1-earnings-here-s-what-you-need-to-know?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-analyst_blog|earnings_preview-2461749">This article originally published on Zacks Investment Research (zacks.com).</a></p><p><a href="https://www.zacks.com/">Zacks Investment Research</a></p> ]]>
</description>
<link>
<![CDATA[ https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/2461749/murphy-oil-to-release-q1-earnings-here-s-what-you-need-to-know?cid=CS-TRADINGVIEW-FT-analyst_blog|earnings_preview-2461749 ]]>
</link>
<author>
<![CDATA[ Zacks Equity Research ]]>
</author>
<category domain="tradingview:section">
<![CDATA[ Analyst Blog ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NSDQ:APA ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NYSE:OXY ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NYSE:MUR ]]>
</category>
<category domain="tradingview:symbol">
<![CDATA[ NYSE:ET ]]>
</category>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>