<rss xmlns:metadata="http://search.cnbc.com/rss/2.0/modules/siteContentMetadata" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
<channel>
<description>CNBC.com -- First in business worldwide.</description>
<image>
<description>CNBC.com -- First in business worldwide.</description>
<link>https://www.cnbc.com</link>
<url>https://media.cnbc.com/i/CNBC/CNBC_Images/componentbacks/logo_small.gif</url>
<title>CNBC.com</title>
</image>
<copyright>© CNBC, Inc. All Rights Reserved.</copyright>
<title>CNBC News</title>
<link>http://www.cnbc.com</link>
<language>en-us</language>
<pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 15:16:07 GMT</pubDate>
<item>
<media:thumbnail url="https://image.cnbcfm.com/api/v1/image/106317071-15778366643ED1-MM-123119-C.jpg?v=1577836662"/>
<link>https://www.cnbc.com/video/2019/12/31/cramer-makes-the-bull-case-for-including-bonds-in-your-portfolio.html</link>
<media:keywords>Personal finance</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Bonds</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Business</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Jim Cramer</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Investment strategy</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Investment strategy</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Personal investing</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Markets</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Stock markets</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Mad Money with Jim Cramer</media:keywords>
<guid>106317004</guid>
<media:network>US</media:network>
<media:duration>570</media:duration>
<metadata:contentType>Video</metadata:contentType>
<media:show>Mad Money</media:show>
<metadata:country>US</metadata:country>
<metadata:provider>NBCU</metadata:provider>
<metadata:channel>CNBC</metadata:channel>
<title>Cramer makes the bull case for including bonds in your portfolio</title>
<description>Jim Cramer addresses the lingering question of how much is the right amount of bond exposure.</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 23:58:01 GMT</pubDate>
<metadata:updatedDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 23:58:01 GMT</metadata:updatedDate>
<category>Mad Money</category>
<media:content medium="video" bitrate="4500" url="http://pdl.iphone.cnbc.com//VCPS/Y2019/M12D31/7000115776/3ED1-MM-123119-C_MBR_4500.mp4"/>
</item>
<item>
<media:thumbnail url="https://image.cnbcfm.com/api/v1/image/106317065-3ed1-mm-123119-a.jpg?v=1577836030"/>
<link>https://www.cnbc.com/video/2019/12/31/cramer-how-compounding-can-help-you-double-your-money-in-7-years.html</link>
<media:keywords>Do Not Use(use 100271106) - S&P 500 Index </media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Personal finance</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Business</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Jim Cramer</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Investment strategy</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Investment strategy</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Personal investing</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Markets</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Stock markets</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Mad Money with Jim Cramer</media:keywords>
<guid>106317002</guid>
<media:network>US</media:network>
<media:duration>700</media:duration>
<metadata:contentType>Video</metadata:contentType>
<media:show>Mad Money</media:show>
<metadata:country>US</metadata:country>
<metadata:provider>NBCU</metadata:provider>
<metadata:channel>CNBC</metadata:channel>
<title>Cramer: How compounding can help you double your money in 7 years</title>
<description>Jim Cramer explains why young investors stand to benefit from the magic of compounding.</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 23:54:27 GMT</pubDate>
<metadata:updatedDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 23:54:27 GMT</metadata:updatedDate>
<category>Mad Money</category>
<media:content medium="video" bitrate="4500" url="http://pdl.iphone.cnbc.com//VCPS/Y2019/M12D31/7000115774/1577836015920-3ED1-MM-123119-A_MBR_4500.mp4"/>
</item>
<item>
<media:thumbnail url="https://image.cnbcfm.com/api/v1/image/106317064-3ed1-mm-123119-c-short.jpg?v=1577835817"/>
<link>https://www.cnbc.com/video/2019/12/31/the-bull-case-for-bonds-in-your-portfolio.html</link>
<media:keywords>Business</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Jim Cramer</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Investment strategy</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Investment strategy</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Personal investing</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Markets</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Stock markets</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Mad Money with Jim Cramer</media:keywords>
<guid>106317003</guid>
<media:network>US</media:network>
<media:duration>58</media:duration>
<metadata:contentType>Video</metadata:contentType>
<media:show>Mad Money</media:show>
<metadata:country>US</metadata:country>
<metadata:provider>NBCU</metadata:provider>
<metadata:channel>CNBC</metadata:channel>
<title>The bull case for bonds in your portfolio</title>
<description>Jim Cramer addresses the lingering question of how much is the right amount of bond exposure.</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 23:45:48 GMT</pubDate>
<metadata:updatedDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 23:45:48 GMT</metadata:updatedDate>
<category>Mad Money</category>
<media:content medium="video" bitrate="4500" url="http://pdl.iphone.cnbc.com//VCPS/Y2019/M12D31/7000115772/1577835806231-3ED1-MM-123119-C-SHORT_MBR_4500.mp4"/>
</item>
<item>
<media:thumbnail url="https://image.cnbcfm.com/api/v1/image/106312389-1577369980326gettyimages-1152948850.jpeg?v=1690440708"/>
<link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/12/31/north-korean-leader-kim-jong-un-warns-of-shocking-action-new-strategic-weapon.html</link>
<content:encoded>
<![CDATA[ <ul> <li>North Korea leader Kim Jong Un said Wednesday the world will witness a new strategic weapon in the near future, according to the North's state-run media.</li> <li>The announcement came a week after the world braced for a "Christmas gift" that Kim promised to send to the United States.</li> <li>Trump downplayed Kim's cryptic message about a gift and said that rather than a missile test, "maybe it's a nice present."</li></ul><img src="https://image.cnbcfm.com/api/v1/image/106312389-1577369980326gettyimages-1152948850.jpeg?v=1690440708&amp;w=1910&amp;h=1000" data-licensor-name="Brendan Smialowski | AFP | Getty Images" width="1910" alt="North Korea's leader Kim Jong Un in the Demilitarized Zone on June 30, 2019." id="106312389" height="1000"></img><p>North Korean leader Kim Jong Un said Wednesday he will continue developing his country's nuclear deterrent and introduce a new strategic weapon in the near future, according to the North's <a href="https://kcnawatch.org/newstream/1577829999-473709661/report-on-5th-plenary-meeting-of-7th-c-c-wpk/">state-run media KCNA</a>.</p><p>Kim's remarks came after the United States missed a year-end deadline for a restart of denuclearization talks.</p><p>The White House and the Pentagon did not immediately respond to CNBC's request for comment.</p><p>U.S. Secretary of State Mike Pompeo said he hoped North Korea would "choose peace."</p><p>"So, seeing that reporting publicly, it remains the case that we hope that Chairman Kim will take a different course," Pompeo told Fox News in an interview. "We're hopeful that ... Chairman Kim will make the right decision - he'll choose peace and prosperity over conflict and war."</p><p>Kim convened a rare four-day meeting of the ruling Workers' Party's policy-making committee since Saturday as the United States had not responded to his repeated calls for concessions to reopen negotiations, dismissing the deadline as artificial.</p><p>Kim had warned he might have to seek a "new path" if Washington fails to meet his expectations. U.S. military commanders said Pyongyang's actions could include the testing of an intercontinental ballistic missile (ICBM), which it has halted since 2017, alongside nuclear warhead tests.</p><p>There were no grounds for North Korea to be bound any longer by the self-declared nuclear and ICBM test moratorium as the United States continued joint military drills with South Korea, adopted cutting-edge weapons and imposed sanctions while making "gangster-like demands", Kim said, according to KCNA.</p><p>He pledged to further develop North Korea's nuclear deterrent but left the door open for dialogue, saying the "scope and depth" of that deterrent will be "properly coordinated depending on" the attitude of the United States.</p><p>"The world will witness a new strategic weapon to be possessed by the DPRK in the near future," Kim said, using the acronym for North Korea's official name, the Democratic People's Republic of Korea.</p><p>"We will reliably put on constant alert the powerful nuclear deterrent capable of containing the nuclear threats from the U.S. and guaranteeing our long-term security."</p><p>The announcement comes a week after the world braced for a "Christmas gift" that Kim promised to send to the United States. <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2019/12/24/trump-north-koreas-christmas-gift-may-be-vase-not-missile-test.html?&amp;doc=106316989">Trump downplayed Kim's cryptic message</a> and said that rather than a missile test, "maybe it's a nice present."</p><p>"Maybe it's a present where he sends me a beautiful vase as opposed to a missile test," Trump said. "I may get a vase. I may get a nice present from him. You don't know. You never know."</p><a autoplay_flag="false" href="https://www.cnbc.com/video/2019/12/18/kim-jong-un-may-have-faced-domestic-hard-line-pressure.html?&amp;doc=106316989"></a><p>Under third-generation North Korean leader Kim Jong Un, the reclusive state has conducted its most powerful nuclear test, launched its first-ever intercontinental ballistic missile and threatened to send missiles into the waters near Guam.</p><p>Since 2011, <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2019/12/29/all-the-missiles-and-nukes-north-korea-has-tested-in-one-chart.html?&amp;doc=106316989">Kim has launched more than 100 missiles</a> and conducted four nuclear weapons tests, which is more than what his father, Kim Jong Il, and grandfather, Kim Il Sung, launched over a period of 27 years.</p><p>Earlier this month, North Korean state media said that a "very important" test was carried out at a rocket testing ground. Trump responded to the report by tweeting that Kim risks losing "everything" if he does not take steps to denuclearize.<br><br>"Kim Jong Un is too smart and has far too much to lose, everything actually, if he acts in a hostile way. He signed a strong Denuclearization Agreement with me in Singapore," Trump wrote on Twitter, referring to his first summit with Kim in 2018.</p><p>North Korea's ambassador to the United Nations said on the heels of the test that denuclearization was off the negotiating table with the U.S. and lengthy talks with Washington were no longer needed.</p><p><em>— Reuters contributed to this report.</em></p><a autoplay_flag="false" href="https://www.cnbc.com/video/2019/12/24/north-koreas-christmas-gift-to-the-us-may-be-an-icbm-says-expert.html?&amp;doc=106316989"></a><p></p> ]]>
</content:encoded>
<media:keywords>Politics</media:keywords>
<author>Amanda Macias</author>
<guid>106316989</guid>
<metadata:contentType>Story</metadata:contentType>
<metadata:country>US</metadata:country>
<metadata:provider>NBCU</metadata:provider>
<metadata:channel>CNBC</metadata:channel>
<media:content url="http://pdl.iphone.cnbc.com//VCPS/Y2019/M12D23/7000114907/2ED2-ASB-HarryKazianis-122319_MBR_4500.mp4" medium="video" height="1000" width="1910">
<media:description>It's "very clear" that North Korea's "Christmas gift" to the U.S. will be an intercontinental ballistic missile, and it's unlikely to be a satellite test, says Harry Kazianis of the Center for the National Interest. They may also put a "dummy warhead" on the missile to show that it can get through the atmosphere and hit a city, he says.</media:description>
<media:title>North Korea's 'Christmas gift' to the US may be an ICBM, says expert</media:title>
<media:thumbnail width="1910" height="1000" url="https://image.cnbcfm.com/api/v1/image/106310769-15771510192ED2-ASB-HarryKazianis-122319.jpg?v=1577151018&w=1910&h=1000"/>
</media:content>
<media:content url="http://pdl.iphone.cnbc.com//VCPS/Y2019/M12D17/7000114002/3ED2-ASB-VipinNarang-121719_MBR_4500.mp4" medium="video" height="1000" width="1910">
<media:description>Vipin Narang of MIT says China and Russia could have agreed to let Kim Jong Un to test missiles, but not nuclear weapons. North Korea is "waves away" from reopening nuclear testing, he says.</media:description>
<media:title>Kim Jong Un may have faced 'domestic hard line pressure'</media:title>
<media:thumbnail width="1910" height="1000" url="https://image.cnbcfm.com/api/v1/image/106301894-15766511353ED2-ASB-VipinNarang-121719.jpg?v=1576651134&w=1910&h=1000"/>
</media:content>
<title>North Korean leader Kim Jong Un warns of 'shocking' action, new strategic weapon</title>
<description>North Korea leader Kim Jong Un says the world will witness a new strategic weapon in the near future, according to the North's state-run media.</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 21:59:06 GMT</pubDate>
<metadata:updatedDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 23:37:57 GMT</metadata:updatedDate>
<category>Politics</category>
</item>
<item>
<media:thumbnail url="https://image.cnbcfm.com/api/v1/image/106317059-15778339283ED1-FM-123119-REMIX.jpg?v=1577833928"/>
<link>https://www.cnbc.com/video/2019/12/31/2020-stock-resolutions-4-trades.html</link>
<media:keywords>McCormick & Company Inc</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Goldman Sachs Group Inc</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Nike Inc</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Twitter Inc</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Stock markets</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Wall Street</media:keywords>
<guid>106317058</guid>
<media:network>US</media:network>
<media:duration>143</media:duration>
<metadata:contentType>Video</metadata:contentType>
<media:show>Fast Money</media:show>
<metadata:country>US</metadata:country>
<metadata:provider>NBCU</metadata:provider>
<metadata:channel>CNBC</metadata:channel>
<title>2020 stock resolutions: 4 trades</title>
<description>The "Fast Money" traders ring in the new year with 4 stocks to trade in 2020.</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 23:13:26 GMT</pubDate>
<metadata:updatedDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 23:13:26 GMT</metadata:updatedDate>
<category>Fast Money</category>
<media:content medium="video" bitrate="4500" url="http://pdl.iphone.cnbc.com//VCPS/Y2019/M12D31/7000115769/3ED1-FM-123119-REMIX_MBR_4500.mp4"/>
</item>
<item>
<media:thumbnail url="https://image.cnbcfm.com/api/v1/image/106316600-1577803864057gettyimages-1191101513.jpeg?v=1577803906"/>
<link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/12/31/trump-says-iran-will-be-held-fully-responsible-for-attack-on-the-us-embassy-in-iraq.html</link>
<content:encoded>
<![CDATA[ <ul> <li>"Iran is orchestrating an attack on the U.S. Embassy in Iraq. They will be held fully responsible," President Trump wrote on Twitter.</li> <li>His tweet came after dozens of angry Iraqi Shiite militia supporters stormed the U.S. Embassy compound in Baghdad shouting "Down, Down, USA!"</li> <li>The Iraqi protest followed deadly U.S. airstrikes that killed 25 fighters of the Iran-backed militia in Iraq, carried out in retaliation for the killing of an American contractor.</li></ul><a autoplay_flag="false" href="https://www.cnbc.com/video/2019/12/31/protesters-storm-us-embassy-in-iraq-after-deadly-airstrikes.html?&amp;doc=106316457"></a><p>President <strong>Donald Trump</strong> on Tuesday blamed Iran for planning an attack on the U.S. Embassy in Iraq and promised to hold Tehran "fully responsible."</p><p>"Iran killed an American contractor, wounding many. We strongly responded, and always will," the president wrote on Twitter. "Now Iran is orchestrating an attack on the U.S. Embassy in Iraq. They will be held fully responsible."</p><p>"In addition, we expect Iraq to use its forces to protect the Embassy, and so notified!" he added.</p><p><a href="https://twitter.com/realDonaldTrump/status/1211981022084128768">trump tweet</a></p><p>Later Tuesday, Trump amplified his harsh words for Iran. "This is not a Warning, it is a Threat," the president tweeted. "Happy New Year!"</p><p><a href="https://twitter.com/realDonaldTrump/status/1212121026072592384">trump tweet 2</a></p><p>Iran denied it was behind the violent protests and warned against any retaliation. "American officials have the astounding audacity of attributing to Iran the protests of the Iraqi people against (Washington's) savage killing of at least 25 Iraqis ...," Iranian Foreign Ministry spokesman Abbas Mousavi said in a statement carried on a ministry website.</p><p>Trump's tweets came after dozens of angry Iraqi Shiite militia supporters <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2019/12/31/supporters-of-iran-backed-militia-storm-the-us-embassy-in-iraq.html?&amp;doc=106316457">stormed the U.S. Embassy compound</a> in Baghdad and set fire to a reception area on the grounds earlier in the day.</p><p>The Iraqi supporters, many dressed in military apparel, pushed into the compound using cars to break through its gate. The protesters hung a poster on the wall saying, "America is an aggressor."</p><p>Though the mob stopped short of entering the main building of the compound, many shouted "Down, Down, USA!" and flung water and rocks over the embassy walls. About 30 Iraqi soldiers in armored vehicles arrived near the embassy hours after the violence, according to an Associated Press report.</p><p>The attack followed deadly U.S. airstrikes on Sunday that killed 25 fighters of the Iran-backed militia in Iraq, carried out in retaliation for last week's killing of an American contractor in a rocket attack on an Iraqi military base that American officials blamed on the militia.</p><p>"The President is in close touch with his national security team and is receiving regular updates," said White House Press Secretary Stephanie Grisham. "As the President said, Iran is orchestrating this attack and they will be held fully responsible. It will be the President's choice how and when we respond to their escalation."</p><a autoplay_flag="false" href="https://www.cnbc.com/video/2019/12/30/video-shows-aftermath-of-us-airstrikes-on-an-iranian-backed-militia-in-iraq.html?&amp;doc=106316457"></a><p>Trump also spoke with Iraqi Prime Minister Adel Abd al-Mahdi and emphasized the need to protect U.S. personnel and facilities, the White House said in a statement later Tuesday.</p><p>Secretary of Defense Mark Esper said the U.S. would be sending additional troops to the compound to assist in its protection.</p><p>"We are sending additional forces to support our personnel at the Embassy. As in all countries, we rely on host nation forces to assist in the protection of our personnel in country, and we call on the Government of Iraq to fulfill its international responsibilities to do so," he said in a statement.</p><p>"We have taken appropriate force protection actions to ensure the safety of American citizens, military personnel and diplomats in country, and to ensure our right of self-defense," Esper added.</p><p>The U.S. strikes over the weekend were the latest to target the Iraqi state-sanctioned and Iranian-backed militia and appear to mark the start of a more fierce power struggle between the U.S. and Iran throughout the Middle East.</p><p>While Secretary of State Mike Pompeo said Sunday's strikes were designed to convey that the White House will not turn a blind eye to actions taken by Iran that jeopardize American lives, the Iraqi government deemed the attack a "flagrant violation" of its sovereignty and said it will reexamine its relationship with the U.S.-led coalition.</p><p><em>— CNBC's </em><a href="https://www.cnbc.com/amanda-macias/?&amp;doc=106316457"><em>Amanda Macias</em></a><em> and Reuters contributed to this report.</em></p> ]]>
</content:encoded>
<media:keywords>Middle East</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Baghdad</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Iran</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Iraq</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Breaking News: Markets</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Breaking News: Politics</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Donald Trump</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Amanda Macias</media:keywords>
<author>Thomas Franck</author>
<guid>106316457</guid>
<metadata:contentType>Story</metadata:contentType>
<metadata:country>US</metadata:country>
<metadata:provider>NBCU</metadata:provider>
<metadata:channel>CNBC</metadata:channel>
<media:content url="http://pdl.iphone.cnbc.com//VCPS/Y2019/M12D30/7000115500/1577724759966-2ED4-REQ-123019IranAirstrikes_MBR_4500.mp4" medium="video" height="1000" width="1910">
<media:description>The Pentagon said in a statement that three locations in Iraq and two in Syria were targeted by U.S. forces. The locations included weapon storage facilities and command and control locations that the Iranian-backed Shi'ite Muslim militia uses to plan and execute attacks on OIR coalition forces.</media:description>
<media:title>Video shows aftermath of US airstrikes on an Iranian-backed militia in Iraq</media:title>
<media:thumbnail width="1910" height="1000" url="https://image.cnbcfm.com/api/v1/image/106315341-2ed4-req-123019iranairstrikes.jpg?v=1577724790&w=1910&h=1000"/>
</media:content>
<media:content url="http://pdl.iphone.cnbc.com//VCPS/Y2019/M12D31/7000115685/1577805398972-3ED5-BL-123019-IraqProtests_MBR_4500.mp4" medium="video" height="1000" width="1910">
<media:description>"Iran is orchestrating an attack on the U.S. Embassy in Iraq. They will be held fully responsible," President Trump wrote on Twitter. His tweet came after dozens of angry Iraqi Shiite militia stormed the U.S. Embassy compound in Baghdad shouting "Down, Down, USA!" The Iraqi protest followed deadly U.S. airstrikes that killed 25 fighters of the Iran-backed militia in Iraq, carried out in retaliation for the killing of an American contractor.</media:description>
<media:title>Protesters storm US embassy in Iraq after deadly airstrikes</media:title>
<media:thumbnail width="1910" height="1000" url="https://image.cnbcfm.com/api/v1/image/106316449-1577794006689gettyimages-1191100730.jpeg?v=1577794105&w=1910&h=1000"/>
</media:content>
<title>Trump says Iran will be held 'fully responsible' for attack on the US embassy in Iraq</title>
<description>President Donald Trump on Tuesday blamed Iran for planning an attack on the U.S. Embassy in Iraq.</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 12:11:16 GMT</pubDate>
<metadata:updatedDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 23:12:27 GMT</metadata:updatedDate>
<category>Politics</category>
</item>
<item>
<media:thumbnail url="https://image.cnbcfm.com/api/v1/image/106317044-15778327333ED1-FM-123119-E.jpg?v=1577832733"/>
<link>https://www.cnbc.com/video/2019/12/31/a-global-protection-play.html</link>
<media:keywords>iShares MSCI EAFE ETF</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Investment strategy</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Markets</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Stock markets</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Wall Street</media:keywords>
<guid>106317032</guid>
<media:network>US</media:network>
<media:duration>103</media:duration>
<metadata:contentType>Video</metadata:contentType>
<media:show>Options Action</media:show>
<metadata:country>US</metadata:country>
<metadata:provider>NBCU</metadata:provider>
<metadata:channel>CNBC</metadata:channel>
<title>A global protection play</title>
<description>Mike Khouw looks at a hedging portfolio position in EFA.</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 23:11:31 GMT</pubDate>
<metadata:updatedDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 23:11:31 GMT</metadata:updatedDate>
<category>Options Action</category>
<media:content medium="video" bitrate="4500" url="http://pdl.iphone.cnbc.com//VCPS/Y2019/M12D31/7000115764/3ED1-FM-123119-E_MBR_4500.mp4"/>
</item>
<item>
<media:thumbnail url="https://image.cnbcfm.com/api/v1/image/106317052-3ed1-fm-123119-g.jpg?v=1577833535"/>
<link>https://www.cnbc.com/video/2019/12/31/the-fast-money-2019-year-in-review.html</link>
<media:keywords>NASDAQ 100 Index</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Dow Jones Industrial Average</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>S&P 500 Index</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>iShares Russell 2000 ETF</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>World economy</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Stock markets</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Wall Street</media:keywords>
<author>Melissa Lee</author>
<guid>106317026</guid>
<media:network>US</media:network>
<media:duration>186</media:duration>
<metadata:contentType>Video</metadata:contentType>
<media:show>Fast Money</media:show>
<metadata:country>US</metadata:country>
<metadata:provider>NBCU</metadata:provider>
<metadata:channel>CNBC</metadata:channel>
<title>The Fast Money 2019 year in review</title>
<description>A look back at the year 2019 with the Fast Money traders.</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 23:07:33 GMT</pubDate>
<metadata:updatedDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 23:07:33 GMT</metadata:updatedDate>
<category>Fast Money</category>
<media:content medium="video" bitrate="4500" url="http://pdl.iphone.cnbc.com//VCPS/Y2019/M12D31/7000115766/1577833505653-3ED1-FM-123119-G_MBR_4500.mp4"/>
</item>
<item>
<media:thumbnail url="https://image.cnbcfm.com/api/v1/image/106317042-15778326243ED5-TN-123119-GeneMunster-SHORT.jpg?v=1577832622"/>
<link>https://www.cnbc.com/video/2019/12/31/why-apple-could-become-a-400-stock-in-2020.html</link>
<media:keywords>Investment strategy</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Stock markets</media:keywords>
<guid>106316997</guid>
<media:network>US</media:network>
<media:duration>68</media:duration>
<metadata:contentType>Video</metadata:contentType>
<media:show>Trading Nation</media:show>
<metadata:country>US</metadata:country>
<metadata:provider>NBCU</metadata:provider>
<metadata:channel>CNBC</metadata:channel>
<title>Why Apple could become a $400 stock in 2020</title>
<description>Loup Ventures' Gene Munster lists Apple as his top FAANG stock for the new year.</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 22:56:23 GMT</pubDate>
<metadata:updatedDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 22:56:23 GMT</metadata:updatedDate>
<category>Trading Nation</category>
<media:content medium="video" bitrate="4500" url="http://pdl.iphone.cnbc.com//VCPS/Y2019/M12D31/7000115749/3ED5-TN-123119-GeneMunster-SHORT_MBR_4500.mp4"/>
</item>
<item>
<media:thumbnail url="https://image.cnbcfm.com/api/v1/image/106317040-3ed1-fm-123119-d.jpg?v=1577832545"/>
<link>https://www.cnbc.com/video/2019/12/31/the-pulse-of-the-consumer.html</link>
<media:keywords>Brinker International Inc</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Darden Restaurants Inc</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Bloomin' Brands Inc</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Dine Brands Global</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Consumerism</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Consumer Discretionary Select Sector SPDR Fund</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>NASDAQ 100 Index</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Dow Jones Industrial Average</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>S&P 500 Index</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>iShares Russell 2000 ETF</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>World economy</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Stock markets</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Wall Street</media:keywords>
<author>Melissa Lee</author>
<guid>106317022</guid>
<media:network>US</media:network>
<media:duration>506</media:duration>
<metadata:contentType>Video</metadata:contentType>
<media:show>Fast Money</media:show>
<metadata:country>US</metadata:country>
<metadata:provider>NBCU</metadata:provider>
<metadata:channel>CNBC</metadata:channel>
<title>The pulse of the consumer</title>
<description>Zane Tankel, Apple Metro chairman & CEO, discusses the impact of consumers on the U.S. economy. With CNBC's Morgan Brennan and the Fast Money traders, Steve Grasso, Karen Finerman, Dan Nathan and Guy Adami.</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 22:51:08 GMT</pubDate>
<metadata:updatedDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 22:51:08 GMT</metadata:updatedDate>
<category>Fast Money</category>
<media:content medium="video" bitrate="4500" url="http://pdl.iphone.cnbc.com//VCPS/Y2019/M12D31/7000115762/1577832418574-3ED1-FM-123119-D_MBR_4500.mp4"/>
</item>
<item>
<media:thumbnail url="https://image.cnbcfm.com/api/v1/image/106317028-3ed1-fm-123119-a.jpg?v=1577830785"/>
<link>https://www.cnbc.com/video/2019/12/31/its-been-a-record-year-for-your-money-now-what.html</link>
<media:keywords>Catch Me Up</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Bed Bath & Beyond Inc</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Spdr S&P Retail Etf</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Energy Select Sector SPDR Fund</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>NASDAQ 100 Index</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Dow Jones Industrial Average</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>S&P 500 Index</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>iShares Russell 2000 ETF</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>World economy</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Stock markets</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Wall Street</media:keywords>
<author>Melissa Lee</author>
<guid>106317012</guid>
<media:network>US</media:network>
<media:duration>618</media:duration>
<metadata:contentType>Video</metadata:contentType>
<media:show>Fast Money</media:show>
<metadata:country>US</metadata:country>
<metadata:provider>NBCU</metadata:provider>
<metadata:channel>CNBC</metadata:channel>
<title>It's been a record year for your money. Now what?</title>
<description>The traders offer their 2020 playbook. With CNBC's Morgan Brennan and the Fast Money traders, Steve Grasso, Karen Finerman, Dan Nathan and Guy Adami.</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 22:21:58 GMT</pubDate>
<metadata:updatedDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 22:47:12 GMT</metadata:updatedDate>
<category>Fast Money</category>
<media:content medium="video" bitrate="4500" url="http://pdl.iphone.cnbc.com//VCPS/Y2019/M12D31/7000115753/1577830719726-3ED1-FM-123119-A_MBR_4500.mp4"/>
</item>
<item>
<media:thumbnail url="https://image.cnbcfm.com/api/v1/image/106316918-caroleghosninterviewsonclosingbell.jpg?v=1577823178"/>
<link>https://www.cnbc.com/video/2019/12/31/carlos-ghosn-fled-japan-for-lebanonheres-what-his-wife-said-on-closing-bell-in-2019.html</link>
<media:keywords>Corporate controversy</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Nissan</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Carlos Ghosn</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Beirut</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Lebanon</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Japan</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Crime</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Stock markets</media:keywords>
<guid>106316907</guid>
<media:network>US</media:network>
<media:duration>204</media:duration>
<metadata:contentType>Video</metadata:contentType>
<media:show>Closing Bell</media:show>
<metadata:country>US</metadata:country>
<metadata:provider>NBCU</metadata:provider>
<metadata:channel>CNBC</metadata:channel>
<title>Carlos Ghosn fled Japan for Lebanon—Here's what his wife said on 'Closing Bell' in 2019</title>
<description>Carlos Ghosn, the ousted chairman of Japanese automaker Nissan, said in a statement that he's left Japan and is now in Lebanon. Ghosn was awaiting trial on criminal charges in Japan. His wife, Carole Ghosn, is said to have helped organize his escape. Here are the key moments from Carole Ghosn's interviews on CNBC's "Closing Bell."</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 20:27:22 GMT</pubDate>
<metadata:updatedDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 22:47:07 GMT</metadata:updatedDate>
<category>Closing Bell</category>
<media:content medium="video" bitrate="4500" url="http://pdl.iphone.cnbc.com//VCPS/Y2019/M12D31/7000115736/1577823466283-CaroleGhosninterviewsonClosingBell_MBR_4500.mp4"/>
</item>
<item>
<media:thumbnail url="https://image.cnbcfm.com/api/v1/image/106074997-1565643500288gettybuffettnew.jpg?v=1677865470"/>
<link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/12/31/this-decade-saw-warren-buffett-finally-exit-ibm-jump-big-into-apple.html</link>
<content:encoded>
<![CDATA[ <p><em><strong>As we get ready to say goodbye to the 2010s, CNBC.com is taking a look back at the key players, events and transformations from Wall Street to Silicon Valley to corporate America to the White House that shaped a </strong></em><a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2019/12/13/the-2010s-a-decade-of-disruption.html?&amp;doc=106315407"><em><strong>"Decade of Disruption."</strong></em></a><em><strong> In the lead-up to New Year's Day 2020, CNBC's online journalists will be exploring the moments that defined the past 10 years for your money and set the table for the next decade and beyond.</strong></em></p><p>One of <strong>Warren Buffett</strong>'s biggest investment mistakes, <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/IBM&amp;&amp;doc=106315407">IBM</a>, played out over an agonizing seven-year stretch this decade, which saw the stock plummet along with the company's fortunes. However, the <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/BRK.A&amp;&amp;doc=106315407">Berkshire Hathaway</a> chief was undaunted by his misstep in technology, a sector he generally avoided as a self-admitted Luddite. While fully exiting IBM in the early part of 2018, Buffett simultaneously revealed to CNBC that Berkshire Hathaway amassed an even bigger stake in <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/AAPL&amp;&amp;doc=106315407">Apple</a>, which by late 2019 would become his most valuable holding.</p><p>Berkshire's transition out of IBM and in to Apple marked a changing of the guard in technology. IBM and Apple, rival computer-makers in the 1980s, took very different paths over the years, with IBM struggling to capitalize on its focus on enterprise and Apple emerging and thriving as a dominant force in consumer electronics with the iPhone.</p><h4>Berkshire started buying IBM shares in 2011</h4><p><a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2011/11/14/what-has-warren-buffett-been-buying-harold.html?&amp;doc=106315407">Buffett's IBM debacle began in November 2011</a> when he said on <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/squawk-box-us/?&amp;doc=106315407">"Squawk Box"</a> that Berkshire Hathaway bought 64 million shares at an average price of $170 each, valuing the stake at the time at $10.7 billion. Buffett said he went against his no-tech-company-rule because he'd been "hit between the eyes" by how IBM finds and keeps clients. "It's a company that helps IT departments do their job better," he added. "There is a lot of continuity to it."</p><p>However, by the time he told CNBC's <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/becky-quick/?&amp;doc=106315407">Becky Quick</a> in May 2018 that Berkshire Hathaway <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2018/05/04/warren-buffett-says-berkshire-hathaway-has-sold-completely-out-of-ibm.html?&amp;doc=106315407">no longer owned any IBM stock,</a> the tech company had suffered nearly six years of declining revenue and a share price sinking into the mid-$140 range.</p><a autoplay_flag="false" href="https://www.cnbc.com/video/2018/05/04/berkshire-hathaway-bought-75-million-shares-of-apple-in-q1.html?&amp;doc=106315407"></a><p>Wasting no time licking his wounds, Buffett said, in that same May 2018 CNBC interview, that <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2018/05/03/buffetts-berkshire-hathaway-bought-stunning-75-million-apple-shares-in-first-quarter.html?&amp;doc=106315407">Berkshire Hathaway bought 75 million more Apple shares,</a> adding to its already huge stake at the time of 165.3 million shares.</p><p>In a statement to CNBC then, Apple CEO <strong>Tim Cook</strong> said the company is "thrilled to have Warren and Berkshire Hathaway as a major investor." Cook added, "On a personal level, I've always greatly admired Warren and have always been grateful for his insight and advice."</p><p><img src="https://fm-static.cnbc.com/awsmedia/chart/2019/12/31/IBM-apple_chart.1577791660795.jpg" class="inlineChart"></p><h4>Berkshire buys small Apple stake in 2016, then goes big</h4><p>Berkshire Hathaway, through one of Buffett's lieutenants, bought its <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2016/05/16/buffetts-berkshire-hathaway-takes-new-stake-in-apple.html?&amp;doc=106315407">first 10 million Apple shares in May 2016.</a> In February 2017, Buffett, who didn't even personally own an iPhone, told CNBC that Berkshire <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2017/02/27/billionaire-warren-buffett-more-than-doubled-his-holdings-in-apple-in-2017.html?&amp;doc=106315407">added almost 76 million Apple shares</a> to its holdings the prior month. "Apple strikes me as having quite a sticky product, and an enormously useful product to people that use it," Buffett told CNBC.</p><p>Buffett also said in February 2017 that he was <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2017/05/04/warren-buffett-has-revalued-ibm-downward-cites-big-strong-competitors.html?&amp;doc=106315407">more certain about Apple's future than that of IBM.</a> Five months later, he said he lost confidence in IBM. "When it got above $180 we actually sold a reasonable amount of stock," he said at the time. About a year later, he was out of IBM completely.</p><a autoplay_flag="false" href="https://www.cnbc.com/video/2017/05/05/warren-buffett-sells-off-a-third-of-his-stake-in-ibm.html?&amp;doc=106315407"></a><h4>Apple is Berkshire's most valuable holding at $72 billion</h4><p>As of Sept. 30, 2019, Berkshire Hathaway held nearly 249 million shares of Apple. Based on Apple's $291.52 closing share price Monday, Berkshire's Apple stake was worth more than $72 billion. Apple stock hit an all-time, intraday high of $293.97 on Friday. On a closing basis in 2019, Apple is up a stunning 85% as of Monday, far and away the best performing component this year of the 30 stocks that comprise the <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/.DJI&amp;&amp;doc=106315407">Dow Jones Industrial Average</a>.</p><p>Berkshire owns all or parts of over 60 companies including Geico auto insurance, Nebraska Furniture Mart, running-shoe maker Brooks and NetJets. It also buys stocks in blue chip companies and tends to hold them over a number of years.</p><p>After Apple, rounding out Berkshire's top five holdings by market value are <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/BAC&amp;&amp;doc=106315407">Bank of America</a>, <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/KO&amp;&amp;doc=106315407">Coca-Cola</a>, <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/WFC&amp;&amp;doc=106315407">Wells Fargo</a> and <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/AXP&amp;&amp;doc=106315407">American Express</a>. Berkshire also has major stakes in dozens of other household names such as <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/KHC&amp;&amp;doc=106315407">Kraft Heinz</a>, <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/JPM&amp;&amp;doc=106315407">J.P. Morgan Chase</a>, <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/GM&amp;&amp;doc=106315407">General Motors</a> and <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/AMZN&amp;&amp;doc=106315407">Amazon</a>.</p><p>Buffett said in the past that he admired what <strong>Jeff Bezos</strong> did with Amazon but was too late to the buy stock. Earlier this year, however, one of his lieutenants<a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2019/08/14/warren-buffetts-berkshire-hathaway-raises-amazon-stake-by-11percent.html?&amp;doc=106315407"> started buying Amazon,</a> building up a stake worth nearly $1 billion based on Amazon's $1,846.89 close on Monday. (Buffett's Berkshire, Bezos' Amazon, and J.P. Morgan, run by <strong>Jamie Dimon,</strong> all work together in a <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2019/03/06/amazon-jp-morgan-berkshire-hathaway-health-care-venture-named-haven.html?&amp;doc=106315407">joint venture called Haven</a>, which aims to figure out how to reduce health-care costs.)</p><h4>How Buffett become one of the richest in the world</h4><p>Buffett, who bought his first stock at age 11, has become one of the most successful and celebrated investors of all time and earned the nickname The Oracle of Omaha. He built Omaha, Nebraska-based Berkshire Hathaway into an investment powerhouse. Berkshire's annual shareholders meeting, which has been called the Woodstock of Capitalism, draws tens of thousands of the Buffett-faithful to Omaha every year.</p><p>As of Monday, according to Forbes, Buffett is the third richest person in the world, with a net worth of nearly $90 billion. He has promised to give nearly all of his fortune away to charity. <a href="https://givingpledge.org/About.aspx">He started The Giving Pledge</a> with Bill and Melinda Gates in 2010, which gets other billionaires to commit to giving a majority their money away to "address some of society's most pressing problems." More than 200 of the world's wealthiest people have made the pledge.</p><p>While a wildly successful investor and a generous philanthropist, Buffett is also known for his frugality. He likes eating at <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/MCD&amp;&amp;doc=106315407">McDonald's</a> and drinking Coke. He still lives in the same house he bought in 1958.</p><p><em><strong>With Berkshire's 2019 annual meeting in the books, users can revisit the highlights in CNBC's </strong></em><a href="https://cnb.cx/2A5I00o"><em><strong>Warren Buffett Archive,</strong></em></a><em><strong> which houses searchable video from 25 full annual meetings, going back to 1994, synchronized to 2,600 pages of transcripts. The Warren Buffett Archive also includes 500 shorter-form videos arranged by topic, CNBC interviews, a Buffett Timeline and a Berkshire Portfolio Tracker.</strong></em></p> ]]>
</content:encoded>
<media:keywords>Philanthropy</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Wealth</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Melinda Gates</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Bill Gates</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Financials</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Omaha</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Markets</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Technology</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Software</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Internet</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Warren Buffett</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>International Business Machines Corp</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Berkshire Hathaway Inc</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Apple Inc</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Becky Quick</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Tim Cook</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Bank of America Corp</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Coca-Cola Co</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Wells Fargo & Co</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Kraft Heinz Co</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>American Express Co</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>JPMorgan Chase & Co</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>General Motors Co</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>McDonald's Corp</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Dow Jones Industrial Average</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Amazon.com Inc</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Jeff Bezos</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Jamie Dimon</media:keywords>
<author>Matthew J. Belvedere</author>
<guid>106315407</guid>
<metadata:contentType>Story</metadata:contentType>
<metadata:country>US</metadata:country>
<metadata:provider>NBCU</metadata:provider>
<metadata:channel>CNBC</metadata:channel>
<media:content url="http://pdl.iphone.cnbc.com//VCPS/Y2018/M05D11/7000018989/2018-CNBC-0503-CLIP-3_MBR_4500.mp4" medium="video" height="1000" width="1910">
<media:description>Warren Buffett tells Becky Quick that Berkshire sold the last of its IBM shares during the first quarter of 2018.</media:description>
<media:title>I think we have zero IBM shares</media:title>
<media:thumbnail width="1910" height="1000" url="https://image.cnbcfm.com/api/v1/image/105203817-2018-CNBC-0503-CLIP-3.jpg?v=1529478230&w=1910&h=1000"/>
</media:content>
<media:content url="http://pdl.iphone.cnbc.com/VCPS/Y2017/M05D05/3000616127/6ED3-SB-BuffetIBM-050517_MBR_4500.mp4" medium="video" height="1000" width="1910">
<media:description>Squawk Box's Becky Quick talks to Berkshire Hathaway's Warren Buffett about his decision to sell a third of his stake in IBM.</media:description>
<media:title>Warren Buffett sells off a third of his stake in IBM</media:title>
<media:thumbnail width="1910" height="1000" url="https://image.cnbcfm.com/api/v1/image/104439889-EA_Warren_Buffett.jpg?v=1529474968&w=1910&h=1000"/>
</media:content>
<media:content url="http://pdl.iphone.cnbc.com//VCPS/Y2018/M05D04/7000017531/6ED2-SB-050418-BerkBought_MBR_4500.mp4" medium="video" height="1000" width="1910">
<media:description>"Squawk Box's" Becky Quick talks with Warren Buffett about Berkshire Hathaway's big investment in Apple.</media:description>
<media:title>Berkshire Hathaway bought 75 million shares of Apple in Q1</media:title>
<media:thumbnail width="1910" height="1000" url="https://image.cnbcfm.com/api/v1/image/105184920-849890542.jpg?v=1529478174&w=1910&h=1000"/>
</media:content>
<title>This decade saw Warren Buffett finally turn his back on IBM and jump big time into Apple</title>
<description>One of Warren Buffett's biggest investment mistakes, IBM, played out over an agonizing seven-year stretch this decade. But in the end, he rotated into Apple for a lucrative ride.</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 14:23:02 GMT</pubDate>
<metadata:updatedDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 22:46:34 GMT</metadata:updatedDate>
<category>Investing</category>
</item>
<item>
<media:thumbnail url="https://image.cnbcfm.com/api/v1/image/106317038-3ed1-fm-123119-c.jpg?v=1577831621"/>
<link>https://www.cnbc.com/video/2019/12/31/feds-doing-something-it-hasnt-since-y2k-and-it-could-spark-sell-off.html</link>
<media:keywords>U.S. 10 Year Treasury</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Jerome Powell</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Federal Reserve System</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>NASDAQ 100 Index</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Dow Jones Industrial Average</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>S&P 500 Index</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>iShares Russell 2000 ETF</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>World economy</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Stock markets</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Wall Street</media:keywords>
<author>Melissa Lee</author>
<guid>106317019</guid>
<media:network>US</media:network>
<media:duration>295</media:duration>
<metadata:contentType>Video</metadata:contentType>
<media:show>Fast Money</media:show>
<metadata:country>US</metadata:country>
<metadata:provider>NBCU</metadata:provider>
<metadata:channel>CNBC</metadata:channel>
<title>Fed's doing something it hasn't since Y2K and it could spark sell-off, says Jim Bianco</title>
<description>Jim Bianco, Bianco Research, on Fed policy in 2019 and where it goes from here. With CNBC's Morgan Brennan and the Fast Money traders, Steve Grasso, Karen Finerman, Dan Nathan and Guy Adami.</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 22:35:13 GMT</pubDate>
<metadata:updatedDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 22:35:13 GMT</metadata:updatedDate>
<category>Fast Money</category>
<media:content medium="video" bitrate="4500" url="http://pdl.iphone.cnbc.com//VCPS/Y2019/M12D31/7000115760/1577831577620-3ED1-FM-123119-C_MBR_4500.mp4"/>
</item>
<item>
<media:thumbnail url="https://image.cnbcfm.com/api/v1/image/106317030-3ed4-req-123119marketsnow.jpg?v=1577831138"/>
<link>https://www.cnbc.com/video/2019/12/31/cnbc-markets-now-december-31-2019.html</link>
<media:keywords>ALEXA VIDEOS</media:keywords>
<guid>106317029</guid>
<media:network>US</media:network>
<media:duration>73</media:duration>
<metadata:contentType>Video</metadata:contentType>
<media:show>CNBC Markets Now</media:show>
<metadata:country>US</metadata:country>
<metadata:provider>NBCU</metadata:provider>
<metadata:channel>CNBC</metadata:channel>
<title>CNBC Markets Now: December 31, 2019</title>
<description>CNBC Markets Now provides a look at the day's market moves with commentary and analysis from Michael Santoli, CNBC Senior Markets Commentator.</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 22:31:55 GMT</pubDate>
<metadata:updatedDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 22:32:30 GMT</metadata:updatedDate>
<category>CNBC Markets Now</category>
<media:content medium="video" bitrate="4500" url="http://pdl.iphone.cnbc.com//VCPS/Y2019/M12D31/7000115757/1577831115497-3ED4-REQ-123119MarketsNOW-C_MBR_4500.mp4"/>
</item>
<item>
<media:thumbnail url="https://image.cnbcfm.com/api/v1/image/106317031-3ed1-fm-123119-b.jpg?v=1577831147"/>
<link>https://www.cnbc.com/video/2019/12/31/whats-ahead-for-the-tech-sector.html</link>
<media:keywords>Netflix Inc</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Microsoft Corp</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Apple Inc</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Alphabet Class A</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Amazon.com Inc</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Meta Platforms Inc</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Technology Select Sector SPDR Fund</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>NASDAQ 100 Index</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Dow Jones Industrial Average</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>S&P 500 Index</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>iShares Russell 2000 ETF</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>World economy</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Stock markets</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Wall Street</media:keywords>
<author>Melissa Lee</author>
<guid>106317017</guid>
<media:network>US</media:network>
<media:duration>336</media:duration>
<metadata:contentType>Video</metadata:contentType>
<media:show>Fast Money</media:show>
<metadata:country>US</metadata:country>
<metadata:provider>NBCU</metadata:provider>
<metadata:channel>CNBC</metadata:channel>
<title>What's ahead for the tech sector?</title>
<description>Tech ended year as market's best-performing sector. With CNBC's Morgan Brennan and the Fast Money traders, Steve Grasso, Karen Finerman, Dan Nathan and Guy Adami.</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 22:27:35 GMT</pubDate>
<metadata:updatedDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 22:27:35 GMT</metadata:updatedDate>
<category>Fast Money</category>
<media:content medium="video" bitrate="4500" url="http://pdl.iphone.cnbc.com//VCPS/Y2019/M12D31/7000115758/1577831104759-3ED1-FM-123119-B_MBR_4500.mp4"/>
</item>
<item>
<media:thumbnail url="https://image.cnbcfm.com/api/v1/image/101822530-94843576.jpg?v=1747327172"/>
<link>https://www.cnbc.com/video/2019/12/31/google-veterans-on-brain-drain-company-has-become-unrecognizable.html</link>
<media:keywords>Alphabet Class A</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Technology</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Business</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Markets</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Stock markets</media:keywords>
<guid>106316948</guid>
<media:network>US</media:network>
<media:duration>162</media:duration>
<metadata:contentType>Video</metadata:contentType>
<media:show>Closing Bell</media:show>
<metadata:country>US</metadata:country>
<metadata:provider>NBCU</metadata:provider>
<metadata:channel>CNBC</metadata:channel>
<title>Google veterans on brain drain: Company has become 'unrecognizable'</title>
<description>CNBC's Jennifer Elias reports on Google veterans' complaints that the company has turned into the opposite of what the founders said they hoped it would be.</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 22:18:50 GMT</pubDate>
<metadata:updatedDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 22:20:52 GMT</metadata:updatedDate>
<category>Closing Bell</category>
<media:content medium="video" bitrate="4500" url="http://pdl.iphone.cnbc.com//VCPS/Y2019/M12D31/7000115748/1577829544545-191231CBgooglechatelias_MBR_4500.mp4"/>
</item>
<item>
<media:thumbnail url="https://image.cnbcfm.com/api/v1/image/106317023-3ed1-req-techcheckpm-123119.jpg?v=1577830419"/>
<link>https://www.cnbc.com/video/2019/12/31/cnbc-tech-check-evening-edition-december-31-2019.html</link>
<media:keywords>ALEXA VIDEOS</media:keywords>
<guid>106317021</guid>
<media:network>US</media:network>
<media:duration>91</media:duration>
<metadata:contentType>Video</metadata:contentType>
<media:show>CNBC Tech Check</media:show>
<metadata:country>US</metadata:country>
<metadata:provider>NBCU</metadata:provider>
<metadata:channel>CNBC</metadata:channel>
<title>CNBC Tech Check Evening Edition: December 31, 2019</title>
<description>CNBC's Tech Check brings you the latest in tech news from CNBC's 1 Market in the heart of San Francisco.</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 22:14:51 GMT</pubDate>
<metadata:updatedDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 22:14:51 GMT</metadata:updatedDate>
<category>CNBC Tech Check</category>
<media:content medium="video" bitrate="4500" url="http://pdl.iphone.cnbc.com//VCPS/Y2019/M12D31/7000115751/1577830362107-3ED1-REQ-TechCheckPM-123119_MBR_4500.mp4"/>
</item>
<item>
<media:thumbnail url="https://image.cnbcfm.com/api/v1/image/106316994-191231cbhedgefund2020playbook.jpg?v=1577828630"/>
<link>https://www.cnbc.com/video/2019/12/31/heres-the-2020-hedge-fund-playbook.html</link>
<media:keywords>Hedge Funds</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Business</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Wall Street</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Markets</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Stock markets</media:keywords>
<guid>106316947</guid>
<media:network>US</media:network>
<media:duration>89</media:duration>
<metadata:contentType>Video</metadata:contentType>
<media:show>Closing Bell</media:show>
<metadata:country>US</metadata:country>
<metadata:provider>NBCU</metadata:provider>
<metadata:channel>CNBC</metadata:channel>
<title>Here's the 2020 hedge fund playbook</title>
<description>CNBC's Leslie Picker reports on the 2020 playbook for hedge funds on "Closing Bell."</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 21:59:15 GMT</pubDate>
<metadata:updatedDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 21:59:15 GMT</metadata:updatedDate>
<category>Closing Bell</category>
<media:content medium="video" bitrate="4500" url="http://pdl.iphone.cnbc.com//VCPS/Y2019/M12D31/7000115747/1577828775991-191231CBhedgefund2020playbook_MBR_4500.mp4"/>
</item>
<item>
<media:thumbnail url="https://image.cnbcfm.com/api/v1/image/106316991-191231cbkniffen.jpg?v=1577828294"/>
<link>https://www.cnbc.com/video/2019/12/31/jan-kniffen-gives-his-2020-retail-forecast.html</link>
<media:keywords>Wall Street</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Markets</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Stock markets</media:keywords>
<guid>106316946</guid>
<media:network>US</media:network>
<media:duration>151</media:duration>
<metadata:contentType>Video</metadata:contentType>
<media:show>Closing Bell</media:show>
<metadata:country>US</metadata:country>
<metadata:provider>NBCU</metadata:provider>
<metadata:channel>CNBC</metadata:channel>
<title>Jan Kniffen gives his 2020 retail forecast</title>
<description>Jan Kniffen, CEO at J Rogers Kniffen WWE, wraps up retail in 2019 and gives his outlook for 2020 on "Closing Bell."</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 21:58:17 GMT</pubDate>
<metadata:updatedDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 21:58:17 GMT</metadata:updatedDate>
<category>Closing Bell</category>
<media:content medium="video" bitrate="4500" url="http://pdl.iphone.cnbc.com//VCPS/Y2019/M12D31/7000115744/1577828564451-191231CBkniffen_MBR_4500.mp4"/>
</item>
<item>
<media:thumbnail url="https://image.cnbcfm.com/api/v1/image/106316990-191231cbbiggestsectormovers.jpg?v=1577828288"/>
<link>https://www.cnbc.com/video/2019/12/31/here-are-2019s-biggest-sector-movers.html</link>
<media:keywords>Restaurants</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Business</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Wall Street</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Markets</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Stock markets</media:keywords>
<guid>106316944</guid>
<media:network>US</media:network>
<media:duration>136</media:duration>
<metadata:contentType>Video</metadata:contentType>
<media:show>Closing Bell</media:show>
<metadata:country>US</metadata:country>
<metadata:provider>NBCU</metadata:provider>
<metadata:channel>CNBC</metadata:channel>
<title>Here are 2019's biggest sector movers</title>
<description>CNBC's Meg Tirrell, Kate Rogers and Courtney Reagan explain the biggest movers in biotech, restaurants and retail on "Closing Bell."</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 21:56:48 GMT</pubDate>
<metadata:updatedDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 21:57:07 GMT</metadata:updatedDate>
<category>Closing Bell</category>
<media:content medium="video" bitrate="4500" url="http://pdl.iphone.cnbc.com//VCPS/Y2019/M12D31/7000115743/1577828328990-191231CBbiggestsectormovers_MBR_4500.mp4"/>
</item>
<item>
<media:thumbnail url="https://image.cnbcfm.com/api/v1/image/106313893-1577485339680gettyimages-471530340.jpeg?v=1577485561"/>
<link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/12/31/microsoft-wraps-up-its-best-year-since-2009.html</link>
<content:encoded>
<![CDATA[ <ul> <li>Satya Nadella has now been Microsoft's CEO for almost six years.</li> <li>This year the company won a major government contract and saw companies adopting its latest technology.</li></ul><img src="https://image.cnbcfm.com/api/v1/image/106313893-1577485339680gettyimages-471530340.jpeg?v=1577485561&amp;w=1910&amp;h=1000" data-licensor-name="David Paul Morris | Getty Images | Bloomberg" width="1910" alt="Satya Nadella, chief executive officer of Microsoft Corp., speaks during a keynote session at the Microsoft Developers Build Conference in San Francisco, California, U.S., on Wednesday, April 29, 2015." id="106313893" height="1000"></img><p><a href="https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/MSFT&amp;&amp;doc=106312807">Microsoft</a> just finished its best year in a decade — at least when it comes to stock price performance.</p><p>Shares ended trading at $157.70 on Tuesday, extending its gains for 2019 to 55.3%, making this the stock's best year since 2009, when it rose 56.8%. Microsoft shares were up 417% higher for the decade — not quite the 9,562% gain of the 1990s, which saw the launch of Windows 95, but easily overshadowing the 2000s, when the company emerged from its major antitrust case.</p><p>The Dow Jones Industrial Average, Nasdaq Composite and S&amp;P 500 also jumped in the 2010s amid <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2019/07/02/this-is-now-the-longest-us-economic-expansion-in-history.html?&amp;doc=106312807">the longest economic expansion in U.S. history</a>. The Nasdaq outperformed the other two indices with 295% growth. Microsoft didn't grow as much as some other S&amp;P 500 constituents like <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/AMZN&amp;&amp;doc=106312807">Amazon</a>, <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/AVGO&amp;&amp;doc=106312807">Broadcom</a> and <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/NFLX&amp;&amp;doc=106312807">Netflix</a>. Then again, Microsoft is worth more than all three of those companies, with a $1.20 trillion market capitalization. Only Apple and Saudi Aramco are worth more.</p><a autoplay_flag="false" href="https://www.cnbc.com/video/2019/12/30/microsoft-vs-amazonthe-ongoing-battle-over-jedi.html?&amp;doc=106312807"></a><p>This year Microsoft was a major contributor to the S&amp;P 500's rise, second only to <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/AAPL&amp;&amp;doc=106312807">Apple</a>. It contributed about 7% of the index's gains in 2019.</p><p>The stock outcome reflects Microsoft's evolution. In the past 10 years the company underwent leadership changes and strategy shifts and pulled off <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2019/12/27/linkedin-ceo-jeff-weiner-is-ok-with-microsofts-hands-off-approach.html?&amp;doc=106312807">its biggest acquisition yet</a>. This year Microsoft has built on those transitions, and investors are expecting more growth as companies upgrade to the company's newest technology.</p><p>And while regulators have looked afresh at Alphabet, Amazon, Apple and Facebook in recent months, Microsoft has largely escaped their scrutiny this time around.</p><p>Here are some of the highlights of 2019 that could set up Microsoft for future gains in the months and years ahead:</p><ul> <li><strong>Windows 7 end of support. </strong>Microsoft will stop releasing security patches for Windows 7, which was released in 2009, on January 14, 2020. This event has been leading companies to shell out money so that employees can be on the latest platform, Windows 10. In <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2019/10/23/microsoft-msft-earnings-q1-2020.html?&amp;doc=106312807">the first quarter of Microsoft's 2020 fiscal year</a>, Windows OEM Pro revenue grew 19%, the fastest growth since 2014. Windows OEM Pro reflects sales of Windows licenses for commercial PCs, and it represents 46% of Microsoft's total Windows revenue, Bernstein Research analysts Mark Moerdler and Firoz Valliji estimated a note distributed to clients in November. The analysts have the equivalent of a buy rating on Microsoft stock.</li> <li><strong>Server product updates.</strong> The SQL Server 2008 database software reached end of support in July, and the Windows Server 2008 and Windows Server 2008 R2 operating systems will hit that point on January 14, 2020. Organizations have started moving to newer products, and that has helped boost Microsoft's Server products and cloud services revenue. The category grew by 30% in the first quarter of Microsoft's 2020 fiscal year, and that's saying something, because it's the biggest major product or service in terms of revenue. Server products and cloud services also includes the Azure public cloud.</li> <li><strong>Government business. </strong>Perhaps the best news for Microsoft this year was scoring the Joint Enterprise Defense Infrastructure, or JEDI, contract to supply Azure cloud services to the Defense Department, a deal that could be worth up to $10 billion. <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/AMZN&amp;&amp;doc=106312807">Amazon</a> Web Services, the top cloud infrastructure provider and the vendor that some people expected to win the contract, is <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2019/12/09/amazon-blames-trump-for-losing-jedi-cloud-contract.html?&amp;doc=106312807">protesting the award</a>, but for now Microsoft is the recipient of one of the most prominent government information-technology contracts in recent memory. Should Microsoft hold onto it, a cloud-snowball effect could take hold, and the win could attract additional business.</li> <li><strong>Console wars, round four.</strong> Gaming might not be the first thing you think of when you think of Microsoft, but it gives the company 9% of its revenue. The company isn't about to abandon the market. Even as it's been readying a game streaming service, Microsoft is planning the launch of its fourth-generation console, the black refrigerator-shaped Xbox Series X, in the 2020 holiday season. In the 2010s Xbox One consoles never managed to exceed 32% of total console shipments and were always outsold by <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/6758.T-JP&amp;&amp;doc=106312807">Sony's</a> PlayStation 4, according to figures compiled by Lewis Ward, a research director at industry analysis firm IDC. Now the company is hungry. "We like leading in power and performance, and I feel like we're going to be there again," Microsoft's executive vice president of gaming, Phil Spencer, recently told <a href="https://www.gamespot.com/articles/xbox-series-x-specs-twice-as-powerful-as-xbox-one-/1100-6472198/">GameSpot</a>.</li></ul><img src="https://image.cnbcfm.com/api/v1/image/106294353-1576218158943xboxseriesxhandout.jpg?v=1576218199&amp;w=1910&amp;h=1000" data-licensor-name="Microsoft" width="1910" alt="Microsoft's next-generation Xbox Series X console." id="106294353" height="1000"></img><p>Microsoft was the largest holding in investment bank William Blair's Large Cap Growth Fund at the end of the third quarter, at over 9%. The 20-year-old fund bought Microsoft stock after Nadella took over based on the company's potential in areas like cloud and artificial intelligence, Jim Golan, a portfolio manager of the fund, told CNBC in an interview in November.</p><p>"We've been very pleased with that investment," Golan said. "I think just [Nadella] changing the mindset and refocusing the company on key core growth areas has been really instrumental in terms of driving the performance that we've seen over the past several years."</p><p>The adoption of cloud services will be a major driver for Microsoft in the future, and the company should be able to expand its margins as Azure gains scale, he said.</p><p><strong>WATCH:</strong> <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/video/2019/10/24/nadella-has-made-cloud-a-massive-part-of-microsoft-fund-manager.html?&amp;doc=106312807">Nadella has made cloud a 'massive part' of Microsoft: Fund manager</a></p><a autoplay_flag="false" href="https://www.cnbc.com/video/2019/10/24/nadella-has-made-cloud-a-massive-part-of-microsoft-fund-manager.html?&amp;doc=106312807"></a><p><a href="https://bit.ly/1UqI26M"><em><strong>Follow @CNBCtech on Twitter for the latest tech industry news.</strong></em></a></p> ]]>
</content:encoded>
<media:keywords>Enterprise</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Breaking News: Technology</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Technology</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Business</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Microsoft Corp</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Apple Inc</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Amazon.com Inc</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Broadcom Inc</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Netflix Inc</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Sony Corp</media:keywords>
<author>Jordan Novet</author>
<guid>106312807</guid>
<metadata:contentType>Story</metadata:contentType>
<metadata:country>US</metadata:country>
<metadata:provider>NBCU</metadata:provider>
<metadata:channel>CNBC</metadata:channel>
<media:content url="http://pdl.iphone.cnbc.com//VCPS/Y2019/M10D24/7000105130/5ED3-SBEU-102419-AnthonyGinsberg_MBR_4500.mp4" medium="video" height="1000" width="1910">
<media:description>Anthony Ginsberg, managing director at GinsGlobal Index Funds, discusses the race for dominance in cloud technology.</media:description>
<media:title>Nadella has made cloud a 'massive part' of Microsoft: Fund manager</media:title>
<media:thumbnail width="1910" height="1000" url="https://image.cnbcfm.com/api/v1/image/106200663-15719120395ED3-SBEU-102419-AnthonyGinsberg.jpg?v=1571912039&w=1910&h=1000"/>
</media:content>
<media:content url="http://pdl.iphone.cnbc.com//VCPS/Y2019/M12D30/7000115514/1577729694696-MSFTvsAMZN_MBR_4500.mp4" medium="video" height="1000" width="1910">
<media:description>CNBC's Josh Lipton reports on the battle between to tech giants over a massive cloud-computing contract with the Pentagon.</media:description>
<media:title>Microsoft vs. Amazon—The ongoing battle over Jedi</media:title>
<media:thumbnail width="1910" height="1000" url="https://image.cnbcfm.com/api/v1/image/106315417-msftvsamzn.jpg?v=1577729653&w=1910&h=1000"/>
</media:content>
<title>Microsoft wraps up its best year since 2009</title>
<description>Microsoft can grow further in the coming years with Windows 10, the Azure cloud, the next Xbox console and other products.</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 21:11:03 GMT</pubDate>
<metadata:updatedDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 21:51:11 GMT</metadata:updatedDate>
<category>Technology</category>
</item>
<item>
<media:thumbnail url="https://image.cnbcfm.com/api/v1/image/106316998-3ed4-req-123119marketclose.jpg?v=1577828719"/>
<link>https://www.cnbc.com/video/2019/12/31/post-market-wrap-december-31-2019.html</link>
<media:keywords>ALEXA VIDEOS</media:keywords>
<guid>106316995</guid>
<media:network>US</media:network>
<media:duration>89</media:duration>
<metadata:contentType>Video</metadata:contentType>
<media:show>CNBC News Briefing</media:show>
<metadata:country>US</metadata:country>
<metadata:provider>NBCU</metadata:provider>
<metadata:channel>CNBC</metadata:channel>
<title>Post-Market Wrap: December 31, 2019</title>
<description>CNBC brings you fast, accurate, and actionable business news and market updates.</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 21:48:29 GMT</pubDate>
<metadata:updatedDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 21:48:29 GMT</metadata:updatedDate>
<category>CNBC News Briefing</category>
<media:content medium="video" bitrate="4500" url="http://pdl.iphone.cnbc.com//VCPS/Y2019/M12D31/7000115746/1577828698849-3ED4-REQ-123119MarketClose_MBR_4500.mp4"/>
</item>
<item>
<media:thumbnail url="https://image.cnbcfm.com/api/v1/image/104424509-GettyImages-487392310.jpg?v=1741716253"/>
<link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/12/31/apple-pe-ratio-is-at-historic-high-following-an-explosive-year.html</link>
<content:encoded>
<![CDATA[ <ul> <li>One of the more unique aspects of Apple stock has been the company's historically low price-to-earnings, or P/E, ratio compared with its megacap tech peers.</li> <li>The P/E ratio has long been a key metric used on Wall Street to determine whether a stock is fairly valued.</li> <li>Apple's P/E ratio steadily climbed this year alongside its stock price.</li></ul><img src="https://image.cnbcfm.com/api/v1/image/104424509-GettyImages-487392310.jpg?v=1741716253&amp;w=1910&amp;h=1000" data-licensor-name="Getty Images" width="1910" alt="Tim Cook, CEO of Apple Inc." id="104424509" height="1000"></img><p><a href="https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/AAPL&amp;&amp;doc=106315119">Apple</a> stock closed out a year of explosive growth on Tuesday, and another key metric reached a historic high, too.</p><p>Apple's trailing price-to-earnings, or P/E, ratio steadily climbed this year alongside its stock price. Apple began the year with a trailing P/E ratio just over 13, according to FactSet, below its five-year average of 16.2, before finishing 2019 at 24.7, its highest point since 2010.</p><a autoplay_flag="false" href="https://www.cnbc.com/video/2019/12/31/apple-is-the-best-play-for-investors-in-the-next-year-gene-munster.html?&amp;doc=106315119"></a><p>The trailing P/E ratio is the price per share of a stock divided by earnings per share over the last 12 months. Investors often use it as a shorthand metric to determine how expensive a stock is, although it's not perfect, as it does not account for cash or debt and is based on past performance rather than future expectations.</p><p>The company's forward-looking P/E, which measures price-per-share divided by expected earnings over the next 12 months, is 21.8, which is also historically expensive. An increase in a company's P/E ratio could mean that investors expect earnings growth in the future, so they're willing to pay more now. However, it could also be a warning sign that the stock is overvalued.</p><img src="https://image.cnbcfm.com/api/v1/image/106316698-157781016895420191231_apple_pe_ratio_2019.png?v=1577810234&amp;w=1910&amp;h=1000" data-licensor-name="" width="1910" alt="" id="106316698" height="1000"></img><p>Apple has typically had a low P/E ratio compared with its megacap tech peers.</p><p>When Apple's P/E was around 10 in 2016, venture capitalist Marc Andressen <a href="https://fortune.com/2016/02/07/apple-steel-mill-andreessen/">said in a tweet</a>, since deleted, that Apple stock "trades like a steel mill on its way out of business."</p><p>While the current figure is unusually high for Apple, it's still below the average for the S&amp;P 500 information technology index, which consists of 70 companies, but excludes internet companies including <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/META&amp;&amp;doc=106315119">Facebook</a>, <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/AMZN&amp;&amp;doc=106315119">Amazon</a>, <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/NFLX&amp;&amp;doc=106315119">Netflix</a> and <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/GOOGL&amp;&amp;doc=106315119">Alphabet</a>. The average P/E ratio in that index is now 26, up from 20 at the start of the year, according to FactSet.</p><p>A number of factors have driven Apple's P/E ratio up this year, Deutsche Bank analyst Jeriel Ong said, including an overall market drift and bearish expectations on Apple earlier this year. Investors previously modeled iPhones as a perpetually declining business, Ong said, but sentiment has improved and he now expects year-over-year growth.</p><a autoplay_flag="false" href="https://www.cnbc.com/video/2019/12/30/apple-is-overpriced-by-100-a-share-tech-investor-paul-meeks-warns.html?&amp;doc=106315119"></a><p>"Not only did near-term iPhone 11 expectations improve, investors began to look forward to the 5G 2020 iPhone cycle, which is expected to be a supercycle," he said, adding that Apple's wearable devices have performed well, too.</p><p>"AAPL began to trade at a discount to the S&amp;P 500 back in 2012 with the P/E multiple compressing to 10-12x at that point (S&amp;P500 was 12-13x), so the idea that it should now trade at a 3-4x premium to the S&amp;P500 (at 18.5x) is interesting indeed," he said.</p><p>Compared with the other megacap tech stocks, Apple's P/E ratio still ranks among the lowest. <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/AMZN&amp;&amp;doc=106315119">Amazon</a> is finishing the year with a P/E of 81.8, <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/META&amp;&amp;doc=106315119">Facebook</a>'s is 32.8, <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/MSFT&amp;&amp;doc=106315119">Microsoft</a>'s is 29.7, and Google-parent <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/GOOGL&amp;&amp;doc=106315119">Alphabet</a>'s is 28.7.</p><a autoplay_flag="false" href="https://www.cnbc.com/video/2018/02/22/cnbc-explains-price-earnings-ratio.html?&amp;doc=106315119"></a><p></p> ]]>
</content:encoded>
<media:keywords>Apple Inc</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Investment strategy</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Markets</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Technology</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Microsoft Corp</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Amazon.com Inc</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Alphabet Class A</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Netflix Inc</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Facebook</media:keywords>
<author>Will Feuer</author>
<guid>106315119</guid>
<metadata:contentType>Story</metadata:contentType>
<metadata:country>US</metadata:country>
<metadata:provider>NBCU</metadata:provider>
<metadata:channel>CNBC</metadata:channel>
<media:content url="http://pdl.iphone.cnbc.com//VCPS/Y2018/M02D22/7000001388/5ED1-REQ-PeRatio-022218_MBR_4500.mp4" medium="video" height="1000" width="1910">
<media:description>This is one popular way to figure out if a stock is cheap or not.</media:description>
<media:title>CNBC Explains: Price-Earnings ratio</media:title>
<media:thumbnail width="1910" height="1000" url="https://image.cnbcfm.com/api/v1/image/105023382-PERatioV1.00_00_09_05.Still001.jpg?v=1529477567&w=1910&h=1000"/>
</media:content>
<media:content url="http://pdl.iphone.cnbc.com//VCPS/Y2019/M12D31/7000115695/1577809028842-191231SAmunster_MBR_4500.mp4" medium="video" height="1000" width="1910">
<media:description>Gene Munster, Loup Ventures, and John Freeman, CFRA, join 'Squawk Alley' to discuss tech's last decade and what the future holds for the industry.</media:description>
<media:title>Apple is the best play for investors in the next year: Gene Munster</media:title>
<media:thumbnail width="1910" height="1000" url="https://image.cnbcfm.com/api/v1/image/106295923-1576268576211gettyimages-1167255506.jpeg?v=1576268611&w=1910&h=1000"/>
</media:content>
<media:content url="http://pdl.iphone.cnbc.com//VCPS/Y2019/M12D30/7000115603/2ED2-REQ-TradingNation-LONG-123019_MBR_4500.mp4" medium="video" height="1000" width="1910">
<media:description>The money manager known for running the world's largest technology fund during the dot-com boom believes Apple's stock price does not accurately reflect fundamentals.</media:description>
<media:title>Apple is 'overpriced' by $100 a share, tech investor Paul Meeks warns</media:title>
<media:thumbnail width="1910" height="1000" url="https://image.cnbcfm.com/api/v1/image/106315892-15777478672ED2-REQ-TradingNation-LONG-123019.jpg?v=1577747866&w=1910&h=1000"/>
</media:content>
<title>After its strongest year in a decade, Apple stock is historically expensive on a price-to-earnings basis</title>
<description>When Apple's P/E was around 10 in 2016, venture capitalist Marc Andressen said in a tweet, since deleted, that Apple stock "trades like a steel mill on its way out of business."</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 17:18:03 GMT</pubDate>
<metadata:updatedDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 21:38:49 GMT</metadata:updatedDate>
<category>Technology</category>
</item>
<item>
<media:thumbnail url="https://image.cnbcfm.com/api/v1/image/101286246-Tool_Whiskey.jpg?v=1387468138"/>
<link>https://www.cnbc.com/video/2019/12/31/heres-how-tariffs-and-taxes-impact-the-bourbon-business.html</link>
<media:keywords>Catch Me Up</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Distillery operation</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>United States</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Import and export prices</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Liquor</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Sanctions and embargoes</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Trade agreements</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Trade</media:keywords>
<guid>106316888</guid>
<media:network>US</media:network>
<media:duration>219</media:duration>
<metadata:contentType>Video</metadata:contentType>
<media:show>Power Lunch</media:show>
<metadata:country>US</metadata:country>
<metadata:provider>NBCU</metadata:provider>
<metadata:channel>CNBC</metadata:channel>
<title>Here's how tariffs and taxes impact the whiskey business</title>
<description>Michter's president Joseph Magliocco joins CNBC's "Power Lunch" team to break down how new tariffs on booze may impact the company and the sector.</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 20:10:26 GMT</pubDate>
<metadata:updatedDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 21:24:29 GMT</metadata:updatedDate>
<category>Power Lunch</category>
<media:content medium="video" bitrate="4500" url="http://pdl.iphone.cnbc.com//VCPS/Y2019/M12D31/7000115735/1577822644692-Michtersmaglioccoonbourbontariffs_MBR_4500.mp4"/>
</item>
<item>
<media:thumbnail url="https://image.cnbcfm.com/api/v1/image/106316963-191231cbmarketsafterbell.jpg?v=1577826274"/>
<link>https://www.cnbc.com/video/2019/12/31/sp-500-and-nasdaq-end-2019-as-best-year-since-2013.html</link>
<media:keywords>Investment strategy</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Economy</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>U.S. Economy</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Business</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Wall Street</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>NASDAQ Composite</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>S&P 500 Index</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Dow Jones Industrial Average</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Markets</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Stock markets</media:keywords>
<guid>106316941</guid>
<media:network>US</media:network>
<media:duration>191</media:duration>
<metadata:contentType>Video</metadata:contentType>
<media:show>Closing Bell</media:show>
<metadata:country>US</metadata:country>
<metadata:provider>NBCU</metadata:provider>
<metadata:channel>CNBC</metadata:channel>
<title>S&P 500 and Nasdaq end 2019 as best year since 2013</title>
<description>Barry Knapp from Ironsides Macroeconomics and Keith Bliss from iQ Capital USA join CNBC's "Closing Bell" to discuss markets after the bell on the last day of 2019.</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 21:21:14 GMT</pubDate>
<metadata:updatedDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 21:21:14 GMT</metadata:updatedDate>
<category>Closing Bell</category>
<media:content medium="video" bitrate="4500" url="http://pdl.iphone.cnbc.com//VCPS/Y2019/M12D31/7000115741/1577826805528-191231CBmarketsafterbell_MBR_4500.mp4"/>
</item>
<item>
<media:thumbnail url="https://image.cnbcfm.com/api/v1/image/106316911-1577822455237gettyimages-1191105987.jpeg?v=1582117132"/>
<link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/12/31/dow-futures-last-trading-day-of-2019.html</link>
<content:encoded>
<![CDATA[ <a autoplay_flag="false" href="https://www.cnbc.com/video/2019/12/31/geopolitical-issues-may-limit-gains-in-2020-says-jp-morgans-david-lebovitz.html?&amp;doc=106316098"></a><p>Stocks rose slightly on Tuesday as Wall Street wrapped up a banner year that saw equities surge to record highs, overcoming concerns about the economy and a trade fight with China.</p><p>The <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/.SPX&amp;&amp;doc=106316098">S&amp;P 500</a>&nbsp;climbed 0.3% to 3,230.78. The&nbsp;<a href="https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/.IXIC&amp;&amp;doc=106316098">Nasdaq Composite</a>&nbsp;also advanced 0.3% and ended the day at 8,972.60. The <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/.DJI&amp;&amp;doc=106316098">Dow Jones Industrial Average</a> closed 76.30 points higher, or 0.3% at 28,538.44. Materials and energy were the best-performing sectors in the S&amp;P 500, rising around 0.7% each. IBM, Cisco Systems and Apple led the Dow higher.&nbsp;</p><p>Tuesday's performance capped off a strong year for stocks. The S&amp;P 500 was up 28.9% for 2019, its biggest one-year gain since 2013, when it rallied 29.6%. The Nasdaq also had its best one-year performance in six years after rallying 35.2% in 2019. The Dow rose 22.3% in 2019, its best annual performance since 2017.</p><img src="https://image.cnbcfm.com/api/v1/image/106315858-157782659923620191231_mkt_close_stock_market_performance_sp500_djia_nasdaq.png?v=1577826720&amp;w=1910&amp;h=1000" data-licensor-name="" width="1910" alt="" id="106315858" height="1000"></img><p>"We climbed a wall of worry, from a growth slowdown and profits flat at best, trade concerns, potential impeachment, and high valuations bothering investors — including myself," said Ned Davis, founder of Ned Davis Research, in a note.</p><p>Stocks surged in 2019 despite the ongoing U.S.-China trade war as the Federal Reserve cut rates three times while consumer sentiment remained high. Trade tensions also declined in the fourth quarter after China and the U.S. agreed to sign a so-called phase one trade deal.</p><p>"That one's in the bank," White House advisor Peter Navarro told CNBC's "<a href="https://www.cnbc.com/squawk-box-live/?&amp;doc=106316098">Squawk Box</a>" on Tuesday, referring to the <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2019/12/31/trump-trade-advisor-navarro-says-phase-one-trade-deal-is-in-the-bank-waiting-on-translation.html?&amp;doc=106316098">phase-one agreement</a>. "We're just waiting for the Chinese translation of the 86-page agreement and I'm trying to figure out whether it's going to be more pages or less in Chinese."</p><p>President Donald Trump later said he will sign the agreement on <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2019/12/31/trump-says-he-will-sign-phase-one-china-trade-deal-jan-15-at-the-white-house.html?&amp;doc=106316098">Jan. 15 at the White House</a>.</p><p><a href="https://twitter.com/realDonaldTrump/status/1212014713808273410">Tweet</a></p><p>"By any objective measure US large cap stocks start 2020 on perilous footing. Valuations are rich. Corporate debt levels are at record highs," said Nicholas Colas, co-founder of DataTrek Research, in a note. "But… we know the Federal Reserve has learned its lesson. It will be quick to ease if necessary and slow – very slow – to raise rates."</p><p><img src="https://fm-static.cnbc.com/awsmedia/chart/2019/12/31/image (12).1577806777375.png" class="inlineChart"></p><p><a href="https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/AAPL&amp;&amp;doc=106316098">Apple</a> and <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/MSFT&amp;&amp;doc=106316098">Microsoft</a> led the way higher for stocks in 2019, rallying 86.2% and 55.3%, respectively. They are the best-performing Dow stocks of the year and accounted for about 15% of the S&amp;P 500's <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2019/12/30/apple-microsoft-contributed-most-to-the-markets-2019-gains.html?&amp;doc=106316098">overall gains for 2019</a>.</p><p>Chipmakers Advanced Micro Devices, Lam Research and KLA Corp. were the best-performing S&amp;P 500 stocks in 2019. AMD and Lam Research both rose more than 100% for the year while KLA surged 99.1%. Retailer Target and fast-casual dining chain Chipotle Mexican Grill also rallied more than 90% this year.</p><p>Tuesday also marked the final trading day of the decade. Over the past 10 years, the S&amp;P 500 has surged more than 188%. The broad index's total return — which includes dividends — tops 255% for the decade.</p><p><em>—CNBC's Silvia Amaro contributed to this report.</em></p> ]]>
</content:encoded>
<media:keywords>Breaking News: Markets</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Pre-markets</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Bitcoin</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Markets</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Stock markets</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Dow Jones Industrial Average</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Do Not Use(use 100271106) - S&P 500 Index </media:keywords>
<media:keywords>NASDAQ Composite</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>SPDR S&P 500 ETF Trust</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>PowerShares QQQ Trust</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>SPDR Dow Jones Industrial Average ETF Trust DUP</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>iShares Core S&P 500 ETF</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>S&P 500 Index</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Apple Inc</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Microsoft Corp</media:keywords>
<author>Fred Imbert</author>
<guid>106316098</guid>
<metadata:contentType>Story</metadata:contentType>
<metadata:country>US</metadata:country>
<metadata:provider>NBCU</metadata:provider>
<metadata:channel>CNBC</metadata:channel>
<media:content url="http://pdl.iphone.cnbc.com//VCPS/Y2019/M12D31/7000115662/3ED2-REQ-123119-MorningReport_MBR_4500.mp4" medium="video" height="1000" width="1910">
<media:description>U.S. stock index futures point to a higher start to the trading day for the last trading day of 2019.</media:description>
<media:title>Futures point to a higher open on the last trading day of 2019</media:title>
<media:thumbnail width="1910" height="1000" url="https://image.cnbcfm.com/api/v1/image/106316425-15777908983ED2-REQ-123119-MorningReport.jpg?v=1577790898&w=1910&h=1000"/>
</media:content>
<media:content url="http://pdl.iphone.cnbc.com//VCPS/Y2019/M12D31/7000115671/1577797778468-191231SBkinahanlebovitzeconomy_MBR_4500.mp4" medium="video" height="1000" width="1910">
<media:description>JJ Kinahan, chief market strategist at TD Ameritrade, and David Lebovitz, global market strategist at JP Morgan Asset Management, join "Squawk Box" to discuss what's ahead for the market in 2020.</media:description>
<media:title>Geopolitical issues may limit gains in 2020, says JP Morgan's David Lebovitz</media:title>
<media:thumbnail width="1910" height="1000" url="https://image.cnbcfm.com/api/v1/image/106316500-191231sbkinahanlebovitzeconomy.jpg?v=1577797715&w=1910&h=1000"/>
</media:content>
<title>Stocks post best annual gain in 6 years with the S&P 500 surging more than 28%</title>
<description>The Nasdaq Composite posted a 35% gain for the year as tech stocks such as Apple and Microsoft boomed.</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 06:38:32 GMT</pubDate>
<metadata:updatedDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 21:17:03 GMT</metadata:updatedDate>
<category>Markets</category>
</item>
<item>
<media:thumbnail url="https://image.cnbcfm.com/api/v1/image/106316965-3ed5-tn-123119-seg1.jpg?v=1577826298"/>
<link>https://www.cnbc.com/video/2019/12/31/delta-and-these-other-stocks-are-flashing-a-bullish-sign-into-2020.html</link>
<media:keywords>HP Inc</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Ralph Lauren Corp</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Conocophillips</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Monster Beverage Corp</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Delta Air Lines Inc</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Investment strategy</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Stock markets</media:keywords>
<guid>106316903</guid>
<media:network>US</media:network>
<media:duration>215</media:duration>
<metadata:contentType>Video</metadata:contentType>
<media:show>Trading Nation</media:show>
<metadata:country>US</metadata:country>
<metadata:provider>NBCU</metadata:provider>
<metadata:channel>CNBC</metadata:channel>
<title>These stocks are flashing a bullish sign into the new year</title>
<description>A handful of stocks are showing an auspicious sign heading into the new year -- a golden cross. Monster, Delta, HP, ConocoPhillips, and Ralph Lauren have either seen or are about to see their 50-day moving average cross above their 200-day. Boris Schlossberg of BK Asset Management and Matt Maley of Miller Tabak discuss.</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 21:12:07 GMT</pubDate>
<metadata:updatedDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 21:12:07 GMT</metadata:updatedDate>
<category>Trading Nation</category>
<media:content medium="video" bitrate="4500" url="http://pdl.iphone.cnbc.com//VCPS/Y2019/M12D31/7000115740/3ED5-TN-123119-SEG1_MBR_4500.mp4"/>
</item>
<item>
<media:thumbnail url="https://image.cnbcfm.com/api/v1/image/106316924-tengleron2019losersbeing2020winners.jpg?v=1577823716"/>
<link>https://www.cnbc.com/video/2019/12/31/the-2019-laggards-that-could-be-2020-winners.html</link>
<media:keywords>Lam Research Corp</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>ABIOMED Inc</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Occidental Petroleum Corp</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>L Brands Inc</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Gap Inc</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Macy's Inc</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Kraft Heinz Co</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Retail and wholesale</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Investment strategy</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Investment strategy</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Stock markets</media:keywords>
<guid>106316906</guid>
<media:network>US</media:network>
<media:duration>179</media:duration>
<metadata:contentType>Video</metadata:contentType>
<media:show>Closing Bell</media:show>
<metadata:country>US</metadata:country>
<metadata:provider>NBCU</metadata:provider>
<metadata:channel>CNBC</metadata:channel>
<title>The 2019 laggards that could be 2020 winners</title>
<description>CNBC's "Closing Bell" team discusses markets on the last day of 2019 with Nancy Tengler of Laffer Tengler Investments and Keith Bliss of iQ Capital USA.</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 21:11:01 GMT</pubDate>
<metadata:updatedDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 21:11:01 GMT</metadata:updatedDate>
<category>Closing Bell</category>
<media:content medium="video" bitrate="4500" url="http://pdl.iphone.cnbc.com//VCPS/Y2019/M12D31/7000115739/1577825637691-TenglerBlisson2019losersbeing2020winners_MBR_4500.mp4"/>
</item>
<item>
<media:thumbnail url="https://image.cnbcfm.com/api/v1/image/106301178-1576611792659gettyimages-1188990853.jpeg?v=1577822795"/>
<link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/12/31/what-happened-to-the-stock-market-on-tuesday.html</link>
<content:encoded>
<![CDATA[ <img src="https://image.cnbcfm.com/api/v1/image/106301178-1576611792659gettyimages-1188990853.jpeg?v=1577822795&amp;w=1910&amp;h=1000" data-licensor-name="Wang Ying | Xinhua News Agency | Getty Images" width="1910" alt="Traders work at the New York Stock Exchange in New York, the United States, on Dec. 13, 2019." id="106301178" height="1000"></img><h4>Dow Jones Industrial Average rose 76 points</h4><p>The <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/.DJI&amp;&amp;doc=106316914">Dow</a>&nbsp;rose 76.30 points, or 0.27% to end the day at 28,538.44. The <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/.SPX&amp;&amp;doc=106316914">S&amp;P 500</a>&nbsp;was up 0.29% to 3,230.78. The <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/.IXIC&amp;&amp;doc=106316914">Nasdaq Composite</a> ended the day up 0.30% at 8,972.60. Stocks traded in a tight range for most of Tuesday's session as Wall Street wrapped up a banner year.</p><h4>Street ends blockbuster 2019 with a slight gain</h4><p>Wall Street ended the year on with a slight gain in the final moments of trading. Earlier in the day, investors received news on the U.S.-China trade front. President Donald Trump announced he will sign phase one of the U.S.-China trade deal on Jan. 15. The S&amp;P 500 and Nasdaq notched their biggest one-year gains since 2013. Tuesday also marked the last trading day of the decade, with the S&amp;P 500 notching a gain of more than 188% in that time.</p><h4>Apple rises slightly, Mylan leads</h4><p><a href="https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/AAPL&amp;&amp;doc=106316914">Apple</a> shares rose 0.73% while <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/MYL&amp;&amp;doc=106316914">Mylan</a> gained 3.45% and was the best-performing stock in the S&amp;P 500. Meanwhile, shares of Chinese electric vehicle company <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/9866-HK&amp;&amp;doc=106316914">NIO</a> jumped 8.06% after Bank of America upgraded the stock to neutral from outperform.</p><h4>What happens next?</h4><p>Thursday's market session will feature the release of jobless claims and manufacturing data. Also, it will be the first trading day of the new year. Read more <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2019/12/31/outlook-for-thursday-new-year-jobless-claims-and-manufacturing-pmi.html?&amp;doc=106316914">here</a>.</p><p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/c/CNBC?sub_confirmation=1"><em><strong>Subscribe to CNBC on YouTube.</strong></em></a></p> ]]>
</content:encoded>
<media:keywords>Jrwrap</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Markets</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Breaking News: Markets</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Stock markets</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Investment strategy</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Wall Street</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Dow Jones Industrial Average</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>S&P 500 Index</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>NASDAQ Composite</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Apple Inc</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Mylan NV</media:keywords>
<media:keywords>Nio Inc</media:keywords>
<author>Fred Imbert</author>
<guid>106316914</guid>
<metadata:contentType>Story</metadata:contentType>
<metadata:country>US</metadata:country>
<metadata:provider>NBCU</metadata:provider>
<metadata:channel>CNBC</metadata:channel>
<title>Here's what happened to the stock market on Tuesday</title>
<description>Stocks traded in a tight range for most of Tuesday's session as Wall Street wrapped up a banner year.</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 21:10:40 GMT</pubDate>
<metadata:updatedDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 21:10:40 GMT</metadata:updatedDate>
<category>Markets</category>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
